{"_id":"8e1706526193a305043ecbfe32f04553","id":"2021060102","type":"CET6","title":"SectionB","directions":"In this section, you are going to read a passage with ten statements attached to it. Each statement contains information given in one of the paragraps. Identify the paragraph from which the information is derived. You may choose aparagraph more than once. Each paragraph is marked with a letter. Answer the questions by marking the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2.","article":["A) Brains, brains, brains. People are fascinated by brain research. And yet it can be hard to point to places where our education system is really making use of the latest neuroscience(神经科学) findings. But there is one happy link where research is meeting practice: bilingual(双语的) education. “In the last 20 years or so, there's been a virtual explosion of research on bilingualism,” says Judith Kroll, a professor at the University of California, Riverside.","B) Again and again, researchers have found, “bilingualism is an experience that shapes our brain for life,” in the words of Gigi Luk, an associate professor at Harvard's Graduate School of Education. At the same time, one of the hottest trends in public schooling is what’s often called dual-language or two-way immersion programs.","C) Traditional programs for English-language learners, or ELLs, focus on assimilating students into English as quickly as possible. Dual-language classrooms, by contrast, provide instruction across subjects to both English natives and English learners, in both English and a target language. The goal is functional bilingualism and biliteracy for all students by middle school. New York City, North Carolina, Delaware, Utah, Oregon and Washington state are among the places expanding dual-language classrooms.","D) The trend flies in the face of some of the culture wars of two decades ago, when advocates insisted on “English first” education. Most famously, California passed Proposition 227 in 1998. It was intended to sharply reduce the amount of tie that English-language learners spent in bilingual settings. Proposition 58, passed by California voters on November 8, largely reversed that decision, paving the way for a huge expansion of bilingual education in the state that has the largest population of English-language learners.","E) Some of the insistence on English-first was founded on research produced decades ago, in which bilingual students underperformed monolingual(单语的) English speakers and had lower IQ scores. Today’s scholars, like Ellen Bialystok at York University in Toronto, say that research was “deeply flawed.” “Earlier research looked at socially disadvantaged groups,” agrees Antonella Sorace at the University of Edinburgh in Scotland. “This has been completely contradicted by recent research” that compares groups more similar to each other.","F) So what does recent research say about the potential benefits of bilingual education? It turns out that, in many ways, the real trick to speaking two languages consists in managing not to speak one of those languages at a given moment—which is fundamentally a feat of paying attention. Saying “Goodbye” to mom and then “Guten tag” to your teacher, or managing to ask for a crayola roja instead of a red crayon(蜡笔), requires skills called “inhibition” and “task switching.” These skills are subsets of an ability called executive function.","G) People who speak two languages often outperform monolinguals on general measures of executive function. “Bilinguals can pay focused attention without being distracted and also improve in the ability to switch from one task to another,” says Sorace.","H) Do these same advantages benefit a child who begins learning a second language in kindergarten instead of as a baby? We don't yet know. Patterns of language learning and language use are complex. But Gigi Luk at Harvard cites at least one brain-imaging study on adolescents that shows similar changes in brain structure when compared with those who are bilingual from birth, even when they didn't begin practicing a second language in earnest before late childhood.","I) Young children being raised bilingual have to follow social cues to figure out which language to use with which person and in what setting. As a result, says Sorace, bilingual children as young as age 3 have demonstrated a head start on tests of perspective-taking and theory of mind—both of which are fundamental social and emotional skills.","J) About 10 percent of students in the Portland, Oregon public schools are assigned by lottery to dual-language classrooms that offer instruction in Spanish, Japanese or Mandarin, alongside English. Jennifer Steele at American University conducted a four-year, randomized trial and found that the dual-language students outperformed their peers in English-reading skills by a full school-year’s worth of learning by the end of middle school. Because the effects are found in reading, not in math or science where there were few differences, Steele suggests that learning two languages make students more aware of how language works in general.","K) The research of Gigi Luk at Harvard offers a slightly different explanation. She has recently done a small study looking at a group of 100 fourth-graders in Massachusetts who had similar reading scores on a standard test, but very different language experiences. Some were foreign-language dominant and others were English natives. Here's what’s interesting. The students who were dominant in a foreign language weren't yet comfortably bilingual; they were just starting to learn English. Therefore, by definition, they had a much weaker English vocabulary than the native speakers. Yet they were just as good at interpreting a text. “This is very surprising,” Luk says. ”You would expect the reading comprehension performance to mirror the vocabulary—it’s a cornerstone of comprehension.”","L) How did the foreign-language dominant speakers manage this feat? Well, Luk found, they also scored higher on tests of executive functioning. So, even though they didn't have huge mental dictionaries to draw on, they may have been great puzzle-solvers, taking into account higher-level concepts such as whether a single sentence made sense within an overall storyline. They got to the same results as the monolinguals, by a different path.","M) American public school classrooms as a whole are becoming more segregated by race and class. Dual-language programs can be an exception. Because they are composed of native English speakers deliberately placed together with recent immigrants, they tend to be more ethnically and economically balanced. And there is some evidence that this helps kids of all backgrounds gain comfort with diversity and different cultures.","N) Several of the researchers also pointed out that, in bilingual education, non-English-dominant students and their families tend to feel that their home language is heard and valued, compared with a classroom where the home language is left at the door in favor of English. This can improve students' sense of belonging and increase parents' involvement in their children's education, including behaviors like reading to children. “Many parents fear their language is an obstacle, a problem, and if they abandon it their child will integrate better,” says Antonella Sorace of the University of Edinburgh. “We tell them they’re not doing their child a favor by giving up their language.”","O) One theme that was striking in speaking to all these researchers was just how strongly they advocated for dual-language classrooms. Thomas and Collier have advised many school systems on how to expand their dual language programs, and Sorace runs “bilingualism Matters,” an international network of researchers who promote bilingual education projects. This type of advocacy among scientists is unusual; even more so because the “bilingual advantage hypothesis” is being challenged once again.","P) A review of studies published last year found that cognitive advantages failed to appear in 83 percent of published studies, though in a separate analysis, the sum of effects was still significantly positive. One potential explanation offered by the researchers is that advantages that are measurable in the very young and very old tend to fade when testing young adults at the peak of their cognitive powers. And, they countered that no negative effects of bilingual education have been found. So, even if the advantages are small, they are still worth it. Not to mention one obvious, outstanding fact: “Bilingual children can speak two languages!”"],"options":["36. A study found that there are similar changes in brain structure between those who are bilingual from birth and those who start learning a second language later. ","37. Unlike traditional monolingual programs, bilingual classrooms aim at developing students' ability to use two languages by middle school.","38. A study showed that dual-language students did significantly better than their peers in reading English texts.","39. About twenty years ago, bilingual practice was strongly discouraged, especially in California.","40. Ethnically and economically balanced bilingual classrooms are found to be helpful for kids to get used to social and cultural diversity.","41. Researchers now claim that earlier research on bilingual education was seriously flawed.","42. According to a researcher, dual-language experiences exert a lifelong influence on one's brain.","43. Advocates of bilingual education argued that it produces positive effects though they may be limited.","44. Bilingual speakers often do better than monolinguals in completing certain tasks because they can concentrate better on what they are doing.","45. When their native language is used, parents can become more involved in their children's education."],"analysisList":[{"order":36,"answer":"H","analysis":"【精析】H段④句指出﹐脑成像研究表明,童年晚期才开始学习外语的青少年会发生与天生双语使用者类似的大脑结构变化。试题是对该句信息的改写,其中start learning a second language later是对didn't begin practicing a second language in earnest before late childhood的同义替换。"},{"order":37,"answer":"C","analysis":"【精析】C段①至③句通过对比手段聚焦双语课堂特点及目的:传统英语学习项目注重于让学生尽快融入英语环境;双语课堂则用两种语言开展教学,旨在让学生到中学时获得实用性双语能力。试题是对双语课堂特点的概括,Unlike 体现其与传统项目的不同,ability to use two languages 是对原文functional bilingualism and biliteracy 的同义改写。"},{"order":38,"answer":"J","analysis":"【精析】J段介绍双语教育提升阅读理解能力的作用,其中②句介绍研究结果;双语学生对其他同学的英语阅读技能优势达到了相当于一整个学年的学习。试题是对该句研究结果的同义改写,其中significantly better是对a full school-year's worth of learning 的准确概括。"},{"order":39,"answer":"D","analysis":"【精析】D段①至③句介绍双语教育过去如何遭到抵制;二十年前的文化战争中,人们高举“英语优先”的大旗,加利福尼亚州更是专门发布法律,限制英语学习者置身于双语环境的时间。试题是对原文信息的提炼,其中 strongly discouraged 归纳了“English first” education与 sharply reduce the amount of time...spent in bilingual settings的共同指向“双语教育受阻”。"},{"order":40,"answer":"M","analysis":"【精析】M段介绍双语教育帮助学生融入多族裔、多文化环境。③④句具体说明双语课堂(they回指上句中的Dual-language programs)如何起作用:把英语母语使用者和新移民有意地混在一起→在族裔和经济状况的分布上都更为均衡→有助于学生适应多族裔、多文化环境。试题是对原文信息的整合,getused to同义改写gain comfort with。"},{"order":41,"answer":"E","analysis":"【精析】E段②句介绍当代研究者对以往双语教育研究的看法:漏洞百出(that research回指①句中“数十年前发表的研究”)。试题是对本句信息的复现, earlier research on bilingual education明确了句中that research所指。"},{"order":42,"answer":"B","analysis":"【精析】B段①句引用一名研究者的原话确认双语能力的相关发现“对大脑带来终生影响”。试题是对该句内容的概括, exert...influence是对shapes的同义改写。"},{"order":43,"answer":"P","analysis":"【精析】Р段③至⑤句指出双语教育研究者/倡导者的看法:双语教育尚未发现有负面影响,而且益处即便小也仍然值得;双语教育至少能让孩子学会两门语言。试题是对双语教育正面影响描述的提炼，positive...though they may be limited是对even if the advantages are small...still worth it 的同义改写。"},{"order":44,"answer":"G","analysis":"【精析】G段两句指出,双语使用者比单语使用者在执行功能测评中的表现更好,更能高度集中注意力。试题是对本段信息的提炼和总结，其中completing certain tasks是对general measures ofexecutive function的明确化, because是对原文两句逻辑关系的揭示(专注度更高,因而任务完成得更好)。"},{"order":45,"answer":"N","analysis":"【精析】N段①句指出,双语教育让英语学习者的母语得到重视;②句进而指出,这能提高学生的归属感和家长对孩子教育的参与度。试题是对原文信息的截取, native language is used同义替换home language is heard。"}]}
{"_id":"8e1706526193a305043ecbff3e7053fa","id":"2020090203","type":"CET6","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are 2 passages in this section. Each passage is followed by some questions or unfinished statements. For each of them there are four choices marked A), B), C) and D). You should decide on the best choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["Danielle Steel, the 71-year-old romance novelist is notoriously productive, having published 179 books at a rate of up to seven a year. But a passing reference in a recent profile by Glamour magazine to her 20-hour workdays prompted an outpouring of admiration.","Steel has given that 20-hour figure when describing her “exhausting” process in the past: “I start the book and don't leave my desk until the first draft is finished.” She goes from bed, to desk, to bath, to bed, avoiding all contact aside from phone calls with her nine children. “I don't comb my hair for weeks,” she says. Meals are brought to her desk, where she types until her fingers swell and her nails bleed.","The business news website Quartz held Steel up as an inspiration, writing that if only we all followed her “actually extremely liberating” example of industrious sleeplessness, we would be quick to see results.","Some argue that so many adults have abandoned drawing because we've miscategorized it and given it a very narrow definition.In his book, Stick Figures:Drawing as a Human Practice,Professor D.B. Dowd argues that we have misfiled the significance of drawing because we see it as a professional skill instead of a personal capacity. We mistakenly think of“good”Well, indeed. With research results showing the cumulative effects of sleep loss and its impact on productivity, doubt has been voiced about the accuracy of Steel’s self-assessment. Her output maybe undeniable, but sceptics have suggested that she is guilty of erasing the role of ghost writers(代笔人) at worst, gross exaggeration at best.","Steel says working 20 hours a day is “pretty brutal physically.” But is it even possible? “No,” says Maryanne Taylor of the Sleep Works. While you could work that long, the impact on productivity would make it hardly worthwhile. If Steel was routinely sleeping for four hours a night, she would be drastically underestimating the negative impact, says Alison Gardiner, founder of the sleep improvement programme Sleep station. “It’s akin to being drunk.”","It’s possible that Steel is exaggerating the demands of her schedule. Self-imposed sleeplessness has “become a bit of a status symbol”, says Taylor, a misguided measure to prove how powerful and productive you are. Margaret Thatcher was also said to get by on four hours a night, while the 130-hour workweeks endured by tech heads has been held up as key to their success.","That is starting to change with increased awareness of the importance of sleep for mental health. “People are starting to realise that sleep should not be something that you fit in between everything else,” says Taylor.","But it is possible—if statistically extremely unlikely—that Steel could be born a “short sleeper” with an unusual body clock, says sleep expert Dr. Sophie Bostock. “It’s probably present in fewer than 1% of the population.”","Even if Steel does happen to be among that tiny minority, says Bostock, it's “pretty irresponsible” to suggest that 20-hour days are simply a question of discipline for the rest of us."],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"What do we learn from the passage about Glamour magazine readers?","options":["A) They are intrigued by the exotic romance in Danielle Steel's novels.","B) They are amazed by the number of books written by Danielle Steel.","C) They are deeply impressed by Danielle Steel's daily work schedule.","D) They are highly motivated by Danielle Steel’s unusual productivity."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查与《魅力》杂志相关的事实。根据Glamour magazine定位至首段②句(a passingreference. . . by Glamour magazine to.. . )。","analysis":"【精析】②句指出《魅力》杂志的一篇简介提到斯蒂尔每天工作20个小时,这激起了一片赞赏之声,即读者折服于这一工作时长惊人的日程安排。C是对②句语义的准确概括,为正确项。"},{"order":47,"question":"What did the business news website Quartz say about Danielle Steel?","options":["A) She could serve as an example of industriousness.","B) She proved we could liberate ourselves from sleep.","C) She could be an inspiration to novelists all over the world.","D) She showed we could get all our work done without sleep. "],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查对石英财经网观点的理解。根据business news website Quartz定位至第三段(Thebusiness news website Quartz held Steel up as an inspiration.. . )。","analysis":"【精析】该段后半句指出,如果我们都能效仿斯蒂尔勤奋的不眠行为( follow her. . . example ofindustrious sleeplessness),我们很快就能看到成果。可见石英财经网认为,斯蒂尔的超短睡眠是勤奋刻苦的表现,而且是可以为人们效仿的,A是对原文的正确理解。"},{"order":48,"question":"What do sceptics think of Danielle Steel's work schedule claims?","options":["A) They are questionable.","B) They are alterable.","C) They are irresistible.","D) They are verifiable."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查持怀疑态度的人的看法。根据sceptics定位至第四段③句(sceptics have suggested that...)","analysis":"【精析】第四段③句指出,持怀疑态度的人认为,斯蒂尔可能严重夸大了事实,或者可能干脆抹去了代笔人的角色。可见持怀疑态度的人认为斯蒂尔隐瞒了真实情况,她的说法是值得怀疑的,A是对原句的准确概括。"},{"order":49,"question":"What does Maryanne Taylor think of self-imposed sleeplessness?","options":["A) It may turn out to be key to a successful career.","B) It may be practiced only by certain tech heads.","C) It may symbolise one's importance and success.","D) It may well serve as a measure of self-discipline."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查人物观点。根据Maryanne Taylor和self-imposed sleeplessness定位至第六段②句(Self-imposed sleeplessness has. . . says Taylor. . . )。","analysis":"【精析】第六段②句指出“自我强加的不眠行为已经有点变成一种地位的象征(status symbol)”，C项importance and success同义改写status,为正确项。"},{"order":50,"question":"How does Dr. Sophie Bostock look at the 20-hour daily work schedule?","options":["A) One should not adopt it without consulting a sleep expert.","B) The general public should not be encouraged to follow it.","C) One must be duly self-disciplined to adhere to it.","D) The majority must adjust their body clock for it."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查人物观点。根据Dr. Sophie Bostock和20-hour daily work schedule定位至末段( says Bostock. . .that 20-hour days are. . . )。","analysis":"【精析】末段指出“对大部分并非短睡眠者的人说每天工作20个小时不过是自律问题,这是非常不负责任的”,换言之,不应该向人们传达“只要自律就能每天工作20个小时”的思想, simply a question ofdiscipline是鼓励人们效仿这种做法的说辞，The general public同义改写the rest of us(与 that tiny minority相对),B是对末段的正确解读。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["Organic agriculture is a relatively untapped resource for feeding the Earth's population, especially in the face of climate change and other global challenges. That's the conclusion I reached in reviewing 40 years of science comparing the long-term prospects of organic and conventional farming.","The review study, “Organic Agriculture in the 21st Century,” is featured as the cover story for the February issue of the journal Nature Plants. It is the first to compare organic and conventional agriculture across the main goals of sustainability identified by the National Academy of Sciences: productivity, economics, and environment.","Critics have long argued that organic agriculture is inefficient, requiring more land to yield the same amount of food. It's true that organic farming produces lower yields, averaging 10 to 20 percent less than conventional. Advocates contend that the environmental advantages of organic agriculture far outweigh the lower yields, and that increasing research and breeding resources for organic systems would reduce the yield gap. Sometimes excluded from these arguments is the fact that we already produce enough food to more than feed the world's 7.4 billion people but do not provide adequate access to all individuals.","In some cases, organic yields can be higher than conventional. For example, in severe drought conditions, which are expected to increase with climate change in many areas, organic farms can produce as good, if not better, yields because of the higher water-holding capacity of organically farmed soils. What science does tell us is that mainstream conventional farming systems have provided growing supplies of food and other products but often at the expense of other sustainability goals.","Conventional agriculture may produce more food, but it often comes at a cost to the environment. Biodiversity loss, environmental degradation, and severe impacts on ecosystem services have not only accompanied conventional farming systems but have often extended well beyond their field boundaries. With organic agriculture, environmental costs tend to be lower and the benefits greater.","Overall, organic farms tend to store more soil carbon, have better soil quality, and reduce soil erosion compared to their conventional counterparts. Organic agriculture also creates less soil and water pollution and lower greenhouse gas emissions. And it’s more energy-efficient because it doesn't rely on synthetic fertilizers or pesticides.","Organic agriculture is also associated with greater biodiversity of plants, animals, insects and microorganisms as well as genetic diversity. Biodiversity increases the services that nature provides and improves the ability of farming systems to adapt to changing conditions.","Despite lower yields, organic agriculture is more profitable for farmers because consumers are willing to pay more. Higher prices, called price premiums, can be justified as a way to compensate farmers for providing ecosystem services and avoiding environmental damage or external costs."],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":"What do we learn from the conclusion of the author's review study?","options":["A) More resources should be tapped for feeding the world's population.","B) Organic farming may be exploited to solve the global food problem.","C) The long-term prospects of organic farming are yet to be explored.","D) Organic farming is at least as promising as conventional farming."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查研究结论。由the conclusion of the author's review study定位至首段②句(...That's the conclusion I.. .),再由②句指代词精准定位至其所回指的①句。","analysis":"【精析】文首句直陈指出:就养活地球人口而言,有机农业这种农耕方式还有待开发利用,尤其是在面临气候变化及其他全球挑战之际。言外之意即为,可以考虑利用有机农业这种耕种方式来解决当前全球人口粮食问题。故B正确。"},{"order":52,"question":"What is the critics' argument against organic farming?","options":["A) It cannot meet the need for food.","B) It cannot increase farm yields.","C) It is not really practical.","D) It is not that productive."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查批评者反对有机农业的理由。由critics’argument定位至第三段①句(Critics havelong argued that. . . )。","analysis":"【精析】第三段①句介绍批评者的观点:有机农业效率低下,需要更多的土地才能产出同等数量的粮食。可见,批评者认为有机农业“不够高产”,D项not. . . productive是对此缺陷的恰当概括。"},{"order":53,"question":"What does the author think should be taken into account in arguing about organic farming?","options":["A) Growth in world population.","B) Deterioration in soil fertility.","C) Inequality in food distribution.","D) Advance in farming technology."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查作者的观点。由 should be taken into account in arguing定位至第三段末句( Sometimes excluded from these arguments is.. . )。","analysis":"【精析】第三段末句指出作者的看法:关于有机农业的争论有时会忽略这样一个事实,那就是,如今生产的粮食已足够养活全世界人口,而(之所以有饥饿现象是因为)没有提供足够的机会让每个人都能获取到这些粮食。“总量足够但并非每个人都有”这一矛盾体现出“粮食的分配不均”,此为作者认为应当考虑的因素。Inequality是对do not provide adequate access to all individuals的合理概括。"},{"order":54,"question":"What does science tell us about conventional farming?","options":["A) It will not be able to meet global food demand.","B) It is not conducive to sustainable development.","C) It will eventually give away to organic farming.","D) It is going mainstream throughout the world."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查对传统农业的评价。由What. . . science tell us, conventional farming定位至第五段( What science does tell us is. . . conventional farming. . . )。","analysis":"【精析】第五段指出,科学告诉我们,传统耕种方式尽管高产,但却往往以其他可持续目标为代价，故B正确,其中not conducive to(对……不利)同义转述at the expense of(以……为代价,给……带来伤害)。"},{"order":55,"question":"Why does the author think higher prices of organic farm produce are justifiable?","options":["A) They give farmers going organic a big competitive edge.","B) They motivate farmers to upgrade farming technology.","C) Organic farming costs more than conventional farming.","D) Organic farming does long-term good to the ecosystem."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查作者认为有机农产品高价合理的原因。由higher prices , justifiable定位至末段末句( Higher prices. . .can be justified.. . )。","analysis":"【精析】末段末句指出,有机农产品价高合乎情理,其溢价部分其实是对采用有机耕种的农民的一种补偿,他们为我们的生态系统提供了服务,而且规避了环境污染、外部成本等问题。言外之意为,实行有机耕种的农民对环境作出了许多无法量化的长远贡献,那么其农产品的溢价就算是对此环境效益的合理补偿。does long-term good to the ecosystem是对providing ecosystem services and avoiding environmentaldamage or external costs的合理概括。"}]}]}
{"_id":"8e1706526193a305043ecc004907f324","id":"2020090303","type":"CET6","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are 2 passages in this section. Each passage is followed by some questions or unfinished statements. For each of them there are four choices marked A), B), C) and D). You should decide on the best choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["Danielle Steel, the 71-year-old romance novelist is notoriously productive, having published 179 books at a rate of up to seven a year. But a passing reference in a recent profile by Glamour magazine to her 20-hour workdays prompted an outpouring of admiration.","Steel has given that 20-hour figure when describing her “exhausting” process in the past: “I start the book and don't leave my desk until the first draft is finished.” She goes from bed, to desk, to bath, to bed, avoiding all contact aside from phone calls with her nine children. “I don't comb my hair for weeks,” she says. Meals are brought to her desk, where she types until her fingers swell and her nails bleed.","The business news website Quartz held Steel up as an inspiration, writing that if only we all followed her “actually extremely liberating” example of industrious sleeplessness, we would be quick to see results.","Some argue that so many adults have abandoned drawing because we've miscategorized it and given it a very narrow definition.In his book, Stick Figures:Drawing as a Human Practice,Professor D.B. Dowd argues that we have misfiled the significance of drawing because we see it as a professional skill instead of a personal capacity. We mistakenly think of“good”Well, indeed. With research results showing the cumulative effects of sleep loss and its impact on productivity, doubt has been voiced about the accuracy of Steel’s self-assessment. Her output maybe undeniable, but sceptics have suggested that she is guilty of erasing the role of ghost writers(代笔人) at worst, gross exaggeration at best.","Steel says working 20 hours a day is “pretty brutal physically.” But is it even possible? “No,” says Maryanne Taylor of the Sleep Works. While you could work that long, the impact on productivity would make it hardly worthwhile. If Steel was routinely sleeping for four hours a night, she would be drastically underestimating the negative impact, says Alison Gardiner, founder of the sleep improvement programme Sleep station. “It’s akin to being drunk.”","It’s possible that Steel is exaggerating the demands of her schedule. Self-imposed sleeplessness has “become a bit of a status symbol”, says Taylor, a misguided measure to prove how powerful and productive you are. Margaret Thatcher was also said to get by on four hours a night, while the 130-hour workweeks endured by tech heads has been held up as key to their success.","That is starting to change with increased awareness of the importance of sleep for mental health. “People are starting to realise that sleep should not be something that you fit in between everything else,” says Taylor.","But it is possible—if statistically extremely unlikely—that Steel could be born a “short sleeper” with an unusual body clock, says sleep expert Dr. Sophie Bostock. “It’s probably present in fewer than 1% of the population.”","Even if Steel does happen to be among that tiny minority, says Bostock, it's “pretty irresponsible” to suggest that 20-hour days are simply a question of discipline for the rest of us."],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"What do we learn from the passage about Glamour magazine readers?","options":["A) They are intrigued by the exotic romance in Danielle Steel's novels.","B) They are amazed by the number of books written by Danielle Steel.","C) They are deeply impressed by Danielle Steel's daily work schedule.","D) They are highly motivated by Danielle Steel’s unusual productivity."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查与《魅力》杂志相关的事实。根据Glamour magazine定位至首段②句(a passingreference. . . by Glamour magazine to.. . )。","analysis":"【精析】②句指出《魅力》杂志的一篇简介提到斯蒂尔每天工作20个小时,这激起了一片赞赏之声,即读者折服于这一工作时长惊人的日程安排。C是对②句语义的准确概括,为正确项。"},{"order":47,"question":"What did the business news website Quartz say about Danielle Steel?","options":["A) She could serve as an example of industriousness.","B) She proved we could liberate ourselves from sleep.","C) She could be an inspiration to novelists all over the world.","D) She showed we could get all our work done without sleep. "],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查对石英财经网观点的理解。根据business news website Quartz定位至第三段(Thebusiness news website Quartz held Steel up as an inspiration.. . )。","analysis":"【精析】该段后半句指出,如果我们都能效仿斯蒂尔勤奋的不眠行为( follow her. . . example ofindustrious sleeplessness),我们很快就能看到成果。可见石英财经网认为,斯蒂尔的超短睡眠是勤奋刻苦的表现,而且是可以为人们效仿的,A是对原文的正确理解。"},{"order":48,"question":"What do sceptics think of Danielle Steel's work schedule claims?","options":["A) They are questionable.","B) They are alterable.","C) They are irresistible.","D) They are verifiable."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查持怀疑态度的人的看法。根据sceptics定位至第四段③句(sceptics have suggested that...)","analysis":"【精析】第四段③句指出,持怀疑态度的人认为,斯蒂尔可能严重夸大了事实,或者可能干脆抹去了代笔人的角色。可见持怀疑态度的人认为斯蒂尔隐瞒了真实情况,她的说法是值得怀疑的,A是对原句的准确概括。"},{"order":49,"question":"What does Maryanne Taylor think of self-imposed sleeplessness?","options":["A) It may turn out to be key to a successful career.","B) It may be practiced only by certain tech heads.","C) It may symbolise one's importance and success.","D) It may well serve as a measure of self-discipline."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查人物观点。根据Maryanne Taylor和self-imposed sleeplessness定位至第六段②句(Self-imposed sleeplessness has. . . says Taylor. . . )。","analysis":"【精析】第六段②句指出“自我强加的不眠行为已经有点变成一种地位的象征(status symbol)”，C项importance and success同义改写status,为正确项。"},{"order":50,"question":"How does Dr. Sophie Bostock look at the 20-hour daily work schedule?","options":["A) One should not adopt it without consulting a sleep expert.","B) The general public should not be encouraged to follow it.","C) One must be duly self-disciplined to adhere to it.","D) The majority must adjust their body clock for it."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查人物观点。根据Dr. Sophie Bostock和20-hour daily work schedule定位至末段( says Bostock. . .that 20-hour days are. . . )。","analysis":"【精析】末段指出“对大部分并非短睡眠者的人说每天工作20个小时不过是自律问题,这是非常不负责任的”,换言之,不应该向人们传达“只要自律就能每天工作20个小时”的思想, simply a question ofdiscipline是鼓励人们效仿这种做法的说辞，The general public同义改写the rest of us(与 that tiny minority相对),B是对末段的正确解读。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["Organic agriculture is a relatively untapped resource for feeding the Earth's population, especially in the face of climate change and other global challenges. That's the conclusion I reached in reviewing 40 years of science comparing the long-term prospects of organic and conventional farming.","The review study, “Organic Agriculture in the 21st Century,” is featured as the cover story for the February issue of the journal Nature Plants. It is the first to compare organic and conventional agriculture across the main goals of sustainability identified by the National Academy of Sciences: productivity, economics, and environment.","Critics have long argued that organic agriculture is inefficient, requiring more land to yield the same amount of food. It's true that organic farming produces lower yields, averaging 10 to 20 percent less than conventional. Advocates contend that the environmental advantages of organic agriculture far outweigh the lower yields, and that increasing research and breeding resources for organic systems would reduce the yield gap. Sometimes excluded from these arguments is the fact that we already produce enough food to more than feed the world's 7.4 billion people but do not provide adequate access to all individuals.","In some cases, organic yields can be higher than conventional. For example, in severe drought conditions, which are expected to increase with climate change in many areas, organic farms can produce as good, if not better, yields because of the higher water-holding capacity of organically farmed soils. What science does tell us is that mainstream conventional farming systems have provided growing supplies of food and other products but often at the expense of other sustainability goals.","Conventional agriculture may produce more food, but it often comes at a cost to the environment. Biodiversity loss, environmental degradation, and severe impacts on ecosystem services have not only accompanied conventional farming systems but have often extended well beyond their field boundaries. With organic agriculture, environmental costs tend to be lower and the benefits greater.","Overall, organic farms tend to store more soil carbon, have better soil quality, and reduce soil erosion compared to their conventional counterparts. Organic agriculture also creates less soil and water pollution and lower greenhouse gas emissions. And it’s more energy-efficient because it doesn't rely on synthetic fertilizers or pesticides.","Organic agriculture is also associated with greater biodiversity of plants, animals, insects and microorganisms as well as genetic diversity. Biodiversity increases the services that nature provides and improves the ability of farming systems to adapt to changing conditions.","Despite lower yields, organic agriculture is more profitable for farmers because consumers are willing to pay more. Higher prices, called price premiums, can be justified as a way to compensate farmers for providing ecosystem services and avoiding environmental damage or external costs."],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":"What do we learn from the conclusion of the author's review study?","options":["A) More resources should be tapped for feeding the world's population.","B) Organic farming may be exploited to solve the global food problem.","C) The long-term prospects of organic farming are yet to be explored.","D) Organic farming is at least as promising as conventional farming."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查研究结论。由the conclusion of the author's review study定位至首段②句(...That's the conclusion I.. .),再由②句指代词精准定位至其所回指的①句。","analysis":"【精析】文首句直陈指出:就养活地球人口而言,有机农业这种农耕方式还有待开发利用,尤其是在面临气候变化及其他全球挑战之际。言外之意即为,可以考虑利用有机农业这种耕种方式来解决当前全球人口粮食问题。故B正确。"},{"order":52,"question":"What is the critics' argument against organic farming?","options":["A) It cannot meet the need for food.","B) It cannot increase farm yields.","C) It is not really practical.","D) It is not that productive."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查批评者反对有机农业的理由。由critics’argument定位至第三段①句(Critics havelong argued that. . . )。","analysis":"【精析】第三段①句介绍批评者的观点:有机农业效率低下,需要更多的土地才能产出同等数量的粮食。可见,批评者认为有机农业“不够高产”,D项not. . . productive是对此缺陷的恰当概括。"},{"order":53,"question":"What does the author think should be taken into account in arguing about organic farming?","options":["A) Growth in world population.","B) Deterioration in soil fertility.","C) Inequality in food distribution.","D) Advance in farming technology."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查作者的观点。由 should be taken into account in arguing定位至第三段末句( Sometimes excluded from these arguments is.. . )。","analysis":"【精析】第三段末句指出作者的看法:关于有机农业的争论有时会忽略这样一个事实,那就是,如今生产的粮食已足够养活全世界人口,而(之所以有饥饿现象是因为)没有提供足够的机会让每个人都能获取到这些粮食。“总量足够但并非每个人都有”这一矛盾体现出“粮食的分配不均”,此为作者认为应当考虑的因素。Inequality是对do not provide adequate access to all individuals的合理概括。"},{"order":54,"question":"What does science tell us about conventional farming?","options":["A) It will not be able to meet global food demand.","B) It is not conducive to sustainable development.","C) It will eventually give away to organic farming.","D) It is going mainstream throughout the world."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查对传统农业的评价。由What. . . science tell us, conventional farming定位至第五段( What science does tell us is. . . conventional farming. . . )。","analysis":"【精析】第五段指出,科学告诉我们,传统耕种方式尽管高产,但却往往以其他可持续目标为代价，故B正确,其中not conducive to(对……不利)同义转述at the expense of(以……为代价,给……带来伤害)。"},{"order":55,"question":"Why does the author think higher prices of organic farm produce are justifiable?","options":["A) They give farmers going organic a big competitive edge.","B) They motivate farmers to upgrade farming technology.","C) Organic farming costs more than conventional farming.","D) Organic farming does long-term good to the ecosystem."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查作者认为有机农产品高价合理的原因。由higher prices , justifiable定位至末段末句( Higher prices. . .can be justified.. . )。","analysis":"【精析】末段末句指出,有机农产品价高合乎情理,其溢价部分其实是对采用有机耕种的农民的一种补偿,他们为我们的生态系统提供了服务,而且规避了环境污染、外部成本等问题。言外之意为,实行有机耕种的农民对环境作出了许多无法量化的长远贡献,那么其农产品的溢价就算是对此环境效益的合理补偿。does long-term good to the ecosystem是对providing ecosystem services and avoiding environmentaldamage or external costs的合理概括。"}]}]}
{"_id":"8e1706526193a305043ecc013b7a8f6e","id":"2020120103","type":"CET6","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are 2 passages in this section.Each passage is followed by some questions or wnfinishedstatements. For each of them there are four choices marked A),B),C) and D). You should decide on thebest choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["What is the place of art in a culture of inattention? Recent visitors to the Louvre report that tourists can now spend only a minute in front of the Mona Lisa before being asked to move on. Much of that time, for some of them, is spent taking photographs not even of the painting but of themselves with the painting in the background.","One view is that we have democratised tourism and gallery-going so much that we have made it effectively impossible to appreciate what we’ve travelled to see. In this oversubscribed society, experience becomes a commodity like any other. There are queues to climb Mt. Jolmo Lungma as well as to see famous paintings. Leisure, thus conceived, is hard labour, and returning to work becomes a well-earned break from the ordeal.","What gets lost in this industrialised haste is the quality of looking. Consider an extreme example, the late philosopher Richard Wollheim. When he visited the Louvre he could spent as much as four hours sitting before a painting. The first hour, he claimed, was necessary for misperceptions to be eliminated. It was only then that the picture would begin to disclose itself. This seems unthinkable today, but it is still possible to organise. Even in the busiest museums there are many rooms and many pictures worth hours of contemplation which the crowds largely ignore. Sometimes the largest crowds are partly the products of bad management; the Mona Lisa is such a hurried experience today partly because the museum is being reorganised. The Uffizi in Florence, another site of cultural pilgrimage, has cut its entry queues down to seven minutes by clever management. And there are some forms of art, those designed to be spectacles as well as objects of contemplation, which can work perfectly well in the face of huge crowds.","Olafur Eliasson’s current Tate Modern show, for instance, might seem nothing more than an entertainment, overrun as it is with kids romping (喧闹地玩耍)in fog rooms and spray mist installations. But it’s more than that: where Eliasson is at his most entertaining, he is at his most serious too, and his disorienting installations bring home the reality of the destructive effects we are having on the planet — not least what we are doing to the glaciers of Eliasson’s beloved Iceland.","Marcel Proust, another lover of the Louvre, wrote: “ It is only through art that we can escape from ourselves and know how another person sees the universe, whose landscapes would otherwise have remained as unknown as any on the moon.”If any art remains worth seeing, it must lead us to such escapes. But a minute in front of a painting in a hurried crowd won’t do that."],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"What does the scene at the Louvre demonstrate according to the author?","options":["A) The enormous appeal of a great piece of artistic work to tourists.","B) The near impossibility of appreciating art in an age of mass tourism.","C) The ever-growing commercial value of long-cherished artistic works.","D) The real difficulty in getting a glimpse at a masterpiece amid a crowd."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查“卢浮宫的景象”的本质。由the Louvre定位至首段。","analysis":"【精析】该段②③句描述卢浮宫内的场景;卢浮宫要求参观者只能在《蒙娜丽莎》前停留一分钟，而在这宝贵的一分钟中,很多游客只顾着拍照,而且是以画像为背景给自己拍照,并非把画作拍下来。第二段①句作者对这种场景作出评价:我们现在将旅游和观展变得太过普及,以至于根本无法欣赏奔波前往观看的作品,即在大众旅游时代欣赏艺术愈发困难,可见B正确。该项The near impossibility同义转述effectively impossible, an age of mass tourism概括we have democratised tourism...so much所展现的时代特点。"},{"order":47,"question":"Why did the late philosopher Richard Wollheim spend four hours before a picture?","options":["A) It takes time to appreciate a piece of art fully.","B) It is quite common to misinterpret artistic works.","C) The longer people contemplate a picture, the more likely they will enjoy it.","D) The more time one spends before a painting, the more valuable one finds it."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查“Wollheim长时间欣赏画作”的原因。由Richard Wollheim定位至第三段②至⑤句。","analysis":"【精析】第三段②句首先明确Wollheim的事例为极端例子(就此追溯至①句观点句“工业化的仓促和快旅游风尚使旅游及观展品质降低”并判断②句Wollheim事例意在以过去情形之“慢”凸显当今情形之“快”),③句进而描述事例本身“Wollheim 会在画作前停留四个小时之久”,④⑤句接着援引Wollheim本人话语说明原因:第一个小时是为消除误解,后面三个小时才开始逐渐领悟画作真谛。A正确。"},{"order":48,"question":"What does the case of the Uffizi in Florence show?","options":["A) Art works in museums should be better taken care of.","B) Sites of cultural pilgrimage are always flooded with visitors.","C) Good management is key to handling large crowds of visitors.","D) Large crowds of visitors cause management problems for museums."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查“乌菲兹美术馆事例”的写作目的,可定位至第三段⑨句(并追溯至⑥句观点句)。","analysis":"【精析】第三段⑥句指出“Wolheim式的深度参观(即长时间停留欣赏画作以领悟其真谛)可通过组织管理来实现”,⑦⑧句指出“博物馆人满为患,资源配置不当,游客仓促参观的原因是管理不善或正处修整期”,⑨句介绍乌菲兹美术馆做法“通过巧妙的管理极大地缩短了入场排队时间”。综合可知,文章提及乌菲兹美术馆的事例是为了说明“良好的管理可应对大批游客,为其提供更多空间及时间来实现深度参观”,C正确。"},{"order":49,"question":"What do we learn from Olafur Eliasson’s current Tate Modern show?","options":["A) Children learn to appreciate art works most effectively while they are playing.","B) It is possible to combine entertainment with appreciation of serious art.","C) Art works about the environment appeal most to young children.","D) Some forms of art can accommodate huge crowds of visitors."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查“奥拉维尔·埃利亚松的展览”的相关事实细节,可定位至第四段。","analysis":"【精析】第四段先指出“埃利亚松的展览看起来不过是一场娱乐活动,满是嬉闹的孩子”,后转而指出“这次展览不止于此,埃利亚松娱乐大众,也给人以严肃之感,整个展览意在警示人类行为对环境的影响”。综合可知,该展览表明“娱乐消遣和欣赏严肃艺术可以很好地结合起来”,B正确。"},{"order":50,"question":"What can art do according to Marcel Proust?","options":["A) Enable us to live a much fuller life.","B) Allow us to escape the harsh reality.","C) Help us to see the world from a different perspective.","D) Urge us to explore the unknown domain of the universe."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查马塞尔·普鲁斯特对于“艺术的作用”的观点﹐由Marcel Proust可定位至末段。","analysis":"【精析】末段①句引用普鲁斯特之言指出“唯有通过艺术,我们才能超脱自我,了解他人如何看待天地万物”。由此可知,普鲁斯特认为“艺术可以帮助我们超越自身的固有认知,从另一个角度看世界”,C正确。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["Every five years, the government tries to tell Americans what to put in their bellies. Eat more vegetables. Dial back the fats. It’s all based on the best available science for leading a healthy life. But the best available science also has a lot to say about what those food choices do to the environment, and some researchers are annoyed that new dietary recommendations of the USDA (United States Department of Agriculture) released yesterday seem to utterly ignore that fact.","Broadly, the 2016 - 2020 dietary recommendations aim for balance: More vegetables, leaner meats and far less sugar.","But Americans consume more calories per capita than almost any other country in the world. So the things Americans eat have a huge impact on climate change. Soil tilling releases carbon dioxide, and delivery vehicles emit exhaust. The government’s dietary guidelines could have done a lot to lower that climate cost. Not just because of their position of authority: The guidelines drive billions of dollars of food production through federal programs like school lunches and nutrition assistance for the needy.","On its own, plant and animal agriculture contributes 9 percent of all the country’s greenhouse gas emissions. That’s not counting the fuel burned in transportation, processing, refrigeration, and other waypoints between farm and belly. Red meats are among the biggest and most notorious emitters, but trucking a salad from California to Minnesota in January also carries a significant burden. And greenhouse gas emissions aren’t the whole story. Food production is the largest user of fresh water, largest contributor to the loss of biodiversity, and a major contributor to using up natural resources.","All of these points and more showed up in the Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee’s scientific report, released last February. Miriam Nelson chaired the subcommittee in charge of sustainability for the report, and is disappointed that eating less meat and buying local food aren’t in the final product. “Especially if you consider that eating less meat, especially red and processed, has health benefits,” she says.","So what happened? The official response is that sustainability falls too far outside the guidelines’ official scope, which is to provide “nutritional and dietary information.”","Possibly the agencies in charge of drafting the decisions are too close to the industries they are supposed to regulate. On one hand, the USDA is compiling dietary advice. On the other, their clients are US agriculture companies.","The line about keeping the guidelines’ scope to nutrition and diet doesn’t ring quite right with researchers. David Wallinga, for example, says, “ In previous guidelines, they’ve always been concerned with things like food security — which is presumably the mission of the USDA. You absolutely need to be worried about climate impacts and future sustainability if you want secure food in the future.”"],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":"Why are some researchers irritated at the USDA's 2016-2020 Dietary Guidelines?","options":["A) It ignores the harmful effect of red meat and processed food on health.","B) Too much emphasis is given to eating less meat and buying local food.","C) The dietary recommendations are not based on medical science.","D) It takes no notice of the potential impact on the environment."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查一些研究者恼怒于美国农业部的膳食指南的原因,根据题干关键词some researchers irritated at the USDA's 2016—2020 Dietary Guidelines定位至第一段末句(...some researchersare annoyed that new dietary recommendations of the USDA...)。","analysis":"【精析】第一段末句指出,一些研究者恼怒的是美国农业部的新版膳食建议似乎完全忽视了“食物选择会对环境造成诸多影响”这一事实(that fact的具体所指),故D正确。"},{"order":52,"question":"Why does the author say the USDA could have contributed a lot to lowering the climate cost through its dietary guidelines?","options":["A) It has the capacity and the financial resources to do so.","B) Its researchers have already submitted relevant proposals.","C) Its agencies in charge of drafting the guidelines have the expertise.","D) It can raise students’ environmental awareness through its programs."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查作者的观点。由题干关键词Why...contributed a lot to lowering the climate cost定位至第三段④⑤句(.. .could have done a lot to lower that climate cost，Not just because of...)。","analysis":"【精析】第三段④句指出政府(USDA)的膳食指南本可以为降低气候成本作出巨大贡献,⑤句进而点明原因:这些指导方针不仅仅象征着权威,还可通过各种形式的联邦计划推动数十亿美元的粮食生产。由此可推断,美国农业部不仅有能力(具有威望),也有财力(享有财政资源)去降低气候成本,A符合文意。"},{"order":53,"question":"What do we learn from the Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee’s scientific report?","options":["A) Food is easily contaminated from farm to belly.","B) Greenhouse effect is an issue still under debate.","C) Modern agriculture has increased food diversity.","D) Farming consumes most of our natural resources."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查膳食指南咨询委员会科学报告的具体内容。由题干关键词the Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee's scientific report可初步定位至第五段首句,再根据首句中these points的回指功能最终锁定第四段。","analysis":"【精析】第四段末句指出,粮食生产是自然资源枯竭的主要原因,D中most of,consumes...natural resources分别对应句中major contributor, using up natural resources。"},{"order":54,"question":"What may account for the neglect of sustainability in the USDA’s Dietary Guidelines according to the author?","options":["A) Its exclusive concern with Americans’ food safety.","B) Its sole responsibility for providing dietary advice.","C) Its close ties with the agriculture companies.","D) Its alleged failure to regulate the industries."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查作者对“膳食指南为何忽略可持续性”的看法,由题干关键词What may account for the neglect of sustainability定位至第六段及之后的内容(So what happened...sustainability falls too far outside...)。","analysis":"【精析】第七段①句中作者先概述指出,负责草拟膳食决议的官方机构(USDA)与其本应监管的行业走得过近,后于③句明确本应被监管行业的具体所指“美国农业公司”,可见C正确。"},{"order":55,"question":"What should the USDA do to achieve food security according to David Wallinga?","options":["A) Give top priority to things like nutrition and food security.","B) Endeavor to ensure the sustainable development of agriculture.","C) Fulfill its mission by closely cooperating with the industries.","D) Study the long-term impact of climate change on food production."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查文中人物所提的建议。根据题干关键词David Wallinga定位至第八段②③句。","analysis":"【精析】第八段③句大卫·沃林加指出,美国农业部若想在未来保障粮食安全,就必须关注气候影响和未来可持续性,意即美国农业部要想实现粮食安全,就必须考虑农业发展/粮食生产的可持续性,B正确。"}]}]}
{"_id":"8e1706526193a305043ecc02686f8cf8","id":"2020120203","type":"CET6","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are.2 passages in this section.Each passage is followed by some questions or wnfinishedstatements. For each of them there are four choices marked A),B),C) and D). You should decide on thebest choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["Vegetarians would prefer not to be compelled to eat meat. Yet the reverse compulsion ( 51 if!) 1s hidden in the proposals for a new plant-based “planetary diet.” Nowhere is this more visible than in India.","Earlier this year, the EAT-Lancet Commission released its global report on nutrition and called for a global shift to a more plant-based diet and for “ substantially reducing consumption of animal source foods.” In countries like India, that call could become a tool to aggravate an already tense political situation and stress already undernourished populations.","The EAT report presumes that“traditional diets”in countries like India include little red meat,which might be consumed only on special occasions or as minor ingredients in mixed dishes.","In India, however, there is a vast difference between what people would wish to consume andwhat they have to consume because of innumerable barriers around class, religion, culture,cost,geography, etc. Policymakers in India have traditionally pushed for a cereal-heavy“vegetarian diet”on a meat-eating population as a way of providing the cheapest sources of food.","Currently, under an aggressive Hindu nationalist government, Muslims, Christians, disadvantagedclasses and indigenous communities are being compelled to give up their traditional foods.","None of these concerns seem to have been appreciated by the EAT-Lancet Commission's representative,Brent Loken, who said“India has got such a great example'in sourcing protein from pants","But how much of a model for the world is India's vegetarianism? In the Global Hunger Index2019, the country ranks 102nd out of 117.Data from the National Family Health Survey indicate thatonly 10 percent of infants of 6 to 23 months are adequately fed.","Which is why calls for a plant-based diet modeled on India risk offering another whip with which to beat already vulnerable communities in developing countries.","A diet directed at the affluent West fails to recognize that in low-income countries undernourished children are known to benefit from the consumption of milk and other animal source foods,improving cognitive functions, while reducing the prevalence of nutritional deficiencies as well as mortality.","EAT-Lancet claimed its intention was to “spark conversations”among all Indian stakeholders.Yet vocal critics of the fod processing industry and food fortification strategies have been left out ofthe debate. But the most conspicuous omission may well be the absence of India's farmers.","The government, however,seems to have given the report a thumps-up.Rather than addressing chronic hunger and malnutrition through an improved access to wholesome and nutrient-dense foods, the government is opening the door for company-dependent solutions, ignoring the environmental and economic cost, which will destroy local food systems. It's a model full of danger for future generations."],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"What is more visible in India than anywhere else according to the passage?","options":["A) People's positive views on the proposals for a “planetary diet.”","B) People's reluctance to be compelled to eat plant-based food.","C) People's preferences for the kind of food they consume.","D) People's unwillingness to give up their eating habits."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查印度相比其他国家的突出之处。由题干关键信息more visible in India定位至首段末句。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案]B。首段末句指出:这一点(this)在印度最为明显。this回指前一句中the reversecompulsion,即与首句“强迫素食者吃肉”相反的“强迫肉食者吃素”。可见,印度的突出之处在于人们(概指食肉的人)不愿被迫吃素(即食用植物性食品),故B正确。"},{"order":47,"question":"What would the EAT-Lancet Commission's report do to many people in countries like India?","options":["A) Radically change their dietary habits.","B) Keep them further away from politics.","C) Make them even more undernourished.","D) Substantially reduce their food choices."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查EAT-Lancet 委员会报告对印度等国的民众的影响。由题干关键词the EAT-Lancet Commission's report 定位至其首次出现的第二段。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案]C。第二段①句介绍EAT-Lancet委员会报告所呼吁的内容,②句指出该呼吁对印度等国的影响:使本已紧张的政治局势恶化,给本就营养不良的人群加压。C符合后一影响,即加剧人们营养不良的问题。"},{"order":48,"question":"What do we learn from the passage about food consumption in India?","options":["A) People's diet will not change due to the EAT-Lancet report.","B) Many people simply do not have access to foods they prefer.","C) There is a growing popularity of a cereal-heavy vegetarian diet.","D) Policymakers help remove the barriers to people's choice of food."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查EAT-Lancet 委员会报告对印度等国的民众的影响。由题干关键词the EAT-Lancet Commission's report 定位至其首次出现的第二段。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案]C。第二段①句介绍EAT-Lancet委员会报告所呼吁的内容,②句指出该呼吁对印度等国的影响:使本已紧张的政治局势恶化,给本就营养不良的人群加压。C符合后一影响,即加剧人们营养不良的问题。"},{"order":49,"question":"What does the passage say about a plant-based diet modeled on India?","options":["A) It may benefit populations whose traditional diet is meat-based.","B) It may be another blow to the economy in developing countries.","C) It may help narrow the gap between the rich and poor countries.","D) It may worsen the nourishment problem in low-income countries."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查“效仿印度的植物性饮食”相关信息,由关键词a plant-based diet modeled on India初步定位至第七、八段(a model for the world is India's vegetarianism、a plant-based diet modeled on India)。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案] D。第七段首句设问“印度素食主义的典范作用有多大?”,②③句说明印度的饥饿问题与婴儿温饱问题严峻。第八段继而明确效仿印度植物性饮食的危害:进一步打击发展中国家本已脆弱的社会群体。.综合可知,植物性饮食会使发展中国家的营养问题恶化,D正确"},{"order":50,"question":"How does the Indian government respond to the EAT-Lancet Commission's proposals?","options":["A) It accepts them at the expense of the long-term interests of its people.","B) It intends them to spark conversations among all Indian stakeholders.","C) It gives them approval regardless of opposition from nutrition experts.","D) It welcomes them as a tool to address chronic hunger and malnutrition."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查印度政府对EAT-Lancet委员会提议的反应。由Indian government. the EAT-Lancet Commission's proposals可定位至末段(The government... the report、the government is...It's... )。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案] A。末段先指出“印度政府似乎对EAT-Lancet委员会的提议赞赏有加”,后介绍这一态度的影响:政府对“依靠公司”的处理方案敞开了大门，忽视经济和环境成本，破坏当地食品系统，最终危害后代。可见,印度政府不顾提议对人民的深远危害而将其接受,A正确。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["Back in 1964,in his book Games People Play,psychiatrist Eric Berne described a pattern of conversation he called“Why Don't You—Yes But”, which remains one of the most rritating aspects of everyday social life. The person adopting the strategy is usually a chronic complainer. Something is terrible about their relationship, job, or other situation, and they moan about it ceaselessly, but find some excuse to dismiss any solution that's proposed. The reason, of course, is that on some level they don't want a solution; they want to be validated in their position that the world is out to get them. If they can “win, the game-dismissing every suggestion until their interlocutor( 对话者) gives up in annoyance-they get to feel pleasurably righteous ( 正当的 ) in their resentments and excused from any obligation to change.","Part of the trouble here is the so-called responsibility/fault fallacy（谬误）.When you're feeling hard done by—taken for granted by your partner,say, or obliged to work for a half-witted boss—it's easy to become attached to the position that it's not your job to address the matter, and that doing so would be an admission of fault. But there's a confusion here. For example, if I were to discover a newborn at my front door, it wouldn't be my fault, but it most certainly would be my responsibility. There would be choices to make, and no possibility of avoiding them, since trying to ignore the matter would be a choice. The point is that what goes for the baby on the doorstep is true in all cases: even if the other person is 100? the wrong, there's nothing to be gained, long-term, from using this as a justification to evade responsibility","Should you find yourself on the receiving end of this kind of complaining, there's an ingenious way to shut it down—which is to agree with it, ardently. Psychotherapist Lori Gottlieb describes this as“over-validation”. For one thing, you'll be spared further moaning,since the other person's motivation was to confirm her beliefs, and now you're confirming them. But for another,as Gottlieb notes, people confronted with over-validation often hear their complaints afresh and start arguingback. The notion that they're utterly powerless suddenly seems unrealistic—not to mention rather annoying—so they're prompted instead to generate ideas about how they might change things.","“And then, sometimes, something magical might happen,”Gottlieb writes. The other person“might realise she's not as trapped as you are saying she is, or as she feels.”Whichilustrates the irony of the responsibility/fault fallacy: evading responsibility feels comfortable, but turns out to be a prison; whereas assuming responsibility feels unpleasant, but ends up being freeing."],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":"What is characteristic of a chronic complainer, according to psychiatrist Eric Berne?","options":["A) People tend to think that one should not be held responsible for others'mistakes.","B) It is easy to become attached to the position of overlooking one's own fault.","C) People are often at a loss when confronted with a number of choices.","D) A distinction should be drawn between responsibility and fault."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查惯性抱怨者的特征，根据题干中人名Eric Berne以及关键词characteristic of achronic complainer定位至第一段②至⑤句(... a chronic complainer... )。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案] C。第一段②③句指出惯性抱怨者的行为特征:当人际关系、工作或其他方面出现糟糕的事情时,他们便会一边喋喋不休地抱怨,一边却又找借口拒绝别人提出来的任何解决方案。⑤句进一步指出他们的心理特征:自己的怨艾理所应当,没有任何责任/义务做出改变。故C正确，选项中dismiss others'proposals、taking no responsibility for tackling the problem 同义替换原文dismiss any solution that'sproposed.、excused from any obligation to change."},{"order":52,"question":"What does the author try to illustrate with the example of the newborn on one's doorstep?","options":["A) People tend to think that one should not be held responsible for others' mistakes.","B) It is easy to become attached to the position of overlooking one's own fault.","C) People are often at a loss when confronted with a number of choices.","D) A distinction should be drawn between responsibility and fault."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查事例的写作目的。由题干关键词the newborn on one's doorstep 定位至第二段④⑤⑥句(if 1 were to discover a newborn. .. what goes for the baby on the doorstep... )。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案] D。第二段①②③句先引出新概念“责任/过错谬误”,即,将“责任”与“过错”混为一谈,④⑤⑥句再以“家门口的新生儿”为例指出“责任”与“过错”并不对等,以“过错并不在我”作为逃避责任的借口并不可取。可见“新生儿”的事例旨在解释“责任/过错谬误”这一概念，即“责任不等于过错/二者应当有所区分”。"},{"order":53,"question":"What does the author advise people to do to chronic complainers?","options":["A) Stop them from going further by agreeing with them.","B) Listen to their complaints ardently and sympathetically.","C) Ask them to validate their beliefs with further evidence.","D) Persuade them to clarify the confusion they have caused."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查作者就应对惯性抱怨者的建议，由advise... to do定位至第三段(there's aningenious way to... )。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案] A。第三段①②句指出,针对惯性抱怨者,使其停止抱怨的方法是对其抱怨表示赞同，可见A正确,Stop them from going further 是对原文shut it down所含语义的明示。"},{"order":54,"question":"What happens when chronic complainers receive over-validation?","options":["A) They are motivated to find ingenious ways to persuade their interlocutor.","B) They are prompted to come up with ideas for making possible changes.","C) They are stimulated to make more complaints.","D) They are encouraged to start arguing back."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查惯性抱怨者被过度认可后的反应。由receive over-validation定位至第三段。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案] B。第三段③句指出惯性抱怨者受到过度认可后的反应一:停止抱怨。④⑤句指出反应二:重新审视并反驳这种抱怨,并开始想办法改变现状。可见B正确,其中are prompted to come up with ideas 对应⑤句they' re prompted... to generate ideas; making possible changes对应how they might change things。"},{"order":55,"question":"How can one stop being a chronic complainer according to the author?","options":["A) Analysing the so-called responsibility/fault fallacy.","B) Avoiding hazardous traps in everyday social life.","C) Assuming responsibility to free oneself.","D) Awaiting something magical to happen."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查摆脱习惯性抱怨的方法,根据各选项关键词“责任/过错谬误”“困境”“神奇之事”以及试题命制顺序原则可定位至末段。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案] C。末段首两句先承上继续说明过度认可给惯性抱怨者带来的认知改变:他们并非深陷困境、除了抱怨外无计可施,而是具备主动权、有能力改变现状。末句随后揭示这一转变的启示:只有承担责任才能获得自由、解脱自我。可见C正确，其中Assuming responsibility to free oneself 概括assumingresponsibility feels unpleasant, but ends up being freeing 暗含的应有做法。"}]}]}
{"_id":"8e1706526193a305043ecc0311c8107e","id":"2020120303","type":"CET6","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are 2 passages in this section. Each passage is followed by some questions or unfinished statements. For each of them there are four choices marked A), B), C) and D). You should decide on the best choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["Why does social media trigger feelings of loneliness and inadequacy? Because instead of being real life, it is, for the most part, impression management, a way of marketing yourself, carefully choosing and filtering the pictures and words to put your best face forward.","Online “friends” made through social media do not follow the normal psychological progression of an interpersonal relationship. You share neither physical time nor emotional conversations over the Internet. You simply communicate photographs and catchy posts to a diverse group of people whom you have “friended” or “followed” based on an accidental interaction. This is not to say that your social media friends can’t be real friends. They absolutely can, but the two are not synonymous.","Generally speaking, there are no unfiltered comments or casually taken photos on our social media pages. And, rightfully so, because it wouldn’t feel safe to be completely authentic and vulnerable with some of our “ friends ” whom we don’t actually know or with whom trust has yet to be built.","Social media can certainly be an escape from the daily grind, but we must be cautioned against the negative effects, such as addiction, on a person’s overall psychological well-being.","As humans, we yearn for social connection. Scrolling (滚动)through pages of pictures and comments, however, does not provide the same degree of fulfillment as face-to-face interactions do. Also, we tend to idealize others’ lives and compare our downfalls to their greatest accomplishments, ending in feelings of loneliness and inadequacy.","Social media can lead people on the unhealthy quest for perfection. Some people begin to attend certain events or travel to different places so that they can snap that “ perfect ” photo. They begin to seek validation through the number of people who “ like ” their posts. In order for it to play a psychologically healthy role in your social life, social media should supplement an already healthy social network. Pictures and posts should be byproducts of life’s treasured moments and fun times, not the planned and calculated image that one is putting out into cyberspace in an attempt to fill insecurities or unmet needs.","Ultimately, social media has increased our ability to connect with various types of people all over the globe. It has opened doors for businesses and allowed us to stay connected to people whom we may not otherwise get to follow. However, social media should feel like a fun experience, not one that contributes to negative thoughts and feelings. If the latter is the case, increasing face-to-face time with trusted friends, and minimizing time scrolling online, will prove to be a reminder that your social network is much more rewarding than any “ like,” “ follow ” or “ share ” can be."],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"What does the author imply social media may do to our life?","options":["A) It may facilitate our interpersonal relationships.","B) It may filter our negative impressions of others.","C) It may make us feel isolated and incompetent.","D) It may render us vulnerable and inauthentic."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查社交媒体对人们生活的影响。根据social media和 do to our life定位至首段①句( Why does social media trigger.. .)。","analysis":"【精析】首段①句设问“为什么社交媒体会引发孤独感和能力不足之感”,这暗示作者观点:社交媒体会让人们感到孤独和无能为力。C正确,选项同义改写trigger feelings of loneliness and inadequacy。"},{"order":47,"question":"Why do people post comments selectively on social media?","options":["A) They do not find all their online friends trustworthy.","B) They want to avoid offending any of their audience.","C) They do not want to lose their followers.","D) They are eager to boost their popularity."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查人们在社交媒体上选择性地发表评论的原因。根据 Why和 post commentsselectively定位至第二段⑥⑦句(no unfiltered comments. . . rightfully so，because.. .)。","analysis":"【精析】第二段⑥句指出社交媒体页面上不会出现未经筛选的评论(即题干所述的现象),⑦句解释原因(so 指代⑥句所述内容):人们未与某些网友建立信任关系,因此不敢完全展示真实的自己。A正确。"},{"order":48,"question":"What are humans inclined to do according to the passage?","options":["A) Exaggerate their life’s accomplishments.","A) Exaggerate their life’s accomplishments.","C) Paint a rosy picture of other people’s lives.","D) Learn lessons from other people’s downfalls."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查人们的行为倾向。题干中humans、inclined to对应第四段的humans/ we tend to。","analysis":"【精析】第四段③句指出我们人类(we与上句humans同指)倾向于把别人的生活理想化,并把自己的失败与他们最大的成就相比较,C正确。"},{"order":49,"question":"What is the author’s view of pictures and posts on social media?","options":["A) They should record the memorable moments in people’s lives.","B) They should be carefully edited so as to present the best image.","C) They should be shown in a way that meets one’s security needs.","D) They should keep people from the unhealthy quest for perfection."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查作者对社交媒体内容的看法。结合题干关键词pictures and posts和“题文同序”原则可定位到第五段(photo.posts、 Pictures and posts)。","analysis":"【精析】第五段末句指出,(社交媒体上的)图片和帖子应该是人们生活中珍贵时刻和快乐时光的副产品,言外之意为,人们发布图片和帖子的目的应该是纪念生活中的难忘时刻,故A正确。"},{"order":50,"question":"What does the author advise people to do when they find their online experience unconstructive?","options":["A) Use social media to increase their ability to connect with various types of people.","B) Stay connected to those whom they may not otherwise get to know and befriend.","C) Try to prevent negative thoughts and feelings from getting into the online pages.","D) Strengthen ties with real-life friends instead of caring about their online image."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查作者建议(如何让网络体验更积极有益),可定位至末段:该段③句( social media)experience,negative thoughts and feelings对应题干中online experience , unconstructive(非建设性的;无助益的)。","analysis":"【精析】末段末句指出,若社交媒体让你产生消极想法和情绪(即用户体验缺乏建设性/积极意义),不妨多与好友面对面交流,尽量减少使用社交媒体的时间,最终你会明白现实中的社交网络比社交媒体更有意义( scrolling online和any “like，”“follow”or “share”均指向社交媒体);且由上文可知社交媒体会诱发病态完美主义,让用户过度在意自己的网络形象。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["Imagine that an alien species landed on Earth and, through their mere presence, those aliens caused our art to vanish, our music to homogenize, and our technological know-how to disappear. That is effectively what humans have been doing to our closest relatives — chimps (大猩猩).","Back in 1999, a team of scientists led by Andrew Whiten showed that chimps from different parts of Africa behave very differently from one another. Some groups would get each other’s attention by rapping branches with their knuckles (指关节)，while others did it by loudly ripping leaves with their teeth. The team identified 39 of these traditions that are practiced by some communities but not   others — a pattern that, at the time, hadn’t been seen in any animal except humans. It was evidence, the team said, that chimps have their own cultures.","It took a long time to convince skeptics that such cultures exist, but now we have plenty of examples of animals learning local traditions from one another.","But just when many scientists have come to accept the existence of animal cultures, many of those cultures might vanish. Ammie Kalan and her colleagues have shown, through years of intensive fieldwork, that the very presence of humans has eroded the diversity of chimp behavior. Where we flourish, their cultures wither. It is a bitterly ironic thing to learn on the 20th anniversary of Whiten’s classic study.","“ It’s amazing to think that just 60 years ago, we knew next to nothing of the behavior of our sister species in the wild,” Whiten says. “ But now, just as we are truly getting to know our primate(灵长类)cousins, the actions of humans are closing the window on all we have discovered.”","“ Sometimes in the rush to conserve the species, I think we forget about the individuals,” says Cat Hobaiter, a professor at the University of St. Andrews. “ Each population, each community, even each generation of chimps is unique. An event might only have a small impact on the total population of chimps, but it may wipe out an entire community — an entire culture. No matter what we do to restore habitat or support population growth, we may never be able to restore that culture.”","No one knows whether the destruction of chimp culture is getting worse. Few places have tracked chimp behavior over long periods, and those that have are also more likely to have protected their animals from human influence.","Obviously, conservationists need to think about saving species in a completely new way—by preserving animal traditions as well as bodies and genes. “ Instead of focusing only on the conservation of genetically based entities like species, we now need to also consider culturally based entities,” says Andrew Whiten."],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":"What does the author say we humans have been doing to chimps?","options":["A) Ruining their culture.","B) Accelerating their extinction.","C) Treating them as alien species.","D) Homogenizing their living habits."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查人类一直以来对大猩猩所做之事,由humans have been doing to chimps可定位至首段。","analysis":"【精析】首段①句虚设情境“某外星物种登陆地球,凭一己之力将人类文明毁灭”,②句回归现实，指出“这正是人类一直以来对大猩猩所做之事”,意即“人类一直都在摧毁大猩猩的文化”,A正确。"},{"order":52,"question":"What is the finding of Andrew Whiten’s team?","options":["A) Chimps demonstrate highly developed skills of communication.","B) Chimps rely heavily upon their body language to communicate.","C) Chimps behave in ways quite similar to those of human beings.","D) Different chimp groups differ in their way of communication."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查Andrew Whiten团队的研究发现,可定位至第二段(a team of scientists led byAndrew Whiten showed. . . The team identified.. . )。","analysis":"【精析】第二段①句总述团队发现“非洲不同地区的大猩猩行为大不相同”,②句举例详释“群体间引起对方注意的方式完全不同”,③句进一步指出“研究发现的这种‘一些社群遵从奉行,其他社群则不然’的行为传统已达39种”。可见,不同大猩猩群体的交流方式截然不同,D正确。"},{"order":53,"question":"What did Ammie Kalan and her colleagues find through their intensive fieldwork?","options":["A) Whiten’s classic study has little impact on the diversity of chimp behavior.","B) Chimp behavior becomes less varied with the increase of human activity.","C) Chimps alter their culture to quickly adapt to the changed environment.","D) It might already be too late to prevent animal cultures from extinction."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查Ammie Kalan团队的实地考察发现,可定位至第四段。","analysis":"【精析】第四段①句指出“多种动物文化可能消失不见”②③句介绍Ammie Kalan团队的实地考察发现“正是人类的存在破坏了大猩猩行为的多样性,人类的发展繁荣之地恰是大猩猩文化的凋零之处”,综合可知“人类活动损害了大猩猩行为的多样性”,B正确。"},{"order":54,"question":"What does Cat Hobaiter think we should do for chimp conservation?","options":["A) Try to understand our sister species’ behavior in the wild.","B) Make efforts to preserve each individual chimp community.","C) Study the unique characteristics of each generation of chimps.","D) Endeavor to restore chimp habitats to expand its total population."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查Cat Hobaiter对大猩猩保护方式的建议,可定位至第六段(... says Cat Hobaiter)。","analysis":"【精析】第六段①句指出“人类急于保护整个大猩猩物种,却忽略了个体”,②句强调“大猩猩的每个社群都独一无二”,③④句补充指出“某事件可能对大猩猩整个种群影响极小,却可能彻底摧毁整个社群及整个文化,且社群文化一旦消失则极难复原”,可见,赫伯特认为应努力保全每个大猩猩社群,B正确。"},{"order":55,"question":"What does the author suggest conservationists do?","options":["A) Focus entirely on culturally-based entities rather than genetically-based ones.","B) Place more stress on animal traditions than on their physical conservation.","C) Conserve animal species in a novel and all-round way.","D) Explore the cultures of species before they vanish."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查作者对环保主义者的建议,可定位至第八段句( conservationists need to. .. )。","analysis":"【精析】第八段首句作者提出建议“环境保护主义者需要考虑用一种全新的方式来拯救物种——既保护动物的躯体和基因,也保全它们的传统”,C正确。"}]}]}
{"_id":"8e1706526193a305043ecc0426bae0c9","id":"2021060103","type":"CET6","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are.2 passages in this section.Each passage is followed by some questions or wnfinishedstatements. For each of them there are four choices marked A),B),C) and D). You should decide on thebest choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["Humans are fascinated by the source of their failings and virtues. This preoccupation inevitably eads to an old debate: whether nature or nurture moulds us more. A revolution in genetics has poised this as a modern political question about the character of our society: if personalities are hard-wired into our genes, what can governments do to help us? It feels morally questionable, yet claims of genetic selection by intelligence are making headlines.","This is down to“hereditarian”（遗传论的） science and a recent paper claimed“differences in exam performance between pupils attending selective and non-selective schools mirror the genetic differences between them”. With such an assertion, the work was predictably greeted by a lot of absurd claims about“genetics determining academic success”. What the research revealed was the rather less surprising result: the educational benefits of selective schools largely disappear once pupils' inborn ability and socio-economic background were taken into account. It is a glimpse of the blindingly obvious—and there's nothing to back strongly either a hereditary or environmental argument.","Yet the paper does say children are“unintentionally genetically selected”by the school system. Central to hereditarian science is a tall claim: that identifiable variations in genetic sequences can predict an individual's aptness to learn, reason and solve problems. This is problematic on many levels.A teacher could not seriously tell a parent their child has a low genetic tendency to study when external factors clearly exist. Unlike-minded academics say the inheritability of human traits is scientifically unsound. At best there is a weak statistical association and not a causal link between DNA and intelligence. Yet sophisticated statistics are used to create an intimidatory atmosphere of scientific certainty.","While there's an undoubted genetic basis to individual difference, it is wrong to think that socially defined groups can be genetically accounted for. The fixation on genes as destiny is surely false too. Medical predictability can rarely be based on DNA alone; the environment matters too. Something as complex as intellect is likely to be affected by many factors beyond genes. If hereditarians want to advance their cause it will require more balanced interpretation and not just acts of advocacy.","enetic selection is a way of exerting influence over others,“the ultimate collective control of human destinies,”as writer H. G. Wells put it. Knowledge becomes power and power requires a sense of responsibility. In understanding cognitive ability, we must not elevate discrimination to a science: allowing people to climb the ladder of life only as far as their cells might suggest. This will need a more sceptical eye on the science. As technology progresses, we all have a duty to make sure that we shape a future that we would want to find ourselves in."],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"What did a recent research paper claim?","options":["A) The type of school students attend makes a difference to their future.","B) Genetic differences between students are far greater than supposed.","C) The advantages of selective schools are too obvious to ignore.","D) Students' academic performance is determined by their genes."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查论文观点。由题干a recent research paper定位至第二段①句(a recent paper claimed.. . )。","analysis":"【精析】该段①句指出论文观点“学生的考试成绩差异反映出他们的基因差异”,②句进而描述其引发的类似言论“遗传特征决定学业成功”,可见D项正确。该项是对②句genetics determining academicsuccess的同义转述,明确了①句mirror(反映)一词传达的“考试成绩”与“基因”之间的对应关系。"},{"order":47,"question":"What does the author think of the recent research?","options":["A) Its result was questionable.","B) Its implication was positive. ","C) Its influence was rather negligible.","D) Its conclusions were enlightening. "],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查作者对新近研究的看法。由题干中What. . . the author think定位至第二段②③④句(the rather less surprising result, greeted by a lot of absurd claims,a glimpse of the blindingly obvious,there's nothing to back strongly...a hereditary...argument)。","analysis":"【精析】第二段①句首先指出新近研究的观点:基因决定学生成绩。②③④句分析作者对此的看法:招致了大量荒谬言论,所揭示的结果也并不出奇,透露的是极为明显的事实,遗传决定论并无有力证据支持。由此可见,作者认为这项新近研究的结果有问题。故A项正确,同时排除窜改语义色彩的D项。"},{"order":48,"question":"What does the author say about the relationship between DNA and intelligence?","options":["A) It is one of scientific certainty.","B) It is not one of cause and effect.","C) It is subject to interpretation of statistics.","D) It is not fully examined by gene scientists."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查作者对“DNA和智力的关系”的看法。结合试题命制顺序及题干关键词therelationship between DNA and intelligence可快速定位至第三段倒数第二句(association.. . link between DNA and intelligence)。注:上文多处出现DNA, intelligence相关词汇,但 claims,a...claim提示这些论述均属他人观,点,并非作者观点。","analysis":"【精析】第三段倒数第二句指出“DNA和智力只有以统计数据表明的微弱关联,并无因果关系”，B项中cause and effect意为“原因和结果”,是对⑥句a causal link的同义改写,故正确。"},{"order":49,"question":"What do hereditarians need to do to make their claims convincing?","options":["A) Take all relevant factors into account in interpreting their data.","B) Conduct their research using more sophisticated technology.","C) Gather gene data from people of all social classes.","D) Cooperate with social scientists in their research."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查遗传论者增强自身观点可信性的方法。由hereditarians, make their claims convincing可定位至第四段末句(If hereditarians want to advance their cause)。","analysis":"【精析】末句指出“遗传论者若想推进其事业,就要考量影响智力的各种因素,做出更为全面公正的解读,而不应利用统计数据一味鼓吹夸大基因的作用”。A项Take all relevant factors into account体现末句more balanced 传递的“综合平衡各种因素,全面解读数据”之意。"},{"order":50,"question":"What does the author warn against in the passage?","options":["A) Exaggerating the power of technology in shaping the world.","B) Losing sight of professional ethics in conducting research.","C)Misunderstanding the findings of human cognition research.","D)Promoting discrimination in the name of science."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查作者反对的做法。由题干中warn against可定位至末段③句(we must not... )。","analysis":"【精析】③句明确指出:切勿将歧视抬升为科学。言外之意即为,不要以科学为名助长歧视,D项是对句中elevate discrimination to a science的同义改写。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["Nicola Sturgeon's speech last Tuesday setting out the Scottish government's legislative programme for the year ahead confirmed what was already pretty clear. Scottish councils are set to be the first in the UK with the power to levy charges on visitors, with Edinburgh likely to lead the way.","Tourist taxes are not new. The Himalayan kingdom of Bhutan has a longstanding policy of charging visitors a daily fee. France's tax on overnight stays was introduced to assist thermal spa（温泉） towns to develop， and around half of French local authorities use it today.","But such levies are on the rise. Moves by Barcelona and Venice to deal with the phenomenon of “over-tourism”through the use of charges have recently gained prominence. Japan and Greece are among the countries to have recently introduced tourist taxes.","That the UK lags behind is due to our weak, by international standards,local government, as well as the opposition to taxes and regulation of our aggressively pro-market ruling party. Some UK cities have lobbied without success for the power to levy a charge on visitors. Such levies are no universal remedy as the amounts raised would be tiny compared with what has been taken away by central government since 2010.Sill,it is to be hoped that the Scottish government's bold move will prompt others to act.There is no reason why visitors to the UK, or domestic tourists on holiday in hotspots such as Cornwall, should be exempt from taxation-particularly when vital local services including waste collection, park maintenance and arts and culture spending are under unprecedented strain.","On the contrary,compelling tourists to make a financial contribution to the places they visit beyond their personal consumption should be part of a wider cultural shift. Westerners with disposable incomes have often behaved as if they have a right to go wherever they choose with little regard for the consequences. Just as the environmental harm caused by aviation and other transport must come under far greater scrutiny, the social cost of tourism must also be confronted. This includes the impact of short-term lets on housing costs and quality of life for residents. Several European capitals, including Paris and Berlin,are leading a campaign for tougher regulation by the European Union. It alsoincludes the impact of overcrowding, litter and the kinds of behaviour associated with noisy parties.","There is no“one-size-fits-all”solution to this problem. The existence of new revenue streams for some but not all councils is complicated, and businesses are often opposed, fearing higher costs will make them uncompetitive. But those places that want them must be given the chance to make tourist taxes work."],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":"What do we learn from Nicola Sturgeon's speech?","options":["A) The UK is set to adjust its policy on taxation.","B) Tourists will have to pay a tax to visit Scotland.","C) The UK will take new measures to boost tourism.","D) Edinburgh contributes most to Scotland's tourism."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查“妮古拉·斯特金的讲话内容”,根据题干关键词Nicola Sturgeon 's speech定位至首段。","analysis":"【精析】首段①句首先指出妮古拉·斯特金的讲话关乎苏格兰政府未来一年的立法计划,②句随即指出苏格兰政府将对游客征收税费,爱丁堡可能走在最前面。可见,到苏格兰旅游的游客将需要交税。B项同义改写Scottish councils are set to. . . to levy charges on visitors。"},{"order":52,"question":"How come the UK has been slow in imposing the tourist tax?","options":["A) Its government wants to attract more tourists.","B) The tax is unlikely to add much to its revenue.","C) Its ruling party is opposed to taxes and regulation.","D) It takes time for local governments to reach consensus."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查因果细节“英国迟迟不开征旅游税的原因”,由题干关键词the UK,slow in imposingthe tourist tax 可定位到第四段(the UK lags behind is due to...as well as...)。","analysis":"【精析】第四段①句指出,英国之所以在征收旅游税上落后于他国,一是因为其执政党反对征税与政府管控,二是因为地方政府相较软弱无力。C项同义替换文中the opposition to taxes and regulation ofour aggressively pro-market ruling party。"},{"order":53,"question":"Both international and domestic visitors in the UK should pay tourist tax so as to__·","options":["A) elevate its tourism to international standards","B) improve the welfare of its maintenance workers","C) promote its cultural exchange with other nations","D) ease its financial burden of providing local services"],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查因果细节“英国为何应该开征旅游税”。由题干关键信息可定位至第四段末句。","analysis":"【精析】第四段末句指出,英国的国内外游客均没有理由免税,尤其是在至关重要的当地服务(包括垃圾收集,公园维护以及艺术与文化支出)面临前所未有的压力的情况下。换言之,如果对国内外游客征收旅游税,就可以减轻因提供当地服务而带来的财政负担,故D项正确。"},{"order":54,"question":"What does the author say about Western tourists?","options":["A) They don't seem to care about the social cost of tourism.","B) They don't seem to mind paying for additional services.","C) They deem travel an important part of their life.","D) They subject the effects of tourism to scrutiny."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查“与西方游客相关的内容”。由题干Western tourists定位至第五段②句(Westerners)。","analysis":"【精析】第五段②句指出西方游客的表现:有权去任何想去的地方,却很少考虑因此造成的后果。联系③句“正如航空等交通方式所造成的环境危害必须受到正视一样,旅游业的社会成本(即社会环境危害等)也必须得到正视”可知,西方游客往往很少考虑旅游的社会成本,故A项正确。"},{"order":55,"question":"What are UK people's opinions about the levy of tourist tax?","options":["A) Supportive.","B) Divided. ","C) Skeptical.","D) Unclear."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查人物态度“英国各界人士对征收旅游税的态度”。结合试题命制题文同序原则以及题干关键词UK people's opinions可定位至第六段(councils、businesses)。","analysis":"【精析】第六段首句指出,对上述问题(是否征收旅游税)没有一刀切的解决办法。②③句详细说明首句,部分地方议会(政界人士)态度复杂,商界人士反对,部分地区需要/支持。可知,英国各界人士对征收旅游税的意见并不统一,存在巨大分歧,B项正确。"}]}]}
{"_id":"8e1706526193a305043ecc0553ac2d43","id":"2021060203","type":"CET6","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are 2 passages in this section. Each passage is followed by some questions or unfinished statements. For each of them there are four choices marked A),B),C)and D). You should decide on the best choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["We often think of drawing as something that takes inborn talent, but this kind of thinking stems from our misclassification of drawing as, primarily, an art form rather than a tool for learning.","Researchers, teachers,and artists are starting to see how drawing can positively impact a wide variety of skills and disciplines.","Most of us have spent some time drawing before, but at some point, most of us stop drawing. There are people who don't, obviously, and thank god for that: a world without designers and artists would be a very shabby one indeed.","Some argue that so many adults have abandoned drawing because we've miscategorized it and given it a very narrow definition.In his book, Stick Figures:Drawing as a Human Practice,Professor D.B. Dowd argues that we have misfiled the significance of drawing because we see it as a professional skill instead of a personal capacity. We mistakenly think of“good”drawings as those which work as recreations of the real world, as realistic illusions. Rather, drawing should be recategorized as a symbolic tool.","Human beings have been drawing for 73,000 years. It's part of what it means to be human. We dont have the strength of chimpanzees（大猩猩）because we've given up animal strength to manipulate subtle instruments, like hammers, spears, and—later—pens and pencils. The human hand is an extremely dense network of nerve endings. In many ways, human beings are built to draw.","Some researchers argue that doolling（涂画）activates the brain's so-called default circuit— essentially, the areas of the brain responsible for maintaining a baseline level of activity in the absence of other stimuli. Because of this, some believe that doodling during a boring lecture can help students pay attention.In one study, participants were asked to listen to a list of names while either doodling or sitting still. Those who doodled remembered 29 percent more of the names than those who did not.","There's also evidence that drawing talent is based on how accurately someone perceives the world. The human visual system tends to misjudge size,shape, color,and angles but artists perceive these qualities more accurately than non-artists. Cultivating drawing talent can become an essential tool to improve people's observational skills in fields where the visual is important.","Rather than think of drawing as a talent that some creative people are gifted in, we should consider it as a tool for seeing and understanding the world better—one that just so happens to double as an art form. Both absent-minded doodling and copying from life have been shown to positively affect your memory and visual perception, so complain loudly the next time your school board slashes the art department's budget."],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"What do people generally think about drawing?","options":["A) It is a gift creative people are endowed with.","B) It is a skill that is acquired with practice.","C) It is an art form that is appreciated by all.","D) It is an ability everyone should cultivate."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查人们对绘画的惯常看法。根据题干定位至第一段(We often think of drawing as.. . )。","analysis":"【精析】第一段指出人们将绘画主要当作一种艺术形式而非学习工具,因而常常认为绘画需要天赋(something that takes inborn talent. . .an art form)。"},{"order":47,"question":"What do we learn about designers and artists?","options":["A) They are declining gradually in number.","B) They are keen on changing shabby surroundings.","C) They add beauty and charm to the world.","D) They spend most of their lives drawing."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查设计师和艺术家的相关细节。根据题干定位至第三段末句(...designers and artists...)。","analysis":"【精析】第三段末句指出,没有设计师和艺术家的世界会是一个极为粗陋的世界( very shabby)。即设计师和艺术家的存在为世界增色,使世界变得更加美丽迷人,故C项正确。"},{"order":48,"question":"What does Professor D.B.Dowd argue in his book?","options":["A) Everybody is born with the capacity to draw.","B) Drawing is a skill that requires special training.","C) The value of drawing tends to be overestimated.","D) Drawing should be redefined as a realistic illusion."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查人物观点。根据题干中的人名定位至第四段(Professor D. B. Dowd argues that.. . )。[锁定答案]A。第四段介绍D.B.多德教授的看法:我们错把绘画视作一种专业技能( professional skill),而非个人能力(personal capacity)。换句话说,教授认为绘画并非艺术家专有,而是每个人都拥有的能力。第五段则从生理进化的角度对这种个人能力予以解释:人类双手高度灵活,可操控精巧工具,人人都是天生的画者(are built to draw)。可见A项正确。","analysis":"【精析】本题考查人物观点。根据题干中的人名定位至第四段(Professor D. B. Dowd argues that.. . )。[锁定答案]A。第四段介绍D.B.多德教授的看法:我们错把绘画视作一种专业技能( professional skill),而非个人能力(personal capacity)。换句话说,教授认为绘画并非艺术家专有,而是每个人都拥有的能力。第五段则从生理进化的角度对这种个人能力予以解释:人类双手高度灵活,可操控精巧工具,人人都是天生的画者(are built to draw)。可见A项正确。"},{"order":49,"question":"What have some researchers found from one study about doodling?","options":["A) It is a must for maintaining a base level of brain activity.","B) It can turn something boring into something interesting.","C) It is the most reliable stimulant to activate the brain.","D) It helps improve concentration and memory."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查与涂画相关的研究发现。根据题干中one study. . . doodling定位至第六段③④句(one study. . .doodling. . .Those who doodled.. . )。","analysis":"【精析】第六段③句介绍研究方法:受试者涂画或静坐的同时记人名。④句明确研究发现:边涂画边记者比边静坐边记者多记住了29%的人名。improve concentration and memory准确概括此发现,D项正确。"},{"order":50,"question":"What is characteristic of people with drawing talent?","options":["A) Sensitivity to cognitive stimulation.","B) Subtlety of representation.","C) Accuracy in categorization.","D) Precision in visual perception."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查具有绘画禀赋者的特征。根据题干定位至第七段(drawing talent , Cultivatingdrawing talent)。","analysis":"【精析】第七段①句指出,绘画禀赋是基于人对世界的感知准确度。②句举常见现象予以说明:人类的视觉系统通常会误判事物的大小,形状,颜色和角度,而艺术家比非艺术家更能准确地感知这些属性。综合两句可知,绘画禀赋高者的视觉感知更加准确,D项正确。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["The car has reshaped our cities. It seems to offer autonomy for everyone. There is something almost delightful in the detachment from reality of advertisements showing mass-produced cars marketed as symbols of individuality and of freedom when most of their lives will be spent making short journeys on choked roads.","For all the fuss made about top speeds, cornering ability and acceleration, the most useful gadgets on a modern car are those which work when youre going very slowly: parking sensors, sound systems,and navigation apps which will show a way around upcoming traffic jams. This seems to be one of the few areas where the benefit of sharing personal information comes straight back to the sharer: because these apps know where almost all the users are,and how fast they are moving almost all the time，they can spot traffic congestion（堵塞）very quickly and suggest ways round it.","The problem comes when everyone is using a navigation app which tells them to avoid everyone else using the same gadget. Traffic jams often appear where no one has enough information to avoid them. When a lucky few have access to the knowledge, they will benefit greatly. But when everyone has perfect information, traffic jams simply spread onto the side roads that seem to offer a way round them.","This new congestion teaches us two things. The first is that the promises of technology will never be realised as fully as we hope; they will be limited by their unforeseen and unintended consequences. Siting in a more comfortable car in a different traffic jam is pleasant but hardly the liberation that once seemed to be promised. The second is that self-organisation will not get us where we want to go.The efforts of millions of drivers to get ahead do not miraculously produce a situation in which everyone does better than before, but one in which almost everyone does rather worse. Central control and collective organisation can produce smoother and fairer outcomes, though even that much is never guaranteed.","Similar limits can be foreseen for the much greater advances promised by self-driving cars.Last week, one operated by the taxi company Uber struck and killed a woman pushing her bicycle across a wide road in Arizona.This was the first recorded death involving a car which was supposed to be fully autonomous. Experts have said that it suggests a “catastrophic failure”of technology.","ncreasingly，even Silicon Valley has to acknowledge the costs of the intoxicating（令人陶醉的） hurry that characterises its culture. What traffic teaches us is that reckless and uncontrolled change is as likely to harm us as it is to benefit us, and that thoughtful regulation is necessary for a better future."],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":"What does the author say about car advertisements?","options":["A) They portray drivers who enjoy speed on the road.","B) They present a false picture of the autonomy cars provide.","C) They pursue individuality and originality in design concept.","D) They overestimate the potential market of autonomous cars."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查汽车广告的相关信息。根据car advertisements可定位至首段③句(advertisementsshowing. . .cars)。","analysis":"【精析】首段②句指出汽车似乎赋予了每个人自主权,随后③句指出量产汽车广告将汽车标榜为个性与自由之象征的做法脱离了实际,这些汽车大多数时候是在拥堵的道路上进行短途行驶。可见,汽车广告中宣传的个性和自由与现实生活中的拥堵、消耗不符,B项符合此意,其中 a false picture of sth指“对某事物的不实/虚假描述”。"},{"order":52,"question":"What does the author imply about the various gadgets on cars?","options":["A) They can help to alleviate traffic jams.","B) Most of them are as effective as advertised.","C) Only some can be put to use under current traffic conditions.","D) They are constantly upgraded to make driving easier and safer."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查与汽车上的装置有关的暗含信息。根据gadgets on cars可定位至第二段①句(themost useful gadgets on a modern car)。","analysis":"【精析】第二段①句指出尽管人们特别在意汽车的最高时速、转弯和加速能力,但汽车上最有用的装置还是那些在行车非常缓慢(堵车)时起作用的装置,诸如停车传感器,音响系统导航应用程序等。结合首段末尾暗示的当前交通情形(汽车大多数时候是在拥堵的路上行驶)可推知,在目前堵车频发的交通条件下,汽车的动力、转向、加速等装置通常发挥不了作用,只有停车传感器、导航应用程序等装置在堵车时可以派上用场,C项符合此意。"},{"order":53,"question":"What does the author say about the use of navigation apps?","options":["A) It is likely to create traffic jams in other places.","B) It helps a great deal in easing traffic congestion.","C) It sharply reduces the incidence of traffic accidents.","D) It benefits those who are learning to drive."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查运用导航应用程序的影响。根据the use of navigation apps定位至第三段①句( using a navigation app)。","analysis":"【精析】第三段①句指出如果大家都用导航软件来躲避堵车会出现问题,随后②③④句展开说明:当只有少数司机用导航软件获得路况信息时,他们确实可以避开堵车;但是当所有司机都用导航软件时，软件会引导他们走辅路来躲避拥堵的主路,这就造成了辅路的拥堵。综合可知,当大家都用导航应用程序来躲避堵车时,反而可能会在其他地方造成新的拥堵,A项正确。"},{"order":54,"question":"What does the author say about technology?","options":["A) Its consequences are usually difficult to assess.","B) It seldom delivers all the benefits as promised.","C) It depends on the required knowledge for application.","D) Its benefits are guaranteed by collective wisdom."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查作者对技术的评价，可定位至第四段2句(the promises of technology will never berealised as fully as we hope)。","analysis":"【精析】该句指出,技术预期的好处永远不可能像我们所期待的那样得到充分实现,它们会受限于无法预见或预料之外的结果。可见,技术所预期的好处无法全部实现,B项正确。seldom delivers对应原文中的never be realised; all the benefits as promised具体解释the promises of technology ,as fully as。"},{"order":55,"question":"What key message does the author try to convey in the passage?","options":["A) The consequences of technological innovation need not be exaggerated.","B) There is always a price to pay to develop technology for a better world.","C) Technological innovation should be properly regulated.","D) The culture of Silicon Valley ought not to be emulated."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】由题干中的key message, in the passage 推断本题考查文章主旨,可结合篇末总结段解答。","analysis":"【精析】第六段②句指出“为了更美好的未来,周密的管控很有必要”,说明技术创新需要妥善的管控,C正确。选项中be properly regulated同义替换thoughtful regulation。"}]}]}
{"_id":"8e1706526193a305043ecc062b028e8a","id":"2021060303","type":"CET6","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are.2 passages in this section.Each passage is followed by some questions or wnfinishedstatements. For each of them there are four choices marked A),B),C) and D). You should decide on thebest choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["You can't see it, smell it,or hear it, and people disagree on how precisely to define it,or where exactly it comes from.It isn't a school subject or an academic discipline, but it can be learned.It is a quality that is required of artists,but it is also present in the lives of scientists and entrepreneurs. All of us benefit from it and we thrive mentally and spiritually when we are able to wield it. It is a delicate thing, easily stamped out; in fact, it flourishes most fully when people are playful and childlike. Meanwhile, it works best in conjunction with deep knowledge and expertise.","This mysterious——but teachable—-quality is creativity, the subiect of a recently-published report by Durham Commission on Creativity and Education. The report concludes that creativity should not inhabit the school curriculum only as it relates to drama,music, art and other obviously creative subjects， but that creative thinking ought to run through all of school life， infusing（充满）the way humanities and natural sciences are learned.","The authors, who focus on education in England, offer a nunber of sensible recommendations, some of which are an attempt to alleviate the uninspiring and fact-based approach to education that has crept into policy in recent years. When children are regarded as vessels to be filled with facts, creativity does not prosper; nor does it when teachers' sole objective is coaching children towards exams. One suggestion from the commission is a network of teacher-led“creativity collaboratives”, along the lines of existing maths hubs（中心）， with the aim of supporting teaching for creativity through the school curriculum.","Nevertheless, it is arts subjects through which creativity can most obviously be fostered. The value placed on them by the independent education sector is clear. One only has to look at the remarkable arts facilities at Britain's top private schools to comprehend this. But in the state sector the excessive focus on English, maths and science threatens to crush arts subjects; meanwhile, reduced school budgets mean diminishing extracurricular activities. There has been a 28.1 ecline in students taking creative subjects at high schools since 2014, though happily,art and design have seen a recent increase.","This discrepancy between state and private education is a matter of social justice. It is simply wrong and unfair that most children have a fraction of the access to choirs,orchestras,art studios and 6·5 drama that their more privileged peers enjoy. As lives are affected by any number of looming challenges—-climate crisis, automation in the workplace—-humans are going to need creative thinking more than ever.For all of our sakes, creativity in education, and for all, must become a priority."],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"What do we learn from the passage about creativity?","options":["A) It develops best when people are spiritually prepared.","B) It is most often wielded by scientists and entrepreneurs.","C) It is founded on scientific knowledge and analytical skills.","D) It contributes to intellectual growth but can easily be killed."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查创造力的具体特征。根据题干关键词creativity 可直接定位到第二段首句(Thismysterious- but teachable- quality is creativity),并进一步根据This的回指作用以及题文同序原则定位到首段。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案] D。首段先以it 代指,并具体描述其特征。第二段直接点明it即为“创造力(creativity)”,由此可知首段整体是对创造力的描述。其中④句指出当人们利用创造力时，智力与精神将得到极大发展(thrivementally and spiritually);⑤句 指出创造力极其娇弱,很容易被扼杀( delicate. .. easily stamped out)。可见,D项是对这些内容的概括，为正确项,其中contributes to intellectual growth和easily be killed是对原文信息的同义改写。"},{"order":47,"question":"What is the conclusion of a recently-published report?","options":["A) Natural sciences should be learned the way humanities courses are.","B) Cultivation of creativity should permeate the entire school curriculum.","C) Art courses should be made compulsory for all students.","D) Students should learn more obviously creative subjects."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查最近发表报告的结论。根据题干关键词the conclusion of... report可定位至第二段②句(The report concludes that... )。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案]B。②句指出创造力教育不应仅存在于诸如戏剧等明显的创作类科目中,创新性思维应贯穿学校生活的所有方面(run through all of school life),融入到人文科学和自然科学的学习方式中(humanitiesand natural sciences),即扩展至全部课程,B项是对原文信息的准确概括"},{"order":48,"question":"What does the report say is detrimental to the fostering of creativity?","options":["A) Alleviation of pressure.","B) Teacher-led school activities.","C) Test-oriented teaching.","D) Independent learning."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查创造力培养的阻碍因素。根据the report. is detrimental to the fostering ofcreativity及题文同序原则可定位至第三段②句(... creativity dose not prosper 、nor does it... )。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案]C。第三段具体介绍报告的内容(The authors指报告的作者),其中②句指出，当教师唯一的目标是训练孩子们的应试技巧时，创造力也不会蓬勃发展(nor does it等同于it does not prosper either),即应试教育不利于培养创造力,C项正确，Test-oriented teaching 是对文中when teachers' sole objective iscoaching children towards exams的正确概括。"},{"order":49,"question":"What do we learn about the private schools in the UK?","options":["A) They encourage extracurricular activities.","B) They attach great importance to arts education.","C) They prioritize arts subjects over maths and sciences.","D) They cater to students from different family backgrounds."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查有关英国私立学校的信息。根据private schools in the UK可定位至第四段前半部分( the independent education sector 、Britain's top private schools)以及第五段前半部分( private education)。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案] B。第四段①②③句指出,艺术类科目是最能明显培养创造力的科目，只需看看英国顶尖私立学校中令人瞩目的艺术设施,就能明白它们对艺术学科的重视。由此可知英国私立学校非常重视艺术教育,B项正确"},{"order":50,"question":"What should be done to meet the future challenges?","options":["A) Increasing government investment in school education.","B) Narrowing the existing gap between the rich and the poor.","C) Providing all children with equal access to arts education.","D) Focusing on meeting the needs of under-privileged students."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查作者的建议(如何应对未来的挑战)。根据the future challenges可定位至第五段③句(looming challenges)。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案]C。第五段③句指出人类面临诸多重大挑战,比以往任何时候都更需要创造性思维;④句则提出建议:必须把creativity in education, and for all当作首要之事;联系本段①②句论述的教育不公问题可知creativity in education, and for all强调的是“平等无差别地向所有孩子提供享受艺术教育的机会(以培养创新思维)”,C项正确。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["Emulating your conversation partner's actions is a common human behavior classified as “mirroring” and has been known and studied by psychologists for years. We all tend to subconsciously copy gestures of people we like. But why do we act like this?","As a rule, mirroring means that conversationalists enjoy their communication and that there's a certain level of agreement between them. The topic of discussion is equally interesting for both and they know their interests meet.","Repeating someone's behavior is typical of talented communicators, not always because the person is sympathetic, but because there is a goal to be achieved. This way new idols have been brought to the stage: politicians, celebrities, and other big names. Popular culture makes people want to look popular, and act and speak like popular people.","Nowadays celebrities steal lyrics from each other and struggle with copyright violation accusations or straightforwardly claim themselves to be the authors, even though all the work was done by other people.","Among celebrities, it's trendy nowadays to use their own speech writers as politicians do. The so-called“ghostwriting” can take various forms: books, articles, autobiographies, and even social media posts.","Who is a true copycat（抄袭者）and who gets copycatted?Sometimes， it is a hard nut to crack without an expert's help. But new authorship defending methods based on identifying individual writing patterns are already here. Their aim is to protect intellectual property. Using scientific methods, some of them can define authorship with 85% accuracy.","Writing is not an easy craft to master. If you want to write like a professional without plagiarism （抄袭）， there are a few lessons to learn and the first one is∶“Copy from one， it's plagiarism; copy from two, it's research.”The correct interpretation of this statement is not about copying, but rather about creating your own style. When you study an author's writing style, don't stop on a single one, but explore numerous styles instead. Examine types of sentences they use,pay attention to their metaphors， and focus on stories you feel you could write a pretty cool sequel（续篇）to.","Imitation is rather paradoxical. As an integral part of learning, it brings about positive changes, making people develop and grow. However, it may do a lot of harm. Copying someone's thoughts, ideas or inventions is completely unacceptable. It infringes on intellectual property rights of others.","Still,many things we do are about copying others one way or another. So if you want to compliment someone on the work they have done and imitate it,just make sure you do it the right way to avoid committing plagiarism."],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":"What do people tend to do while engaging in a conversation?","options":["A) Repeat what their partners say one way or another.","B) Focus as much as possible on topics of mutual interest.","C) Imitate their partners' gestures without their knowing it.","D) Observe carefully how their partners make use of gestures."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查“交谈中的行为倾向”,根据题干关键词tend to和conversation 可定位至第一段( conversation partner's... We all tend to... )。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案]C。第一段指出,模仿谈话对象的举止是一种常见的人类行为，我们往往会下意识地模仿我们喜欢的人士的举止。C项正确。"},{"order":52,"question":"When does mirroring usually take place in a conversation?","options":["A) When both sides are sympathetic with each other.","B) When both sides have a lot of things in common.","C) When both sides make interesting contributions.","D) When both sides try to seek common ground."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查“镜像模仿发生的情境”,根据题文同序原则(上题people tend to针对第一段,下题popular culture针对第三段)以及题干中mirroring usually take place可推断本题应定位至第二段(As a rule,mirroring means that... )。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案] B。第二段指出,镜像模仿意味着谈话双方在一定程度上意见一致，对谈论的话题同样感兴趣且趣味相投,B项是对这一信息的准确概括,为正确项。"},{"order":53,"question":"What do we learn about popular culture?","options":["A) It encourages people to imitate.","B) It appeals mostly to big names.","C) It acquaints young people with their idols.","D) It can change people's mode of cognition."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查关于“流行文化”的事实,根据题干关键词popular culture 可定位至第三段( Popularculture makes people... )。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案] A。第三段末句指出,流行文化让人们希望自己的外表和言行举止都像流行人物,即流行文化鼓励人们模仿流行人物,A项正确。"},{"order":54,"question":" Why is the saying“copy from two, its research”a lesson to learn?","options":["A) It facilitates the creation of one's own writing style.","B) It helps to protect one's intellectual property rights.","C) It fosters correct interpretation of professional writing.","D) It enables one to write intriguing sequels to famous stories."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查作者对“模仿两个人，则是研究”的解读。根据题干中引号内的内容直接定位至第七段。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案] A。第七段②句先引出培养专业写作技能的最重要的一条经验:模仿一人是抄袭,模仿两人是研究。随后③句对这一说法做出正确解读:模仿两人关乎创造自己的写作风格。④⑤句做出具体解释:对多位作家的写作句型、隐喻表达、故事续篇进行探索(以创造自己的写作风格)。可见，“模仿两人是研究”这种说法之所以说是一条经验,是因为它有助于个人创造自己的写作风格,A项正确。"},{"order":55,"question":"Why does the author say imitation is rather paradoxical?","options":["A) It facilitates the creation of one's own writing style.","B) It helps to protect one's intellectual property rights.","C) It fosters correct interpretation of professional writing.","D) It enables one to write intriguing sequels to famous stories."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查“模仿具有矛盾性的原因”。根据题干关键词imitation. .. paradoxical可定位至第八段。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案] D。第八段先指出“模仿是极为矛盾的(行为)”,后说明模仿会带来积极的变化,使人成长、进步,也可能造成许多危害,比如侵犯他人的知识产权。由此可见,模仿极具矛盾性指的是“模仿有益亦有害”,D项正确。"}]}]}
{"_id":"f4ef47fd61656c6a011914f8244db2d0","id":"2021060103","type":"CET4","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are.2 passages in this section.Each passage is followed by some questions or wnfinishedstatements. For each of them there are four choices marked A),B),C) and D). You should decide on thebest choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["Educators and business leaders have more in common than it may seem. Teachers want to preparestudents for a successful future. Technology companies have an interest in developing a workforce with theSTEM(science, technology, engineering and math) skills needed to grow the company and advance theindustry. How can they work together to achieve these goals? Play may be the answer.","Focusing on STEM skills is important, but the reality is that STEM skills are enhanced and morerelevant when combined with traditional, hands-on creative activities. This combination is proving to bethe best way to prepare today's children to be the makers and builders of tomorrow. That is whytechnology companies are partnering with educators to bring back good, old-fashioned play.","In fact many experts argue that the most important 2lst-century skills aren't related to specifictechnologies or subject matter,but to creativity; skills like imagination,problem-finding and problem-solving, teamwork, optimism, patience and the ability to experiment and take risks. These are skillsacquired when kids tinker（鼓捣小玩意）.High-tech industries such as NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratoryhave found that their best overall problem solvers were master tinkerers in their youth.","There are cognitive（认 知的）benefits of doing things the way we did as children—buildingsomething, tearing it down, then building it up again. Research shows that given 15 minutes of fre play,four- and five-vear-olds will spend a third of this time engaged in spatial,mathematical, and architecturalactivities. This type of play—especially with building blocks—helps children discover and develop keyprinciples in math and geometry","If play and building are critical to 21st-century skill development, that's really good news for tworeasons∶Children are born builders， makers，and creators， so fostering（培养）2lst-century skills may beas simple as giving kids room to play, tinker and try things out,even as they grow older. Secondly, itdoesn't take 21st-century technology to foster 21st-century skills. This is especially important for under-resourced schools and communities. Taking whatever materials are handy and tinkering with them is asimple way to engage those important “maker” skills. And anyone, anywhere,can do it.46. What does the author say about educators?"],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"What does the author say about educators?","options":["A) They seek advice from technology companies to achieve teaching goals.","B) They have been successful in preparing the workforce for companies.","C) They help students acquire the skills needed for their future success.","D) They partner with technology companies to enhance teaching efficiency."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】由题干中的 educators 定位到首段前两句","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题定位句指出教育工作者和商界领袖的共同点比看起来要多。教师希望为学生成功的未来做好准备。Teachers “教师” 指的是 educators “教育工作者”,由此可见,教育工作者帮助学生为成功的未来做好准备,即帮助学生获得未来成功所需的技能,故答案为 C)。"},{"order":47,"question":"How can educators better develop students'STEM skills,according to the author?","options":["A) By blending them with traditional, stimulating activities.","B) By inviting business leaders to help design curriculums.","C) By enhancing students'ability to think in a critical way.","D) By showing students the best way to learn is through play."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】由题干中的 better develop students` STEM skills 定位到第二段第一、二句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句提到,专注于 STEM 技能很重要,但当 STEM 技能与传统的动手创造性活动相结合时,这些技能会增强。事实证明,这种结合是让今天的孩子成为明天的创造者和建设者的最佳方式。换言之,通过将培养 STEM 技能与传统的、趣味盎然的活动相结合,能够更好地培养学生的STEM 技能,故答案为 A)。"},{"order":48,"question":"How do children acquire the skills needed for the 2lst century?","options":["A) By engaging in activities involving specific technologies.","B) By playing with things to solve problems on their own.","C) By familiarizing themselves with high-tech gadgets.","D) By mastering basic principles through teamwork."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】由题干中的 children acquire the skills needed for the 21st century 定位到第三段第一、二句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句指出,许多专家认为21世纪最重要的技能与特定的技术或主题无关,而是与创造力有关;如想象力、发现问题和解决问题的能力、团队合作、乐观、耐心以及做实验和冒险的能力。这些都是孩子们鼓捣小玩意时获得的技能。由此可见,孩子们可以通过摆弄东西来自己解决问题,从而获得21世纪所需的技能,故答案为 B)。"},{"order":49,"question":"What can we do to help children learn the basics of math and geometry?","options":["A) Stimulate their interest as early as possible.","B) Spend more time playing games with them.","C) Encourage them to make things with hands.","D) Allow them to tinker freely with calculators."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】由题干中的 basics of math and geometry 定位到第四段最后一句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句提到,这种类型的游戏特别是搭积木帮助孩子们发现和掌握数学和几何学的关键原理。由此可见,鼓励孩子们动手做东西可以帮助孩子们学习数学和几何的基础知识,故答案为 C)。"},{"order":50,"question":"What does the author advise disadvantaged schools and communities to do?","options":["A) Train students to be makers to meet future market demands.","B) Develop students'creative skills with the resources available.","C) Engage students with challenging tasks to foster their creativity.","D) Work together with companies to improve their teaching facilities."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】由题干中的 disadvantaged schools and communities 定位到文章最后一段最后三句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句指出,这一点对于资源不足的学校和社区尤其重要。利用手边的任何材料,让孩子们去鼓捣小玩意,这是运用那些重要的“制造者”技能的一个简单方法。任何人在任何地方都能做到。换言之，资源不足的学校和社区应尽可能地利用现有资源，故答案为 B)。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["Being an information technology, or IT, worker is not a jobI envy.They are the ones who,right inthe middle of a criticalmeeting, are expected to instantly fix the projector that's no longer working. Theyhave to tolerate the bad tempers of colleagues frustrated at the number of times they've had to call the helpdesk for the same issue. They are also the ones who know there are systems that are more powerful,reliable and faster, but their employer simply will not put up the funds to buy them.","According to a recent survey, employees who have a job reliant on IT support consider IT a majorsource of job dissatisfaction. Through no fault of their own, they can suddenly find their productivitydeteriorating or quality control non-existent. And there's little they can do about it.","The experience of using IT penetrates almost the entire work field. It has become a crucial part ofemployees'overall work experience. When IT is operating as it should, employee self-confidence swells.Their job satisfaction,too,can surge when well-functioning machines relieve them of dull tasks orrepetitive processes. But if there's one thing that triggers widespread employee frustration, it's an ITtransformation project gone wrong, where swollen expectations have been popped and a long list ofpromised efficiencies have been reversed. This occurs when business leaders implement IT initiatives withlittle consideration of how those changes will impact the end user.","Which is why managers should appreciate just how influential the IT user experience is to theiremployees,and exert substantial effort in ensuring their IT team eliminates programming errors andapplication crashes. Adequate and timely IT support should also be available to enable users to cope with technological issues at work. More importantly,IT practitioners need to understand what employeesexperience mentally when they use IT.","Therefore,businesses need to set up their IT infrastructure so that it is designed to fit in with theiremployees'work, rather than adjust their work to fit in with the company's IT limitations."],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":"What does the author say about working in IT?","options":["A) It is envied by many.","B) It does not appeal to him.","C) It is financially rewarding.","D) It does not match his abilities"],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】由题干中的 working in IT 定位到首段第一句","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句提到，“我”并不羡慕信息技术工作者，或者说 IT工作者的工作。由此可知，作者对这样的工作不感兴趣，故答案为 B)。"},{"order":52,"question":"What is the finding of a recent survey on employees who have a job reliant on IT support?","options":["A) IT helps boost productivity.","B) IT helps improve quality control.","C) Many employees are deeply frustrated by IT.","D) Most employees rely heavily on IT in their work."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】由题干中的 a job reliant on IT support 定位到第二段。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位段提到，根据最近的一项调查，那些自身工作依赖信息技术支持的员工认为，信息技术是他们工作不满意的主要原因。他们自己毫无过错，却突然发现生产效率在下降，或质量控制不起作用。他们对此几乎无能为力。由此可知，答案为 C)。"},{"order":53,"question":"What is said to happen when IT is functioning properly?","options":["A) There is a big boost in employees'work efficiency.","B) Employees become more dependent on machines.","C) There are no longer any boring or repetitive tasks.","D) Employees become more confident in their work."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】由题干中的 IT is functioning properly 定位到第三段第三、四句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句指出,当信息技术正常运作时,员工的自信心就会增加。当运转良好的机器将他们从枯燥的任务或重复性的流程中解放出来时,他们的工作满意度也会激增。换言之,当信息技术正常运行时,员工对自己的工作更有信心,故答案为 D)。"},{"order":54,"question":"What should business leaders do before implementing new IT initiatives?","options":["A) Consider the various expectations of their customers.","B) Draw up a list of the efficiencies to be promised.","C) Assess the swollen cost of training the employees.","D) Think about the possible effects on their employees."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】由题干中的 implementing new IT initiactives 定位到第三段最后一句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句指出,当业务领导在实施信息技术计划时很少考虑这些更改将如何影响终端用户时,就会发生这种情况。结合本段倒数第二句可知,这种情况指的是一旦信息技术改造项目出问题,会导致满满的期望破灭,一长串承诺提高效率的方法被推翻。因此,业务领导在实施信息技术计划时,应考虑对员工可能产生的影响故答案为 D)。"},{"order":55,"question":"How can a business help improve its employees'experience in using IT?","options":["A) By designing systems that suit their needs.","B) By ensuring that their mental health is sound.","C) By adjusting their work to suit the IT system.","D) By offering them regular in-service training."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】由题干中的 business、improve is employees` experience in using IT 定位到文章最后一段。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。文章最后一段指出,企业需要建立自己的信息技术基础设施,使其设计能够适应员工的工作,而不是让员工调整自己的工作以适应公司的信息技术系统。即企业应设计适合员工工作需求的系统,故答案为 A)。"}]}]}
{"_id":"8e1706526193a305043ecc071e676db4","id":"2021060203","type":"CET4","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are.2 passages in this section.Each passage is followed by some questions or wnfinishedstatements. For each of them there are four choices marked A),B),C) and D). You should decide on thebest choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["Sugar shocked. That describes the reaction of many Americans this week following revelations that, 50 years ago, the sugar industry paid Harvard scientists for research that shifted the focus away from sugar's role in heart disease-and put the spotlight (注意的中心） squarely on dietary fat.","What might surprise consumers is just how many present-day nutrition studies are still funded by the food industry. Nutrition scholar Marion Nestle of New York University spent a year informally tracking industry-funded studies on food. “Roughly 90% of nearly 170 studies favored the sponsor's interest,”Nestle tells us. Other systematic reviews support her conclusions.","For instance, studies funded by Welch Foods--the brand behind Welch's 100% Grape Juice-found that drinking Concord grape juice daily may boost brain function. Another, funded by Qualcer Oats, concluded, as a Daily Mail story put it, that “hot oatmeal (燕麦粥） brealdast keeps you full for longer. ”","Last year, The New York Times revealed how Cocaola was funding well-known scientists and organizations promoting a message that, in the battle against weight gain, people should pay more  attention to exercise and less to what they eat and drink. Coca七ola also released data detailing its funding  of several medical institutions and associations between 2010 and 2015.","It's certainly problem that so much research in nutrition and health is founded by industry says Bonnie Liebman,  director of nutrition and Center for Science and Public Interest. When the food industry pays for research, it often gets what it pay for. And what it pays for is often a pro- industry finding"],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"What did Harvard scientists do 50 years ago?","options":["A) They raised public awareness of the possible causes of heart disease.","B) They turned public attention away from the health risks of sugar to fat.","C) They placed the sugar industry in the spotlight with their new findings.","D) hey conducted large-scale research on the role of sugar in people's health"],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】由题干中的Harvard scientists和50years ago定位到首段第二句。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位句指出，50年前，制糖业资助哈佛大学科学家将研究重心从糖在心脏病中的影响，转移到了膳食脂肪。由此可见，他们把公众的注意力从糖的健康风险转移到脂肪上，故答案为B)。"},{"order":47,"question":"What does Marion Nestle say about present-day nutrition studies?","options":["A) They took her a full year to track and analyze.","B) Most of them are based on systematic reviews","C) They depend on funding from the food industries","D) Nearly all of them serve the purpose of the funders."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】由题干中的Marion Nestle和present-day nutrition studies定位到第二段","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位段第二、三句提到，纽约大学的营养学家玛丽恩·内斯特尔花了一年的时间非正式地跟踪了各种工业资助的食品研究。她指出，在将近170项研究中，大约有90％的研究都会偏袒赞助商的利益。其他系统的研究综述也支持她的结论。由此可知，几乎所有的营养研究都是为资助者服务的，D)中的Nearly all of them对应原文中的Roughly 90％of nearly 170 studies，故答案为D)。"},{"order":48,"question":"What did Coca-Cola-funded studies claim?","options":["A) xercise is more important to good health than diet.","B) Choosing what to eat and drink is key to weight control.","C) Drinking Coca-Cola does not contribute to weight gain.","D) he food industry plays a major role in fighting obesity"],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】由题干中的Coca-Cola-funded studies定位到第四段第一句。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位句指出，去年，《纽约时报》披露了可口可乐公司资助知名科学家以及组织来宣传一个信息，在对抗增重的斗争中，人们应该更加注意锻炼，少关注饮食。由此可见，由可口可乐公司资助的研究声称锻炼对于身体健康比饮食更重要，故答案为A"},{"order":49,"question":"What does Liebman say about industry-funded research?","options":["A) It simply focuses on nutrition and health.","B) Spend more time playing games with them.","C) It rarely results in objective findings","D) runs counter to the public interest."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】由题干中的Liebman和industry-funded research定位到第五段。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。第五段第二、三句提到，利伯曼认为“食品工业为研究提供资金时，通常会得到相应的回报。”他们所支付的往往是一个利于推动该行业的发展的发现。由此可见，由食品工业资助的研究，其结果并不客观，故答案为C)。"},{"order":50,"question":"What is the author's advice to consumers?","options":["A) Follow their intuition in deciding what to eat.","B) Be doubtful of diet experts'recommendations.","C) Ignore irrelevant information on their news feed.","D) Think twice about new nutrition research findings."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】由题干中的author's advice to consumers 定位到第六段第一句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句指出，鉴于这种环境，消费者在阅读营养科学的最新发现时应持怀疑态度，并且忽略新闻推送上弹出的最新研究。由此可见，作者的建议是对新的营养研究成果三思而后行，D）中的Think twice对应原文中的 skeptical，故答案为D)。  "}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["Success was once defined as being able to stay at a company for a long time and move up the corporate ladder. The goal was to reach the top, accumulate wealth and retire to a life of ease. My father is a successful senior executive. In 35 years,he worked for only three companies","When I started my career, things were already different. If you weren't changing companies every three or four years, you simply weren't getting ahead in your career. But back then, if you were a consultant or freela砒er (自由职业者），people would wonder what was wrong with you. They would assume you had problems getting a job.","Today,consulting or freelancing for five businesses at the same time is a badge of honor. It shows  how valuable an individual is. Many companies now look to these“ultimate professionals” to solve problems their full-time teams can't. Or they save money by hiring“top-tier（顶尖的）experts” only for particular projects","Working at home or in cafes, starting businesses of their own, and even launching business ventures that eventually may fail, all indicate “initiative,” “creativity,” and “adaptability,” which are desirable qualities in today's workplace. Most important, there is a growing recognition that people who balance work and play, and who work at what they are passionate about, are more focused and productive,delivering greater value to their clients","Who are these people? They are artists, writers,programmers,providers of office services and career advice.What's needed now is a marketplace platfomm specifically designed to bring freelancers and clients together. Such platforms then become a place to feature the most experienced, professional, and creative talent. This is where they conduct business, where a sense of community reinforces the culture and values of the gig economy（零工经济），and where success is rewarded with good reviews that encourage more business","Slowly but surely, these platforms create a bridge between traditional enterprises and this emerging economy. Perhaps more important, as the global economy continues to be disrupted by technology and other massive change, the gig economy will itself become an engine of economic and social transformation"],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":"What does the author use the example of his father to illustrate?","options":["A) How long people took to reach the top of their career.","B) How people accumulated wealth in his father's time","C) How people viewed success in his father's time.","D) How long people usually stayed in a company."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】由题干中的the example of father定位到第一段。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位段指出，成功曾经被定义为能在一家公司任职很长时间并获得晋升。目的是到达高位，积累财富，退休后安度晚年。第三、四句提到了作者父亲的亲身经历，用以说明该段前两句的内容，即在其父辈的年代，人们对于成功的定义是怎样的，故答案为C"},{"order":52,"question":"Why did people often change jobs when the author started his career?","options":["A) It was considered a fashion at that time","B) It was a way to advance in their career","C) It was a response to the changing job market","D) It was difficult to keep a job for long"],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】[定位]由题干中的often change jobs和the author started his career定位到第二段第一、二句。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位句提到，当作者开始他的职业生涯时，事情已经不同了。如果你不是每三四年就换一家公司，那么就说明你并未在职业生涯中前进。由此可知，人们频繁换工作是为了 促进职业发展，故答案为B)。"},{"order":53,"question":"hat does the author say about people now working for several businesses at the same time?","options":["A) They are often regarded as most treasured talents","B) ey are.able to bring their potential into fuller play.","C) They have control over their life and work schedules.","D) They feel proud of being outstanding problem solver."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】由题干中的working for several businesses at the same time定位到第三段第一句。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位句指出，现如今，能够同时为五家企业工作是荣耀的象征。接下来的一句指出这能说明一个人的价值所在。也就是说，能同时为多家企业工作的人通常是有价值的人才，故答案为。"},{"order":54,"question":" What have businesses come to recognize now?","options":["A) Who is capable of solving problems with ease","B) How people can be more focused and productive","C) What kind of people can contribute tnore to them.","D) Why some people are more passionate about work."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】由题干中的businesses和recognize而定位到第四段第二句。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位句提到，越来越多的人意识到那些能够平衡工作和娱乐的人，以及做自己喜爱的工作的人，会更加专注和高效，从而为他们的客户提供更大的价值，故答案为C"},{"order":55,"question":"What does the author say about the 'gig economy?","options":["A) It may force companies to reform their business practice.","B) It may soon replace the traditional economic model.","C) It will drive technological progress on a global scale","D) It will bring about radical economic and social changes."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】根据选项内容和题文同序原则定位到最后一段末句。","analysis":"【精析】〖精析〗细节辨认题。定位句指出，或许更重要的是，随着全球经济持续受到科技和其他重大改变的干扰，零工经济本身将会成为经济和社会转型的引擎，故答案为D）。"}]}]}
{"_id":"8e1706526193a305043ecc083ed1f307","id":"2021060303","type":"CET4","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are.2 passages in this section.Each passage is followed by some questions or wnfinishedstatements. For each of them there are four choices marked A),B),C) and D). You should decide on thebest choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["Boredom has become trendy. Studies point to how boredom is good for creativity and innovation, as well as mental health. It is found that people are more creative following the completion of a tedious task. When people are bored, they have an increase in“associative thought”——the process of making new connections between ideas, which is linked to innovative thinking. These studies are impressive, but in reality, the benefits of boredom may be related to having time to clear your mind, be quiet, or daydream.","In our stimulation- rich world, it seems unrealistic that boredom could occur at all. Yet, there are valid reasons boredom may feel so painful. As it turns out, boredom might signal the fact that you have a need that isn't being met.","Our always-on world of social media may result in more connections, but they are superficial and canget in the way of building a real sense of belonging. Feeling bored may signal the desire for a greater sense of community and the feeling that you fit in with others around you. So take the step of joining an organization to build face-to-face relationships.' You'll find depth that you won't get from your screen no matter how many likes you get on your post.","Similar to the need for belonging， bored people often report that they feel a limited sense of meaning. It's a fundamental human need to have a larger purpose and to feel like we re part of something bigger than ourselves. When people are bored, they're more likely to feel less meaning in their lives. If you want to reduce boredom and increase your sense of meaning, seek work where you can make a unique contribution, or find a cause you can support with your time and talent.","If your definition of boredom is being quiet, mindful, and reflective, keep it up. But if you'restruggling with real boredom and the emptiness it provokes, consider whether you might seek new connections and more significant challenges. These are the things that will genuinely relieve boredom and make you more effective in the process."],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"What have studies found about boredom?","options":["A) It facilitates innovative thinking.","B) It is a result of doing boring tasks.","C) It helps people connect with others.","D) It does harm to one's mental health."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】由题干中的studies和boredom定位到第一.段第二、三句。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。文章第一段第二句提到，研究指出,无聊是如何有利于创造力的。第三句提到,研究发现,人们在完成一项枯燥乏昧的任务后更有创造力。第四句进一步指出,当人们感到无聊时,他们会增加“联想思维”,这与创新思维有关。由此可见,科学家对无聊所做的研究表明,无聊可以激发人们的创造性思维,故答案为A)。"},{"order":47,"question":"What does the author say boredom might indicate?","options":["A) A need to be left alone.","B) A desire to be fulfilled.","C) A conflict to be resolved.","D) A feeling to be validated."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】由题干中的boredom might indicate定位到第二段最后一句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句提到,事实证明,无聊可能表明你的需求没有得到满足。由此可知,当人们感到无聊时,这表明人们的某种需求未得到满足,故答案为B)。"},{"order":48,"question":"What do we learn about social media from the passage?","options":["A) It may be an obstacle to expanding one's connections.","B) It may get in the way of enhancing one's social status.","C) It may prevent people from developing a genuine sense of community.","D) It may make people feel that they ought to fit in with the outside world."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】由题千中的social media定位到第三段第一、二句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句指出,推理判断题。定位句指出,我们一直在线的社交媒体世界可能会产生更多的联系,但这些联系是肤浅的，可能会妨碍建立真正的归属感。感到无聊可能表明更强烈的群体意识的欲望,并且想要融人你周围的人之中。由此可见,过多的社交媒体会妨碍我们建立真正的归属感,造成群体意识的缺失,故答案为C)。"},{"order":49,"question":"What does the author suggest people do to get rid of boredom?","options":["A) Count the likes they get on their posts.","B) Reflect on how they relate to others.","C) Engage in real-life interactions.","D) Participate in online discussions."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】由题干中的get rid of boredom定位到第三段第三句和最后一段第二、三句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。第三段第三句提到采取措施加入一一个组织，建立面对面的关系。最后一段第二句提到，如果你正与真正的无聊和它所引发的空虚作斗争,考虑- - 下你是否可能寻求新的联系和更重大的挑战。这些事情将真正缓解无聊，让你在这个过程中更有效率。综合两部分内容可知,答案为C)。"},{"order":50,"question":"What should people do to enhance their sense of meaning?","options":["A) Try to do something original.","B) Confront significant challenges.","C) Define boredom in their unique way.","D) Devote themselves to a worthy cause."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】由题干中的enhance their sense of meaning定位到第四段最后一句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句指出,如果你想减少无聊感,增加你的意义感,找一份你能做出独特贡献的工作,或者找一个你能用时间和才能支持的事业。由此可见,作者认为,人们想要增加意义感的两种方法为:一.找一份可以做出独特贡献的工作;二、找一份能有时间和才能支持的事业。故答案为D)。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["Can you remember what you ate yesterday? If asked, most people will be able to give a vague description of their main meals: breakfast, lunch, dinner. But can you be sure you' ve noted every snack bar in your car, or every handful of nuts at your desk? Most people will have a feeling that they ve missed something out.","We originally had this suspicion back in 2016，puzzled by the fact that national statistics showed calorie consumption falling dramatically over past decades. We found reliable evidence that people were drastically under reporting what they ate.","Now the Office for National Statistics has confirmed that we are consuming 50% more calories thanour national statistics claim.","Why is this happening? We can point to at least three potential causes. One is the rise in obesity levels itself. Under-reporting rates are much higher for obese people, because they simply consume more food, and thus have more to remember.","Another cause is that the proportion of people who are trying to lose weight has been increasing over time. People who want to lose weight are more likely to under-report their eating- regardless of whether they are overweight or not. This may be driven partly by self-deception or“wishful thinking”.","The final potential cause is an increase in snacking and eating out over recent decades- -both in terms of how often they happen and how much they contribute to our overall energy intake. Again, there is evidence that food consumed out of the home is one of the most poorly recorded categories in surveys.","So, what's the message conveyed? For statistics, we should invest in more accurate measurement options. For policy, we need to focus on options that make it easy for people to eat fewer calories. If people do not know how much they are eating, it can be really hard for them to stick to a diet. Also, we should be looking for new ways to ensure what people eat wouldn't have much impact on their waistlines. If this works, it won't matter if they can't remember what they ate yesterday."],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":" What did the author suspect back in 2016?","options":["A) Calorie consumption had fallen drastically over the decades.","B) Most people surveyed were reluctant to reveal what they ate.","C) The national statistics did not reflect the actual calorie consumption.","D) Most people did not include snacks when reporting their calorie intake."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】由题干中的suspect和back in定位到第一段","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位段指出，早在2016年他们就有了这种怀疑，因为国家统计数据显示，在过去几十年，卡路里消耗量大幅下降，这让他们感到困惑。有可靠的证据证明人们严重地漏报了他们吃的东西。由此可见，有证据显示人们漏报了自己摄入的食物，因此作者怀疑国家统计局数据的真实性，故答案为C）。"},{"order":52,"question":" What has the Office for National Statistics verified?","options":["A) People's calorie intake was far from accurately reported.","B) The missing out of main meals leads to the habit of snacking.","C) The nation's obesity level has much to do with calorie intake.","D) Calorie consumption is linked to the amount of snacks one eats."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】由题干中的 the Office for National Statistics和verified定位到第三段。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位段提到，现在国家统计局已经证实,我们消耗的卡路里比国家统计数据声称的多50%。由此可知,国家统计局所报道的数据,与人们消耗卡路里的真实数据有很大的出人,故答案为A)。"},{"order":53,"question":" What do we learn about obese people from the passage?","options":["A) They usually keep their eating habits a secret.","B) They overlook the potential causes of obesity.","C) They cannot help eating more than they should.","D) They have difficulty recalling what they have eaten."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】由题干中的由题干中的obese people定位到第四段最后一句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句指出,肥胖者的漏报率要高得多,因为他们的确吃了更多的食物，因此需要记住更多的信息。由此可见，肥胖者因为自己摄入的食物过多,因此无法事无巨细地将自己所吃的食物完全记住,故答案为D)。"},{"order":54,"question":" What often goes unnoticed in surveys on food consumption?","options":["A) The growing trend of eating out.","B) The potential causes of snacking.","C) People's home energy consumption.","D) People's changing diet over the years."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】由题干中的unnoticed in surveys on food consumption和题文同序原则定位到第六段。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。第六段提到,最后-个潜在的原因是,近几十年来,吃零食和外出吃饭的人越来越多,有证据表明,在调查中,外出吃掉的食物是记录最少的类别之一。 由此可见,外出就餐通常被人们忽略，故答案为A)。"},{"order":55,"question":" What does the author suggest policymakers do about obesity?","options":["A) Remind people to cut down on snacking.","B) Make sure people eat non-fattening food.","C) Ensure people don't miss their main meals.","D) See that people don't stick to the same diet."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】由题干中的 policymakers do about obesity定位到最后一段第三至五句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句指出,在政策方面,我们需要关注那些让人们容易摄人更少卡路里的选择。如果人们不知道自己吃了多少,那他们就真的很难坚持节食了。此外,我们应该寻找新的方法来确保人们的饮食不会对他们的腰围产生太大影响。由此可见,作者认为,政策制定者应该引导人们多吃一些卡路里较少的食物，使之尽量减少对体重的影响,故答案为B)。"}]}]}
{"_id":"8e1706526193a305043ecc097f36af18","id":"2020120303","type":"CET4","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are.2 passages in this section.Each passage is followed by some questions or wnfinishedstatements. For each of them there are four choices marked A),B),C) and D). You should decide on thebest choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["A growing number of U.S. bike riders are attracted to electric bikes for convenience, health benefits and their fun factor. Although ebikes first appeared in the 90s, cheaper options and longer-lasting batteries are breathing new life into the concept.","Established bike companies and startups are embracing ebikes to meet demand. About 34 million ebikes were sold worldwide last year, according to data from eCycleElectric Consultants. Most were sold in Europe and China,where the bikes already have exploded in popularity.Recently, the U.s. market has grown to 263,000 bikes, a 25% gain from the prior year.","The industry is benefiting from improved batteries as suppliers over the years developed technology for laptops, smartphones and electric cars. In 2004, the price of batteries used on ebikes fell, spurring European sales.","But lower cost options are emerging, too. This month, three U.S. bikeshare companies, Motivate, LimeBike and Spin, announced electric bicycles will be added to their fleets. New York-based Jump Bikes is already operating an electric bikeshare in Washington，D.C.， and is launching in San Francisco Thursday. Rides cost $ 2 for 30 minutes.","The system works like existing dockless bikeshare systems,where riders unlock bikes through a smartphone app.“This is the beginning of a long-term shift away from regular pedal(踏板) to electric bikes,”said Jump Bikes CEO Ryan Rzepecki. “When people first jump on an ebike, their face lights up. It’s exciting and joyful in a way that you don’t get from a regular bike.”","Two years ago, CEO Chris Cocalis of Pivot Cycles,which sells high-end mountain bikes,found that U.S. bike shops weren’t interested in stocking ebikes. Some retailers warned Cocalis that they’d drop the brand if it came out with an electric bike.","Now that sales are taking off,the vast majority of bike dealers are asking Cocalis when he’ll make an ebike available. “There’s tremendous opportunity to get a generation of people for whom suffering isn’t their thing,” Cocalis said. “Ebike riders get the enjoyable part of cycling without themassive suffering of climbing huge hills.”"],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"What do we learn from the passage about ebikes?","options":["A) Their health benefits and fun values outweigh their cost.","B) They did not catch public attention in the United States until the 1990s.","C) They did not become popular until the emergence of improved batteries.","D) Their widespread use is attributable to people’s environmental awareness."],"answer":"C","location":" ","analysis":":根据根据题干关键词ebikes定位至首段第二句。该句提到,尽管电动自行车早在90年代就出现了,但更便宜的价格和更耐用的电池给这一概念注入了新的活力。可知,“直到改进电池的出现,它们才开始流行”,故答案选C)项。同时排除D)项;文章首句提到,越来越多的美国自行车骑手都被电动自行车所吸引,因为电动自行车方便、有益健康,而且有趣。但文中并未提到“它们的健康益处和娱乐价值超过了它们的成本”,故排除A)项;电动自行车早在90年代就出现了,但流行起来却是现在,故排除B)项。"},{"order":47,"question":" What brought about the boost in ebike sales in Europe at the beginning of the century?","options":["A) Updated technology of bike manufacture.","B) The falling prices of ebike batteries.","C) Changed fashion in short-distance travel.","D) The rising costs for making electric cars."],"answer":"B","location":"","analysis":"根据题干关键词Europe和 the beginning of the century定位至第三段。该段中提到，由于供应商多年来开发了用于笔记本电脑、智能手机和电动汽车的技术,电动自行车行业正受益于电池的改进。2004年,电动自行车上使用的电池价格下跌﹐刺激了它在欧洲的销量。可知,“电池价格的下跌”使电动自行车在欧洲的销量增加,故答案选B)项。"},{"order":48,"question":" What is the prospect of the bike industry according to Ryan Rzepecki?","options":["A) More will be invested in bike battery research.","B) The sales of ebikes will increase.","C) It will profit from ebike sharing.","D) It will make a difference in people’s daily lives."],"answer":"D","location":"","analysis":"根据题干定位至第五段。该段中提到,Jump Bikes首席执行官莱恩·雷兹皮茨基说:“这是从普通踏板向电动自行车的长期转变的开始。当人们第一次骑电动自行车时,他们的脸上神采飞扬。这种兴奋和快乐是骑普通自行车体会不到的”。可知,莱恩·雷兹皮茨基认为电动自行车会“改变人们的日常生活”,故答案选D)项。A)项和C)项在文中均未提及,故排除;B)项属过度推断,故排除。"},{"order":49,"question":"What prevented Chris Cocalis from developing ebikes sooner?","options":["A) Retailers’ refusal to deal in ebikes.","B) High profits from conventional bikes.","C) Users’concern about risks of ebike riding.","D) His focus on selling costly mountain bikes."],"answer":"A","location":"","analysis":"根据题干定位至第六段。该段提到,两年前﹐销售高端山地车的 Pivot Cycles公司的首席执行官克里斯·科卡利斯发现,美国的自行车商店对储备电动自行车不感兴趣。一些零售商警告科卡利斯,如果他们品牌推出电动自行车,他们就放弃该品牌。可知,“零售商拒绝经销电动自行车”阻止了克里斯·科卡利斯更早地开发电动自行车,故答案选A)项。其他三项在文中均未提及﹐故排除。根据题干关键词boredomisn􀆳tallbad定位至第四段首句。该句提到,但无聊并不都是坏事。通过鼓励自我反省和幻想,它可以激发创造力。故答案选 C)项。其他三项在文中均未提及,故排除。"},{"order":50,"question":"What makes Chris Cocalis believe there is a greater opportunity for ebike sales? ","options":["A) The further lowering of ebike prices.","B) The public’s concern for their health.","C) The increasing interest in mountain climbing.","D) The younger generation’s pursuit of comfortable riding."],"answer":"D","location":"","analysis":"题目就提问。根据题干关键词Chris Cocalis和 a greater opportunity定位到末段。该段中提到,现在有绝佳的机会可以赢得这一代不喜欢吃苦的人,骑电动自行车的人可以享受骑自行车的乐趣,而不必忍受爬坡的巨大痛苦。可知,克里斯·科卡利斯认为电动自行车具有巨大前景是因为“年轻一代对舒适骑行的追求”,故答案选D)项。其他三项在文中均未提及﹐故排除。根据题干关键词authorsuggest定位至末段。该段第二句提到,看着油漆变干或者水沸腾,或者至少把你的智能手机暂时收起来一会儿,你可能会解锁你的又一个了不起的创意。说明,当你做一些无聊的事情时,让头脑放松,可能会想出了不起的创意;那么在面对具有挑战性的问题时,也可以这么做。故答案选 D)项。A)项和 C)项在文中均未提及,故排除;B)项与作者所提的建议相悖,故排除。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["The terms “global warming” and “climate change” are used by many, seemingly interchangeably. But do they really mean the same thing?","Scientists shaped the history of the terms while attempting to accurately describe how humans continue to alter the planet. Later, political strategists adopted the terms to influence public opinion.","In 1975，geochemist Wallace Broecker introduced the term “climate change” in an article published by Science. In 1979, a National Academy of Sciences report used the term “global warming” to define increases in the Earth’s average surface temperature, while “climate change” more broadly referred to the numerous effects of this increase，such as sea-level rise and ocean acidification(酸化).","During the following decades,some industrialists and politicians launched a campaign to sow doubt in the minds of the American public about the ability of fossil-fuel use, deforestation and other human activities to influence the planet’s climate.","Word use played a critical role in developing that doubt. For example,the language and polls expert Frank Luntz wrote a memo encouraging the use of “climate change” because the phrase sounded less scary than “global warming,” reported the Guardian.","However, Luntz’s recommendation wasn’t necessary.A Google Ngram Viewer chart shows that by 1993 climate change was already more commonly used in books than global warming. By the end of the next decade both words were used more frequently, and climate change was used nearly twice as often as global warming.","NASA used the term “climate change” because it more accurately reflects the wide range of changes to the planet caused by increasing amounts of greenhouse gases in the atmosphere.","The debate isn’t new. A century ago, chemist Svante Arrhenius started one of the first debates over the potential for humans to influence the planet’s climate. Arrhenius calculated the capability of carbon dioxide to trap heat in the Earth’s atmosphere, but other chemists disagreed. Some argued that humans werent producing enough greenhouse gases,while others claimed the effects would be tiny. Now, of course, we know that whatever you call it, human behavior is warming the planet, with grave consequences ahead."],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":" Why did politicians use the two terms “global warming” and “climate change”?","options":["A) To sway public opinion of the impact of human activities on Earth.","B) To more accurately describe the consequences of human activities. ","C) To win more popular votes in their campaign activities. ","D) To assure the public of the safety of existing industries."],"answer":"A","location":"","analysis":"根据题干关键词politicians，two terms和global warming and “climate change”定位至文章的第一、二和四段。首段中引入这两个术语;第二段末句提到,政治策略家们采用这些术语来影响公众舆论;第四段中进一步提到,一些工业家和政治家发起了一场运动,使美国公众的心里对化石燃料的使用、滥伐森林以及其他人类活动影响地球气候的能力产生怀疑。可知,政治家们使用全球变暖和气候变化这两个术语是“为了动摇公众对于人类活动影响地球的看法”故答案选A)项。B)项是第七段中的 accurately与末段中的 consequences相杂糅,故排除;C)项和D)项在文中均未提及﹐故排除;"},{"order":52,"question":" As used in a National Academy of Sciences report, the term “climate change” differs from “global warming” in that____.","options":["A)  it sounds less vague","B)  it looks more scientific","C) it covers more phenomena ","D) it is much closer to reality "],"answer":"C","location":"","analysis":"题目就提问。根据题干关键词National Academy of Sciences定位至第三段第二句。该句提到,一份美国国家科学院的报告使用了“全球变暖”这一术语来定义地球表面平均温度的升高,而“气候变化”更广泛地指代这种升高所导致的众多影响,比如海平面上升和海洋酸化。可知,这两个术语的区别在于“全球变暖”表述了现象,而“气候变化”则表述了该现象所带来的后果,因此“气候变化”涵盖了更多的现象,故答案选C)项。其他三项在文中均未提及,故排除。"},{"order":53,"question":" What did industrialists of the late 20th century resort to in order to mislead Americans?","options":["A) Made-up survey results.","B) False research findings.","C)  Hired climate experts. ","D) Deliberate choice of words."],"answer":"D","location":"","analysis":"根据题干关键词industrialists of the late 20th century 和 mislead Americans定位至策四五段。第四段中指出,一些工业家和政治家发起了一场运动,使美国公众的心里对化石燃料的使用,滥伐森林以及其他人类活动影响地球气候的能力产生怀疑。第五段首句又提到,措辞的使用在推动这种质疑的过程中起到了关键的作用;随后举例说明，“气候变化”这一说法听起来没有“全球变暖”那么可怕。可知,工业家们在遣词上作文章从而误导民众的判断,故答案选D)项。其他三项在文中均未提及﹐故排除。"},{"order":54,"question":"Why did NASA choose the term “climate change”?","options":["A) To obtain more funds.","B) For greater precision.","C) For political needs.","D) To avoid debate."],"answer":"B","location":"","analysis":"根据题干关键词NASA定位至第七段。该段提到,美国国家航空航天局使用“气候变化”这一术语,是因为它更准确地反映了由于大气中温室气体的不断增加而给地球带来的广泛变化。可知,选择“气候变化”这一术语的原因是“在涉及温室效应所引起的不良后果时,这一术语的表述更为准确”,故答案选B)项。其他三项均无法从文中得知是否是美国国家航空航天局使用这一术语的原因﹐故排除。"},{"order":55,"question":"What is the author’s final conclusion?","options":["A) Global warming is the more accurate term.","B) Accuracy of terminology matters in science.","C) Human activities have serious effects on Earth.","D) Politics interferes with serious scientific debate. "],"answer":"C","location":"","analysis":"根据题干关键词the author's final conclusion定位至文章末段。在该段中,作者概括性地介绍了对于术语的争论有史以来就存在。其中,末句提到,现在我们知道,不管你怎么称呼它,人类的行为正在使地球变暖,并面临着严重的后果。可知,作者认为无论采用哪个术语,人类的活动都正在给地球带来不好的后果,故答案选C)项。第七段首句中指出,“气候变化”这一术语可以更准确地反映温室气体对地球变化的影响,故排防A)项;B)项和D项在文中均未提及,故排除。"}]}]}
{"_id":"8e1706526193a305043ecc0a74572e32","id":"2020120203","type":"CET4","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are.2 passages in this section.Each passage is followed by some questions or wnfinishedstatements. For each of them there are four choices marked A),B),C) and D). You should decide on thebest choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["Boredom has, paradoxically, become quite interesting to academics lately. In early May, London’s Boring Conference celebrated seven years of delighting in dullness. At this event, people flocked to talks about weather , traffic jams and vending-machine sounds, among other sleep-inducing topics.","What, exactly, is everybody studying? One widely accepted psychological definition of boredom is“the distasteful experience of wanting, but being unable, to engage in satisfying activity.” But how can you quantify a person’s boredom level and compare it with someone else’s? In 1986,psychologists introduced the Boredom Proneness Scale,designed to measure an individual’s overall tendency to feel bored.By contrast,the Multidimensional State Boredom Scale, developed in 2008, measures a person’s feelings of boredom in a given situation.","Boredom has been linked to behavior issues including inattentive driving, mindless snacking, excessive drinking, and addictive gambling. In fact,many of us would choose pain over boredom. One team of psychologists discovered that two-thirds of men and a quarter of women would rather self-administer electric shocks than sit alone with their thoughts for 15 minutes. Researching this phenomenon, another team asked volunteers to watch boring, sad, or neutral films, during which they could self-administer electric shocks. The bored volunteers shocked themselves more and harder than the sad or neutral ones did.","But boredom isn’t all bad. By encouraging self-reflection and daydreaming, it can spur creativity. An early study gave participants abundant time to complete problem-solving and word-association exercises. Once all the obvious answers were exhausted, participants gave more and more inventive answers to combat boredom.A British study took these findings one step further, asking subjects to complete a creative challenge (coming up with a list of alternative uses for a household item). One group of subjects did a boring activity first,while the others went straight to the creative task. Those whose boredom pumps had been primed were more productive.","In our always-connected world, boredom may be a hard-to-define state, but it is a fertile one.Watch paint dry or water boil, or at least put away your smartphone for a while, and you might unlock your next big idea."],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"When are people likely to experience boredom, according to an accepted psychological definition?","options":["A) When they don’t have the chance to do what they want.","B) When they don’t enjoy the materials they are studying. ","C) When they experience something unpleasant.","D) When they engage in some routine activities. "],"answer":"A","location":" ","analysis":":根据题干关键词acceptedpsychologicaldefinition定位至第二段第二句。该句提到,一个被广泛接受的关于无聊的心理学定义是“渴望但又无法参加令人满意的活动而产生的令人不快的经历”。故答案选 A)项。其他三项均不符合心理学定义的内容,故排除。"},{"order":47,"question":"What does the author say boredom can lead to?","options":["A) Determination.","B) Mental deterioration. ","C) Concentration ","D) Harmful conduct. "],"answer":"D","location":"","analysis":"题目就提问。根据题干关键词 boredomcanleadto定位至第三段首句。该句提到,无聊与一些行为问题有关,包括分心驾驶、漫不经心地吃零食、过度饮酒和赌博成瘾。这些行为都是不好的行为习惯,故答案选D)项。A)项在文中并未提及,故排除;B)项与定位句中提到的inattentive不符,故排除;过度饮酒和赌博成瘾或许可以概括为“精神颓废”,但分心驾驶和漫不经心地吃零食不属于“精神颓废”,因此 C)项不能概括文中提到的所有行为,故排除。"},{"order":48,"question":" What is the finding of one team of psychologists in their experiment?","options":["A) Volunteers prefer watching a boring movie to sitting alone deliberating.","B) Many volunteers choose to hurt themselves rather than endure boredom.","C) Male volunteers are more immune to the effects of boredom than females.","D) Many volunteers are unable to resist boredom longer than fifteen minutes. "],"answer":"B","location":"","analysis":"根据题干关键词findingofoneteamofpsychologists定位至第三段第三句。该句提到,一个心理学家小组发现,三分之二的男性和四分之一的女性宁愿自我电击,也不愿独坐思考15分钟。可知,“许多志愿者宁愿自我伤害也不愿忍受无聊”,故答案选 B)项。A)项中的“watchingaboringmovie”是另一个研究小组的研究内容,故排除;该项研究发现,三分之二的男性和四分之一的女性宁愿自我电击,说明,男性更易受到无聊的影响, 故排除 C)项;D)项属曲解文意,故排除。"},{"order":49,"question":"Why does the author say boredom isn’t all bad?","options":["A) It stimulates memorization.","B) It allows time for relaxation. ","C) It may promote creative thinking. ","D) It may facilitate independent learning. "],"answer":"C","location":"","analysis":"根据题干关键词boredomisn􀆳tallbad定位至第四段首句。该句提到,但无聊并不都是坏事。通过鼓励自我反省和幻想,它可以激发创造力。故答案选 C)项。其他三项在文中均未提及,故排除。"},{"order":50,"question":"What does the author suggest one do when faced with a challenging problem? ","options":["A) Stop idling and think big.","B) Unlock one’s smartphone.  ","C) Look around oneself for stimulation. ","D) Allow oneself some time to be bored."],"answer":"D","location":"","analysis":"根据题干关键词authorsuggest定位至末段。该段第二句提到,看着油漆变干或者水沸腾,或者至少把你的智能手机暂时收起来一会儿,你可能会解锁你的又一个了不起的创意。说明,当你做一些无聊的事情时,让头脑放松,可能会想出了不起的创意;那么在面对具有挑战性的问题时,也可以这么做。故答案选 D)项。A)项和 C)项在文中均未提及,故排除;B)项与作者所提的建议相悖,故排除。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["Forests in countries like Brazil and the Congo get a lot of attention from environmentalists,and it is easy to see why. South America and sub-Saharan Africa are experiencing deforestation on an enormous scale: every year almost 5 million hectares are lost. But forests are also changing in rich Western countries. They are growing larger, both in the sense that they occupy more land and that the trees in them are bigger. What is going on? ","Forests are spreading in almost all Western countries,with the fastest growth in places that historically had rather few trees. In 1990 28% of Spain was forested;now the proportion is 37%. In both Greece and Italy, the growth was from 26% to 32% over the same period.Forests are gradually taking more land in America and Australia.Perhaps most astonishing is the trend in Ireland. Roughly 1% of that country was forested when it became independent in 1922. Now forests cover 11% of the land,and the government wants to push the proportion to 18% by the 2040s. ","Two things are fertilising this growth. The first is the abandonment of farmland, especially in high, dry places where nothing grows terribly well. When farmers give up trying to earn a living from farming or herding,trees simply move in. The second is government policy and subsidy. Throughout history, governments have protected and promoted forests for diverse reasons,ranging from the need for wooden warships to a desire to promote suburban house-building. Nowadays forests are increasingly welcome because they suck in carbon pollution from the air. The justifications change, the desire for more trees remains constant.","The greening of the West does not delight everyone.Farmers complain that land is being taken out of use by generously subsidised tree plantations.Parts of Spain and Portugal suffer from terrible forest fires. Others simply dislike the appearance of forests planted in neat rows.They will have to get used to the trees, however. The growth of Western forests seems almost as unstoppable as deforestation elsewhere."],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":" What is catching environmentalists’ attention nowadays?","options":["A) Rich countries are stripping poor ones of their resources.","B) Forests are fast shrinking in many developing countries. ","C) Forests are eating away the fertile farmland worldwide. ","D) Rich countries are doing little to address deforestation."],"answer":"B","location":"","analysis":"根据题干关键词environmentalists􀆳attention定位至文章首句。该句提到,巴西和刚果等国的森林受到了环保主义者的广泛关注,原因很容易理解。随后进一步指出原因是南美洲和撒哈拉以南的非洲正经历着大规模的森林砍伐。可知,“许多发展中国家的森林面积在迅速减少”引起了环保主义者们的注意,故答案选 B)项。A)项在文中并未提及,故排除;第三段中提到,在西方国家,由于某些地区放弃了种什么都长不好的农田,因此才会有树木种进来。说明,并非森林侵蚀了肥沃的农田,故排除 C)项;第三段中提到,森林面积增加的第二个因素是政府出于各种原因保护和推广森林的发展。说明,西方富裕国家对于解决森林砍伐问题并非无作为,故排除 D)项。"},{"order":52,"question":" Which countries have the fastest forest growth?","options":["A) Those that have newly achieved independence.","B) Those that have the greatest demand for timber.","C) Those that used to have the lowest forest coverage. ","D) Those that provide enormous government subsidies. "],"answer":"C","location":"","analysis":"根据题干关键词fastestforestgrowth定位至第二段首句。该句提到,几乎所有的西方国家的森林都在扩张,在历史上树木稀少的地方增长得最快。故答案选 C)项。第二段中提到,爱尔兰在1922年独立,并不是指 newlyachievedindependence,故排除 A)项;B)项在文中并未提及,故排除;第三段中提到的governmentpolicyandsubsidy指的是政府的政策和补贴促进了森林的扩张,但并未提及这个因素和森林增长快之间的关系,故排除 D)项。"},{"order":53,"question":" What has encouraged forest growth historically?","options":["A) The government’s advocacy.","B) The use of wood for fuel.","C) The favourable climate. ","D) The green movement."],"answer":"A","location":"","analysis":"根据题干关键词encouragedforestgrowth定位至第三段首句。该句提到,有两个因素在促进这种增长。即放弃农田和政府的政策及补贴;第五句中还提到,纵观历史,各国政府都出于各种原因保护和推广森林的发展。可知,“政府的倡导”促进了历史上森林面积的增加,故答案选 A)项。其他三项在文中均未提及,故排除。"},{"order":54,"question":" What accounts for our increasing desire for forests?","options":["A) Their unique scenic beauty.","B) Their use as fruit plantations.","C) Their capability of improving air quality. ","D) Their stable supply of building materials. "],"answer":"C","location":"","analysis":"根据题干关键词 ourincreasingdesireforforests定位至第三段倒数第二句。该句提到,森林越来越受欢迎,因为它们吸收空气中的碳污染。可知,森林可以改善空气质量,故答案选 C)项。其他三项在文中均未提及,故排除。"},{"order":55,"question":" What does the author conclude about the prospects of forestation?","options":["A) Deserts in sub-Saharan Africa will diminish gradually.","B) It will play a more and more important role in people’s lives. ","C) Forest destruction in the developing world will quickly slow down.","D) Developed and developing countries are moving in opposite directions. "],"answer":"D","location":"","analysis":"根据题干关键词conclude和prospectsofforestation定位至文章末句。该句提到,西方国家森林的增长似乎和其他地方的森林砍伐一样几乎势不可挡。该句呼应开头提到的西方富裕国家森林增多,有些发展中国家森林减少。说明,作者认为“发达国家和发展中国家正在朝相反的方向发展”,故答案选 D)项。文章首段中提到的是撒哈拉以南的非洲地区的森林将会继续减少,而不是沙漠减少,故排除 A)项;B)项在文中并未提及,"}]}]}
{"_id":"8e1706526193a305043ecc0b5ae68fb6","id":"2020120103","type":"CET4","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are.2 passages in this section.Each passage is followed by some questions or wnfinishedstatements. For each of them there are four choices marked A),B),C) and D). You should decide on thebest choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["Three children in every classroom have a diagnosable mental health condition. Half of these are behavioural disorders,while one third are emotional disorders such as stress,anxiety and depression, which often become outwardly apparent through self-harm. There was an astonishing 52 per cent jump in hospital admissions for children and young people who had harmed themselves between 2009 and 2015.","Schools and teachers have consistently reported the scale of the problem since 2009.Last year, over half of teachers reported that more of their pupils experience mental health problems than in the past. But teachers also consistently report how ill-equipped they feel to meet pupils’ mental health needs,and often cite a lack of training，expertise and support from the National Health Service（英国国家医疗服务体系）.","Part of the reason for the increased pressure on.schools is that there are now fewer ‘early intervention （干预）’and low-level mental health services based in the community. Cuts to local authority budgets since 2010 have resulted in a significant decline of these services, despite strong evidence of their effectiveness in preventing crises further down the line.","The only way to break the pressures on both mental health services and schools is to reinvest in early intervention services inside schools.","There are strong arguments for why schools are best placed to provide mental health services. Schools see young people more than any other service,which gives them a unique ability to get to hard-to-reach children and young people and build meaningful relationships with them over time. Recent studies have shown that children and young people largely prefer to see a counsellor in school rather than in an.outside environment. Young people have reported that for low-level conditions such as stress and anxiety,a clinical setting can sometimes be daunting（令人却步的）.","There are already examples of innovative schools which combine mental health and wellbeing provision with a strong academic curriculum. This will,though,require a huge cultural shift. Politicians, policymakers,commissioners and school leaders must be brave enough to make the leap towards reimagining schools as providers of health as well as education services. "],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"What are teachers complaining about?","options":["A)There are too many students requiring special attention. ","B)They are under too much stress counselling needy students. ","C)Schools are inadequately equipped to implement any intervention. ","D)They lack the necessary resources to address pupils’ mental problems. "],"answer":"D","location":"由题干中的teachers 和complaining定位到第二段最后一句。","analysis":"细节辨认题。定位句指出,老师们也经常报告他们感觉自己在满足学生的心理健康需求方面能力欠缺,并且经常提到缺乏英国国家医疗服务体系的培训专业知识和支持。由此可见，老师们抱怨的是他们缺乏解决学生心理向题的必要资源,故答案为D)“他们缺乏解决学生心理问题的必要资源”。"},{"order":47,"question":"What do we learn from the passage about community health services in Britain?","options":["A)) They have deteriorated due to budget cuts. ","B)They facilitate local residents’ everyday lives. ","C)They prove ineffective in helping mental patients. ","D)They cover preventative care for the local resident."],"answer":"A","location":"由题干中的community health services定位到第三段。","analysis":"推理判断题。定位段第一句提到，现在社区的“早期千预”和初级心理健康服务越来越少,接下来在第二句分析了原因，自2010年以来,地方政府预算的削减导致了这些服务的大幅下降，故答案为A)“由于预算削减,它们情况恶化了”。"},{"order":48,"question":" Where does the author suggest mental health services be placed?","options":["A)At home. ","B)At school. ","C) In hospitals. ","D) In communities."],"answer":"B","location":"由题干中的mental health servi ces和be placed定位到第五段倒数第二句。","analysis":"细节辨认题。定位句指出,最近的研究表明,儿童和年轻人在很大程度上更喜欢在学校里找辅导员，而不是在校外，故答案为B)。"},{"order":49,"question":" What do we learn from the recent studies?","options":["A) Students prefer to rely on peers to relieve stress and anxiety. ","B) Young people are keen on building meaningful relationships. ","C) Students are more comfortable seeking counselling in school. ","D) Young people benefit from various kinds of outdoor activities. "],"answer":"C","location":"由题干中的recent studies定位到第五段最后两句。","analysis":"推理判断题。定位句提到,最近的研究表明，儿童和年轻人在很大程度上更喜欢在学校里找辅导员,而不是在校外。年轻人报告说,对于压力和焦虑等初级状况,临床环境有时会令人望而生畏。由此可知，青少年在学校环境下接受心理辅导会感到更自在,故答案为C)。"},{"order":50,"question":"What does the author mean by a cultural shift (Line 2, Para. 6)?","options":["A) Simplification of schools’ academic curriculums. ","B) Parents’ involvement in schools’ policy-making. ","C) A change in teachers’ attitudes to mental health. ","D) A change in the conception of what schools are. "],"answer":"D","location":"由题干中的a cultural shift和Para. 6定位到最后一段。","analysis":"语义理解题。定位段第二句指出,这将需要巨大的文化转变。第三句接着对“文化转变”作出了阐释:政治家、政策制定者、部长和学校领导必须足够勇敢,向着将学校重新塑造为健康和教育服务提供者的方向飞跃。由此可知,这种文化转变是将学校重新塑造为健康和教育服务提供者，故答案为D)“对学校观念的转变”。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["The work-life balance is dead. By this , I'm not advocating that you should give up your pursuit of having a fufilling career and a thriving personal life, and I'm definitely not saying that you have to give up one to have the other. I also acknowledge that we have a work-life problem, but I'm arguing that the concept of balance has never been helpful, because it's too limiting. You see, our language makes a difference, and how we refer to things matters because it affects our thinking and therefore our actions.","At the minimum, most of us work because we want to be able to support ourselves, our families ,and the people around us. In the ideal world, we're all doing work that we're proud of and that provides meaning and purpose to us. But even if your job doesn't give you shivers of joy each new day, working is a part of what each of us does and the contribution we make to society. When you separate work and life, it's a lttle bit harder to make that connection. But when you think of work as part of a full life and a complete experience, it becomes easier to see that success in one aspect often supports another.","Losing your balance and falling isn't pleasant. A goal to balance suggests that things could quickly get off balance, and that causes terrible outcomes. I's more constructive to think of solutions that continue to evolve over shifts in life and work. Rather than fllig or filing, you may have good days or better days or not-so good days. These variations are normal, and its more useful to think of life as something that is ever evolving and changing, rather than a high-risk enterprise where things could go wrong with one misstep.","How we tllk to ouselves matters, and how we tlk about issues makes a difference. Let's bury “work-life balance” and think bigger and better about work-life fullment to do a lttle less balancing and a lot more living."],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":"Why does the author ask us to imagine buying food in the movie theater?","options":["A)To illustrate people's peculiar shopping behavior. ","B)To illustrate the increasing variety of snacks there.","C)To show how hard it can be to choose a drink there.","D)To show how popular snacks are among movie fans."],"answer":"A","location":"由题干中的buying food in the movie theater定位到第一段第一句。","analysis":"细节辨认题。定位段第一句指出,工作与生活的平衡已经消失了。第三句提到，平衡的概念从来没有什么帮助,因为它太局限了。D)中的contributes little和原文中has never been helpful相对应,故答案为D)。"},{"order":52,"question":" Why is the medium soda priced the way it is? ","options":["A)To attract more customers to buy it. ","B)To show the price matches the amount. ","C)To ensure customers drink the right amount of soda. ","D)To make customers believe they are getting a bargain. "],"answer":"D","location":" 由题干中的language定位到第一段末句。","analysis":" 推理判断题。定位句提到,市场营销部很有可能故意以中杯汽水作为诱饵,让你更有可能购买大杯汽水而不是小杯。第一段倒数第二句提到,大杯汽水只比中杯的贵0.25美分。由此可知,之所以这样给中杯定价,是为了让消费者认为买大杯更合算,故答案为D)“为了让顾客相信他们买得很合算”。"},{"order":53,"question":" What do we learn from Dan Ariely’s experiment? ","options":["A)Lower-priced goods attract more customers. ","B)The Economist’s promotional strategy works.","C)The Economist’s print edition turns out to sell the best. ","D)More readers choose the digital over the print edition."],"answer":"B","location":"由题干中的Dan Ariely's experiment定位到第三段最后两句。","analysis":" 推理判断题。定位句指出,艾瑞里做了一个实验,发现当只提供两个“真实的”选项时,更多的人选择了价格较低的数字版订阅。但是不良选项的增加使人们更有可能选择更昂贵的印刷版加数字版这-选项。由此可知,在面对《经济学人》提供的三个选项时,人们更倾向于选择订阅印刷版加数字版，即《经济学人》的宜传策略奏效了,故答案为B)。"},{"order":54,"question":" For what purpose is “the bad option” (Line 7, Para.3)added?","options":["A)To cater to the peculiar needs of some customers. ","B)To help customers to make more rational choices.","C)To trap customers into buying the more pricey item. ","D)To provide customers with a greater variety of goods."],"answer":"C","location":"由题干中的the bad option和Para 3定位到第三段最后一句。","analysis":"推理判断题。定位句指出,不良选项(印刷版订阅费125美元)的增加使人们更有可能选择更昂贵的印刷版加数字版这一选项。由此可知,添加“不良选项”是为了诱使顾客购买价格较高的商品,故答案为C) 诱使顾客购买价格较高的商品。"},{"order":55,"question":"How do we assess the value of a commodity, acording to the passage? ","options":["A) By considering its usefulness. ","B) By comparing it with other choices. ","C) By taking its quality into account. ","D) By examining its value equation."],"answer":"B","location":" 由题干中的the value of a commodity定位到最后一段最后两句。","analysis":" 细节辨认题。定位句指出,价值几乎从来不是绝对的;相反,我们是相对于其他选择来确定某一物品的价值。如果引入更多选项,则价值等式将发生变化。由此可知,我们是通过比较不同的选择来评估某一商品的价值,故答案为B)“通过与其他选择进行比较”。"}]}]}
{"_id":"8e1706526193a305043ecc0c0180c5d2","id":"2020090303","type":"CET4","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are 2 passages in this section.Each passage is followed by some questions or wnfinishedstatements. For each of them there are four choices marked A),B),C) and D). You should decide on thebest choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["When is cleaning was a crime? When you’re doing it to create art, obviously. A number of street artists around the world have started expressing themselves through a practice known as reverse graffiti (涂鸦). They find dirty surfaces and paint them with images or messages using cleaning brushes or pressure hoses (高压水管) . Either way, it's the same principle: the image is made by cleaning away the dirt. Each artist has their own individual style but all artists share a common aim: to draw attention to the pollution in our cities. The UK’s Paul Curtis, better known as Moose, operates around Leeds and London and has been commissioned by a number of companies to make reverse graffiti advertisements.","Brazilian artist, Alexandre Orion, turned one of Sao Paulo's transport tunnels into an amazing wall painting in 2006 by getting rid of the dirt. Made up of a series of white skulls (颅骨), the painting reminds drivers of the effect their pollution is having on the planet. “Every motorists sits in the comfort of their car, but they don't give any consideration to the price their comfort has for the environment and consequently for themselves,” says Orion.","The anti-pollution message of the reverse graffiti artists confuses city authorities since the main argument against graffiti is that it spoils the appearance of both types of property: public and private. This was what Leeds City Council said about Moose's work: “Leeds residents want to live in clean and attractive neighbourhoods. We view this kind of advertising as environmental damage and will take strong action against it.” Moose was ordered to “clean up his act.” How was he supposed to do this: by making all property he had cleaned dirty again?","As for the Brazilian artist’s work, the authorities were annoyed but could find nothing to charge him with. They had no other option but to clean the tunnel—but only the parts Alexandre had already cleaned. The artist merely continued his campaign on the other side. The city officials then decided to take drastic action. They not only cleaned the whole tunnel but every tunnel in Sao Paulo."],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"What do we learn from the passage about reverse graffiti?","options":["A) It uses paint to create anti-pollution images.","B)  It creates a lot of trouble for local residents.","C)  It causes lots of distraction to drivers.","D)  It turns dirty walls into artistic works."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】由题干中的reverse graffiti定位到首段第三句。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位句后的两句指出,他们找到一些有污垢的墙面,然后用清洁刷或高压水管在上面画上图像或文字。不管用哪种方式,原则是一样的:通过擦去污垢画上图像。由此可知，反向涂鸦使肮脏的墙面变成了艺术作品,故答案为D)。"},{"order":47,"question":"What do reverse graffiti artists try to do?","options":["A) Publicise their artistic pursuit.","B) Beautify the city environment.","C) Raise public awareness of environmental pollution.","D) Express their dissatisfaction with local governments."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】由题干中的reverse graffiti artists定位到首段倒数第二句。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位句指出,所有的艺术家都有一个共同的目的:提醒人们注意我们城市里的污染。由此可知,反向涂鸦艺术家想提高公众对于环境污染的意识,故答案为C)。"},{"order":48,"question":"What do we learn about Brazilian artist Alexandre Orion?","options":["A) He was good at painting white skulls.","B) He chose tunnels to do his graffiti art.","C) He suggested banning all polluting cars.","D) He was fond of doing creative artworks."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】由题干中的Brazilian artist AlexandreOrion定位到第二段第一句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句指出﹐巴西艺术家亚历山大·奥利恩在2006年通过清除灰尘把圣保罗的一条交通隧道变成了一幅令人惊叹的壁画。由此可见,亚历山大·奥利恩选择了在隧道里创作他的涂鸦艺术,故答案为B)。"},{"order":49,"question":" What does the author imply about Leeds City Council’s decision?","options":["A) It is simply absurd.","B) It is well-informed.","C) It is rather unexpected.","D)  It is quite sensible."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】由题干中的Leeds City Council's decision定位到第三段第二至五句。","analysis":"【精析】观点态度题。定位句提到,利兹市议会对穆斯的作品作出这样的评价:“利兹市民想要生活在干净和有魅力的社区里。我们认为这种广告是对环境的破坏,我们会采取强硬措施来抵制它。”穆斯被要求“清理自己做过的事”。他应该怎么做呢?要把他已经清洁的所有墙面再弄脏吗?作者以反讽的语气说明无法清除已经创作好的反向涂鸦作品。由此可见,作者暗示利兹市议会的决定很荒谬,故答案为A)。"},{"order":50,"question":"How did Sao Paulo city officials handle Alexandre Orion’s reverse graffiti?","options":["A)  They made him clean all the tunnels in Sao Paulo.","B) They took drastic action to ban all reverse graffiti.","C) They charged him with polluting tunnels in the city.","D)They made it impossible for him to practice his art."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】由题干中的 Sao Paulo city officials定位到最后一段最后两句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句指出,圣保罗市官员决定采取严厉措施。他们不仅清理了整个隧道，而且把圣保罗的每一条隧道都清理了。由此可知,所有隧道被清理干净了,亚历山大就无法在隧道里进行反向涂鸦创作了,故答案为D)。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["The practice of paying children an allowance became popular in America about 100 years ago. Nowadays, American kids on average receive about $800 per year in allowance. But the vast majority of American parents who pay allowance tie it to the completion of housework. Although many parents believe that paying an allowance for completing chores benefits their children, a range of experts expressed concern that tying allowance very closely to chores may not be ideal. In fact, the way chores work in many households worldwide points to another way.","Suniya Luthar, a psychologist, is against paying kids for chores. Luthar is not opposed to giving allowances, but she thinks it’s important to establish that chores are done not because they will lead to payment, but because they keep the household running. Luthar’s suggested approach to allowance is compatible with that of writer Ron Lieber, who advises that allowances be used as a means of showing children how to save, give, and spend on things they care about. Kids should do chores, he writes, “for the same reason adults do, because the chores need to be done, and not with the expectation of compensation.”","This argument has its critics, but considering the way chores are undertaken around the world may change people’s thinking. Professor David Lancy of Utah State University has studied how families around the world handle chores. At about 18 months of age, Lancy says, most children become eager to help their parents, and in many cultures, they begin helping with housework at that age. They begin with very simple tasks, but their responsibilities gradually increase. And they do these tasks without payment. Lancy contrasts this with what happens in America. “We deny our children’s bids to help until they are 6 or 7 years old,” Lancy says, “when many have lost the desire to help and then try to motivate them with payment. The solution to this problem is not to try to use money as an incentive to do housework, but to get children involved in housework much earlier, when they actually want to do it.”"],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":"What do some experts think about paying children for doing chores?","options":["A)  It may benefit children in more ways than one.","B)  It may help children learn the worth of labor.","C)  It may not turn out to be the best thing to do.","D)  It may not be accepted by low-income parents."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】由题干中的 some experts.paying children和chores定位到首段第四句。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位句指出,尽管很多父母认为因为完成家务活而给孩子零用钱对他们的孩子来说是有益的,但很多专家担心把零用钱和做家务联系得太紧密了可能并不理想。由此可知，专家认为给孩子钱让他们做家务可能不是最好的办法,故答案为C)。选项C)中的the best thing对应定位句中的ideal。"},{"order":52,"question":"According to Suniya Luthar, doing chores will help children learn to ____.","options":["A) share family responsibilities","B) appreciate the value of work","C) cultivate the spirit of independence","D) manage domestic affairs themselves"],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】由题干中的Suniya Luthar定位到第二段第一、二句。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位句提到,心理学家苏妮娅·卢瑟反对因为做家务而给孩子钱。卢瑟不反对给孩子零用钱,但是她认为重要的是应该明确不是因为做家务能得到钱而做家务﹐而是因为做家务能让一个家庭正常运转。由此可知，苏妮娅·卢瑟认为做家务能帮孩子学会分担家庭责任,故答案为A)。"},{"order":53,"question":"What does Ron Lieber think should be the goal of giving children allowances?","options":["A) To help to strengthen family ties.","B) To teach them how to manage money.","C) To motivate them to do more housework.","D) To show parents’ appreciation of their help."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】由题干中的 Ron Lieber定位到第二段第三句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句指出,罗恩·利伯建议零用钱被用作一种向孩子展示如何节省、给予和花在他们在乎的东西上的方法。由此可见，罗恩·利伯认为零花钱教会孩子如何管理金钱，故答案为B)。"},{"order":54,"question":"What does David Lancy say about 18-month-olds?","options":["A) They have a natural instinct to help around the house.","B) They are too young to request money for what they do.","C) They should learn to understand family responsibilities.","D) They need a little incentive to get involved in housework."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】由题干中的David Lancy和 18-month-olds定位到第三段第三句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句提到,兰西认为大多数孩子在大约18个月的时候会渴望帮助他们的父母。由此可见,18个月的孩子本能地想在家里帮忙,故答案为A)。"},{"order":55,"question":"What does David Lancy advise American parents to do?","options":["A)  Set a good example for children in doing housework.","B) Make children do housework without compensation.","C) Teach children how to do housework.","D) Accept children’s early bids to help."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】由题干中的 David Lancy和 advise定位到第三段最后一句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句指出兰西的观点:解决这个问题的办法不是试图用金钱来激励孩子做家务,而是当他们真正想做的时候,让他们更早地参与到家务中。由此可知,兰西认为美国父母应接受孩子早期想帮忙的尝试,故答案为D)。"}]}]}
{"_id":"8e1706526193a305043ecc0d56a04ccb","id":"2020090203","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are 2 passages in this section.Each passage is followed by some questions or wnfinishedstatements. For each of them there are four choices marked A),B),C) and D). You should decide on thebest choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["When is cleaning was a crime? When you’re doing it to create art, obviously. A number of street artists around the world have started expressing themselves through a practice known as reverse graffiti (涂鸦). They find dirty surfaces and paint them with images or messages using cleaning brushes or pressure hoses (高压水管) . Either way, it's the same principle: the image is made by cleaning away the dirt. Each artist has their own individual style but all artists share a common aim: to draw attention to the pollution in our cities. The UK’s Paul Curtis, better known as Moose, operates around Leeds and London and has been commissioned by a number of companies to make reverse graffiti advertisements.","Brazilian artist, Alexandre Orion, turned one of Sao Paulo's transport tunnels into an amazing wall painting in 2006 by getting rid of the dirt. Made up of a series of white skulls (颅骨), the painting reminds drivers of the effect their pollution is having on the planet. “Every motorists sits in the comfort of their car, but they don't give any consideration to the price their comfort has for the environment and consequently for themselves,” says Orion.","The anti-pollution message of the reverse graffiti artists confuses city authorities since the main argument against graffiti is that it spoils the appearance of both types of property: public and private. This was what Leeds City Council said about Moose's work: “Leeds residents want to live in clean and attractive neighbourhoods. We view this kind of advertising as environmental damage and will take strong action against it.” Moose was ordered to “clean up his act.” How was he supposed to do this: by making all property he had cleaned dirty again?","As for the Brazilian artist’s work, the authorities were annoyed but could find nothing to charge him with. They had no other option but to clean the tunnel—but only the parts Alexandre had already cleaned. The artist merely continued his campaign on the other side. The city officials then decided to take drastic action. They not only cleaned the whole tunnel but every tunnel in Sao Paulo."],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"What do we learn from the passage about reverse graffiti?","options":["A) It uses paint to create anti-pollution images.","B)  It creates a lot of trouble for local residents.","C)  It causes lots of distraction to drivers.","D)  It turns dirty walls into artistic works."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】由题干中的reverse graffiti定位到首段第三句。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位句后的两句指出,他们找到一些有污垢的墙面,然后用清洁刷或高压水管在上面画上图像或文字。不管用哪种方式,原则是一样的:通过擦去污垢画上图像。由此可知，反向涂鸦使肮脏的墙面变成了艺术作品,故答案为D)。"},{"order":47,"question":"What do reverse graffiti artists try to do?","options":["A) Publicise their artistic pursuit.","B) Beautify the city environment.","C) Raise public awareness of environmental pollution.","D) Express their dissatisfaction with local governments."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】由题干中的reverse graffiti artists定位到首段倒数第二句。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位句指出,所有的艺术家都有一个共同的目的:提醒人们注意我们城市里的污染。由此可知,反向涂鸦艺术家想提高公众对于环境污染的意识,故答案为C)。"},{"order":48,"question":"What do we learn about Brazilian artist Alexandre Orion?","options":["A) He was good at painting white skulls.","B) He chose tunnels to do his graffiti art.","C) He suggested banning all polluting cars.","D) He was fond of doing creative artworks."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】由题干中的Brazilian artist AlexandreOrion定位到第二段第一句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句指出﹐巴西艺术家亚历山大·奥利恩在2006年通过清除灰尘把圣保罗的一条交通隧道变成了一幅令人惊叹的壁画。由此可见,亚历山大·奥利恩选择了在隧道里创作他的涂鸦艺术,故答案为B)。"},{"order":49,"question":" What does the author imply about Leeds City Council’s decision?","options":["A) It is simply absurd.","B) It is well-informed.","C) It is rather unexpected.","D)  It is quite sensible."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】由题干中的Leeds City Council's decision定位到第三段第二至五句。","analysis":"【精析】观点态度题。定位句提到,利兹市议会对穆斯的作品作出这样的评价:“利兹市民想要生活在干净和有魅力的社区里。我们认为这种广告是对环境的破坏,我们会采取强硬措施来抵制它。”穆斯被要求“清理自己做过的事”。他应该怎么做呢?要把他已经清洁的所有墙面再弄脏吗?作者以反讽的语气说明无法清除已经创作好的反向涂鸦作品。由此可见,作者暗示利兹市议会的决定很荒谬,故答案为A)。"},{"order":50,"question":"How did Sao Paulo city officials handle Alexandre Orion’s reverse graffiti?","options":["A)  They made him clean all the tunnels in Sao Paulo.","B) They took drastic action to ban all reverse graffiti.","C) They charged him with polluting tunnels in the city.","D)They made it impossible for him to practice his art."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】由题干中的 Sao Paulo city officials定位到最后一段最后两句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句指出,圣保罗市官员决定采取严厉措施。他们不仅清理了整个隧道，而且把圣保罗的每一条隧道都清理了。由此可知,所有隧道被清理干净了,亚历山大就无法在隧道里进行反向涂鸦创作了,故答案为D)。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["The practice of paying children an allowance became popular in America about 100 years ago. Nowadays, American kids on average receive about $800 per year in allowance. But the vast majority of American parents who pay allowance tie it to the completion of housework. Although many parents believe that paying an allowance for completing chores benefits their children, a range of experts expressed concern that tying allowance very closely to chores may not be ideal. In fact, the way chores work in many households worldwide points to another way.","Suniya Luthar, a psychologist, is against paying kids for chores. Luthar is not opposed to giving allowances, but she thinks it’s important to establish that chores are done not because they will lead to payment, but because they keep the household running. Luthar’s suggested approach to allowance is compatible with that of writer Ron Lieber, who advises that allowances be used as a means of showing children how to save, give, and spend on things they care about. Kids should do chores, he writes, “for the same reason adults do, because the chores need to be done, and not with the expectation of compensation.”","This argument has its critics, but considering the way chores are undertaken around the world may change people’s thinking. Professor David Lancy of Utah State University has studied how families around the world handle chores. At about 18 months of age, Lancy says, most children become eager to help their parents, and in many cultures, they begin helping with housework at that age. They begin with very simple tasks, but their responsibilities gradually increase. And they do these tasks without payment. Lancy contrasts this with what happens in America. “We deny our children’s bids to help until they are 6 or 7 years old,” Lancy says, “when many have lost the desire to help and then try to motivate them with payment. The solution to this problem is not to try to use money as an incentive to do housework, but to get children involved in housework much earlier, when they actually want to do it.”"],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":"What do some experts think about paying children for doing chores?","options":["A)  It may benefit children in more ways than one.","B)  It may help children learn the worth of labor.","C)  It may not turn out to be the best thing to do.","D)  It may not be accepted by low-income parents."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】由题干中的 some experts.paying children和chores定位到首段第四句。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位句指出,尽管很多父母认为因为完成家务活而给孩子零用钱对他们的孩子来说是有益的,但很多专家担心把零用钱和做家务联系得太紧密了可能并不理想。由此可知，专家认为给孩子钱让他们做家务可能不是最好的办法,故答案为C)。选项C)中的the best thing对应定位句中的ideal。"},{"order":52,"question":"According to Suniya Luthar, doing chores will help children learn to ____.","options":["A) share family responsibilities","B) appreciate the value of work","C) cultivate the spirit of independence","D) manage domestic affairs themselves"],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】由题干中的Suniya Luthar定位到第二段第一、二句。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位句提到,心理学家苏妮娅·卢瑟反对因为做家务而给孩子钱。卢瑟不反对给孩子零用钱,但是她认为重要的是应该明确不是因为做家务能得到钱而做家务﹐而是因为做家务能让一个家庭正常运转。由此可知，苏妮娅·卢瑟认为做家务能帮孩子学会分担家庭责任,故答案为A)。"},{"order":53,"question":"What does Ron Lieber think should be the goal of giving children allowances?","options":["A) To help to strengthen family ties.","B) To teach them how to manage money.","C) To motivate them to do more housework.","D) To show parents’ appreciation of their help."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】由题干中的 Ron Lieber定位到第二段第三句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句指出,罗恩·利伯建议零用钱被用作一种向孩子展示如何节省、给予和花在他们在乎的东西上的方法。由此可见，罗恩·利伯认为零花钱教会孩子如何管理金钱，故答案为B)。"},{"order":54,"question":"What does David Lancy say about 18-month-olds?","options":["A) They have a natural instinct to help around the house.","B) They are too young to request money for what they do.","C) They should learn to understand family responsibilities.","D) They need a little incentive to get involved in housework."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】由题干中的David Lancy和 18-month-olds定位到第三段第三句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句提到,兰西认为大多数孩子在大约18个月的时候会渴望帮助他们的父母。由此可见,18个月的孩子本能地想在家里帮忙,故答案为A)。"},{"order":55,"question":"What does David Lancy advise American parents to do?","options":["A)  Set a good example for children in doing housework.","B) Make children do housework without compensation.","C) Teach children how to do housework.","D) Accept children’s early bids to help."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】由题干中的 David Lancy和 advise定位到第三段最后一句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句指出兰西的观点:解决这个问题的办法不是试图用金钱来激励孩子做家务,而是当他们真正想做的时候,让他们更早地参与到家务中。由此可知,兰西认为美国父母应接受孩子早期想帮忙的尝试,故答案为D)。"}]}],"type":"CET4"}
{"_id":"8e1706526193a305043ecc0e19998613","id":"2020090103","type":"CET4","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are.2 passages in this section.Each passage is followed by some questions or wnfinishedstatements. For each of them there are four choices marked A),B),C) and D). You should decide on thebest choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["Americans spend billions of dollars each year trying to change their weight with diets， gym memberships and plastic surgery.","Trying to live up to the images of“perfect” models and movie heroes has a dark side: anxiety,depression, as well as unhealthy strategies for weight loss or muscle gain. It also has a financial cost. Having an eating disorder boosts annual health care costs by nearly US $ 2 000 per person.","Why is there both external and internal pressure to look“ perfect”? One reason is that society rewards people who are thin and healthy-looking. Researchers have shown that body mass index is related to wages and income. Especially for women, there is a clear penalty at work for being overweight or obese. Some studies have also found an impact for men, though a less noticeable one.","While the research literature is clear that labor market success is partly based on how employers and customers perceive your body image, no one had explored the other side of the question. Does a person's own perception of body image matter to earnings and other indicators of success in the . workplace?","Our recently published study answered this question by tracking a large national random sample of Americans over a critical time period when bodies change from teenage shape into adult form and when people build their identities.","As in other research, women in owr sample tend to over-perceive their weight- -they think they're heavier than they are- while men tend to under-perceive theirs.","We found no relationship between the average person's self-perception of weight and labor market outcomes, although self-perceived weight can influence self-esteem (自尊心) , mental health and heath behaviors.","While the continued gender penalty in the labor market is frustrating, our fnding that misperceived weight does not harm workers is more heartening.","Since employers' perception of weight is what matters in the labor market, changing discrimination laws to include body type as a category would help. Michigan is the only state that prohibits discrimination on the basis of weight and height. We believe expanding such protections would make the labor market more fair and efficient."],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"What does the author say may have an adverse impact on people?","options":["A) Undergoing plastic surgeries in pursuit of beauty.","B) Imitating the lifestyles of heroes and role models.","C) Striving to achieve perfection regardless of financial cost.","D) Attempting to meet society's expectation of appearance."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】由题干中的adverse impact定位到第二段第一句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句指出,试图达到“完美”模特和电影英雄的形象有不良影响,这会导致一系列问题。由此可见,试图满足社会对外表的期望会产生负面影响,故答案为D)“试图满足社会对外表的期望”。"},{"order":47,"question":"What have researchers found out about people's earnings?","options":["A) They are closely related to people's social status.","B) They have to do with people's body weight and shape.","C) They seem to matter much less to men than to women.","D) They may not be equal to people's contributions."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】由题干中的people's earnings定位到第三段第三句。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位句提到,研究人员发现，体重指数与工资和收人有关,由此可知人们的收人和体重.体型有关,故答案为B)。"},{"order":48,"question":" What does the author's recent study focus on?","options":["A) Previous literature on indicators of competitiveness in the workplace.","B) Traits that matter most in one's pursuit of suiccess in the labor market.","C) Whether self-perception of body image impacts one's workplace success.","D) How bosses' perception of body image impacts employees' advancement."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】由题干中的recent study和focus on定位到第五段。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位段指出，作者的团队近期公布的研究回答了这个问题,因此可从上一段找出这个问题是什么。第四段最后一句就是作者的研究重点,即一个人对自己身体形象的看法是否会影响他的收人和其他职场中成功的指标,故答案为C)。"},{"order":49,"question":" What is the finding of the author's recent research?","options":["A) Being overweight actually does not do much harm to the overall wellbeing of employees.","B) People are not adversely affected in the workplace by false self-perception of body weight.","C) Self-esteem helps to combat gender inequality in the workplace.","D) Gender inequality continues to frustrate a lot of female employees."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】由题干中的finding. recent research以及题文同序原则定位到第八段。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位段提到,尽管职场上仍然存在性别歧视，但作者的研究发现,对体重的错误认知并不会对劳动者造成伤害,故答案为B)。"},{"order":50,"question":"What does the author think would help improve the situation in the labor market?","options":["A) Banning discrimination on the basis of employees' body image.","B) Expanding protection of women against gender discrimination.","C) Helping employees change their own perception of beauty.","D) Excluding body shape as a category in the labor contract."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】由题干中的help improve the situation定位到最后一段第一句。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位句指出,由于雇主对体重的看法是影响劳动力市场的重要因素,因此修改反歧视法规,将体型加入其中作为-一个类别,将会有所帮助。由此可见，禁止对员工身体形象的歧视将有助于改善现状,故答案为A)。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["The work-life balance is dead. By this , I'm not advocating that you should give up your pursuit of having a fufilling career and a thriving personal life, and I'm definitely not saying that you have to give up one to have the other. I also acknowledge that we have a work-life problem, but I'm arguing that the concept of balance has never been helpful, because it's too limiting. You see, our language makes a difference, and how we refer to things matters because it affects our thinking and therefore our actions.","At the minimum, most of us work because we want to be able to support ourselves, our families ,and the people around us. In the ideal world, we're all doing work that we're proud of and that provides meaning and purpose to us. But even if your job doesn't give you shivers of joy each new day, working is a part of what each of us does and the contribution we make to society. When you separate work and life, it's a lttle bit harder to make that connection. But when you think of work as part of a full life and a complete experience, it becomes easier to see that success in one aspect often supports another.","Losing your balance and falling isn't pleasant. A goal to balance suggests that things could quickly get off balance, and that causes terrible outcomes. I's more constructive to think of solutions that continue to evolve over shifts in life and work. Rather than fllig or filing, you may have good days or better days or not-so good days. These variations are normal, and its more useful to think of life as something that is ever evolving and changing, rather than a high-risk enterprise where things could go wrong with one misstep.","How we tllk to ouselves matters, and how we tlk about issues makes a difference. Let's bury “work-life balance” and think bigger and better about work-life fullment to do a lttle less balancing and a lot more living."],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":"What does the author suggest by saying“The work-life balance is dead”?","options":["A) The hope of achieving a thriving life is impossible to realize.","B) The pursuit of a fulilling career involves personal sacrifice.","C) The imbalance between work and life simply doesn't exist anymore.","D) The concept of work-life balance contributes lttle to a flflling life."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】由题干中的work-life balance is dead定位到第一段。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位段第一句指出,工作与生活的平衡已经消失了。第三句提到，平衡的概念从来没有什么帮助,因为它太局限了。D)中的contributes little和原文中has never been helpful相对应,故答案为D)。"},{"order":52,"question":" What does the author say about our use of language?","options":["A) It impacts how we think and behave.","C) It reflects how we communicate.","B) It changes with the passage of time.","D) It differs from person to person."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】由题干中的language定位到第一段末句。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位句提到,我们的语言会产生作用,我们如何指代事物很重要,因为它会影响我"},{"order":53,"question":" What does the author say we do in an ideal world?","options":["A) We do work that betters the lives of our families and friends.","B) We do work that gives us bursts of joy each new day.","C) We do meaningful work that contributes to society.","D) We do demanding work that brings our capacity into full play."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】由题干中的inanidealworld定位到第二段第二句。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位句指出,在理想的世界中,我们都在做我们引以为豪的工作,这为我们提供了意义和目标。接着由But引出对意义的进一步解释,即工作也是我们每个人所做的事情以及我们对社会所做贡献的一部分。因此,答案为C)。"},{"order":54,"question":" What does the author say about life?","options":["A) It is cyclical.","C) It is fuflling.","B) It is dynamic.","D) It is risky."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】由题干中的life和题文同序原则定位到文章第三段末句。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位句中的think of life as、对应题干中的say about life, evolving和changing意为“进化”和“改变”,与选项B)中的dynamic“动态的”对应,故答案为B)。"},{"order":55,"question":"What does the author advise us to do?","options":["A) Make life as simple as possible.","C) Balance life and work in a new way.","B) Talk about balance in simpler terms.","D) Strive for a more fulflling life."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】由题干中的advise和题文同序原则定位到最后一段第二句。","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题。定位句指出，让我们把“工作与生活平衡”的想法抛之脑后,思维更开阔一些,重新思考如何让工作和生活充实起来,少做一点平衡,让两者更加充满活力。选项D)中的fuflling对应定位句中的fullment ,故答案为D)。"}]}]}
{"_id":"150083c56198ed41030d0d0d4b2fe6ba","id":"2019060103","type":"CET4","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are.2 passages in this section.Each passage is followed by some questions or wnfinishedstatements. For each of them there are four choices marked A),B),C) and D). You should decide on thebest choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["In the classic marriage vow（誓约）, couples promise to stay together in sickness and in health. But a new study finds that the risk of divorce among older couples rises when the wife-not the husband—becomes seriously ill.","“Married women diagnosed with a serious health condition may find themselves struggling with the impact of their disease while also experiencing the stress of divorce,” said researcher Amelia Karraker.","Karraker and co-author Kenzie Latham analyzed 20 years of data on 2,717 marriages from a study conducted by Indiana University since 1992. At the time of the first interview, at least one of the partners was over the age of 50.","The researchers examined how the onset（发生）of four serious physical illnesses affected marriages. They found that, overall, 31% of marriages ended in divorce over the period studied. The incidence of new chronic（慢性的）illness onset increased over time as will, with more husbands than wives developing serious health problems.","“We found that women are doubly vulnerable to marital break-up in the face of illness,” Karraker said. “They’re more likely to be widowed, and if they’re the noes who become ill, they’re more likely to get divorced.”","While the study didn’t assess why divorce in more likely when wives but not husbands become seriously ill, Karraker offers a few possible reasons. “Gender norms and social expectations about caregiving many make it more difficult for men to provide care to sick spouses,” Karraker said. “And because of the imbalance in marriage markets, especially in older ages, divorced men have more choices among prospective partners than divorced women.”","Given the increasing concern about health care costs for the aging population, Karraker believes policymakers should be aware of the relationship between disease and risk of divorce.","“Offering support services to spouses caring for their other halves may reduce marital stress and prevent divorce at older ages,” she said. “But it’s also important to recognize that the pressure to divorce may be health-related and that sick ex-wives may need additional care and services to prevent worsening health and increased health costs.”"],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"What can we learn about marriage vows from the passage?","options":["A) They may not guarantee a lasting marriage.","B) They are as binding as they used to be.","C) They are not taken seriously any more.","D) They may help couples tide over hard times."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】由题干中的 educators 定位到首段前两句","analysis":"【精析】细节辨认题定位句指出教育工作者和商界领袖的共同点比看起来要多。教师希望为学生成功的未来做好准备。Teachers “教师” 指的是 educators “教育工作者”,由此可见,教育工作者帮助学生为成功的未来做好准备,即帮助学生获得未来成功所需的技能,故答案为 C)。"},{"order":47,"question":"What did Karraker and co-author Kenzie Latham find about elderly husbands?","options":["A) They are generally not good at taking care of themselves.","B) They can become increasingly vulnerable to serious illnesses.","C) They can develop different kinds of illnesses just like their wives.","D) They are more likely to contract serious illnesses than their wives."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】由题干中的 better develop students` STEM skills 定位到第二段第一、二句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句提到,专注于 STEM 技能很重要,但当 STEM 技能与传统的动手创造性活动相结合时,这些技能会增强。事实证明,这种结合是让今天的孩子成为明天的创造者和建设者的最佳方式。换言之,通过将培养 STEM 技能与传统的、趣味盎然的活动相结合,能够更好地培养学生的STEM 技能,故答案为 A)。"},{"order":48,"question":"What does Karraker say about women who fall ill?","options":["A) They are more likely to be widowed.","B) They are more likely to get divorced.","C) They are less likely to receive good care.","D) They are less likely to bother their spouses."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】由题干中的 children acquire the skills needed for the 21st century 定位到第三段第一、二句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句指出,许多专家认为21世纪最重要的技能与特定的技术或主题无关,而是与创造力有关;如想象力、发现问题和解决问题的能力、团队合作、乐观、耐心以及做实验和冒险的能力。这些都是孩子们鼓捣小玩意时获得的技能。由此可见,孩子们可以通过摆弄东西来自己解决问题,从而获得21世纪所需的技能,故答案为 B)。"},{"order":49,"question":"Why is it more difficult for men to take care of their sick spouses according to Karraker?","options":["A) They are more accustomed to receiving care.","B) They find it more important to make money for the family.","C) They think it more urgent to fulfill their social obligations.","D) They expect society to do more of the job."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】由题干中的 basics of math and geometry 定位到第四段最后一句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句提到,这种类型的游戏特别是搭积木帮助孩子们发现和掌握数学和几何学的关键原理。由此可见,鼓励孩子们动手做东西可以帮助孩子们学习数学和几何的基础知识,故答案为 C)。"},{"order":50,"question":"What does Karraker think is also important?","options":["A) Reducing marital stress on wives.","B) Stabilizing old couples’ relations.","C) Providing extra care for divorced women.","D) Making men pay for their wives’ health costs."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】由题干中的 disadvantaged schools and communities 定位到文章最后一段最后三句。","analysis":"【精析】推理判断题。定位句指出,这一点对于资源不足的学校和社区尤其重要。利用手边的任何材料,让孩子们去鼓捣小玩意,这是运用那些重要的“制造者”技能的一个简单方法。任何人在任何地方都能做到。换言之，资源不足的学校和社区应尽可能地利用现有资源，故答案为 B)。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["If you were like most children, you probably got upset when your mother called you by a sibling’s(兄弟姐妹的)name. How could she not know you? Did it mean she loved you less?","Probably not. According to the first research to tackle this topic head-on, misnaming the most familiar people in our life is a common cognitive (认知的)error that has to do with how our memories classify and store familiar names.","The study, published online in April in the journal Memory and Cognition, found that the “wrong” name is not random but is invariably fished out from the same relationship pond: children, siblings, friends. The study did not examine the possibility of deep psychological significance to the mistake, says psychologist David Rubin, “but it does tell us who’s in and who’s out of the group.”","The study also found that within that group, misnamings occurred where the names shared initial or internal sounds, like Jimmy and Joanie or John and Bob. Physical resemblance between people was not a factor. Nor was gender.","The researchers conducted five separate surveys of more than 1,700 people. Some of the surveys included only college students; others were done with a mixed-age population. Some asked subjects about incidents where someone close to them—family or friend—had called them by another person’s name. The other surveys asked about times when subjects had themselves called someone close to them by the wrong name. All the surveys found that people mixed up names within relationship groups such as grandchildren, friends and siblings but hardly ever crossed these boundaries.","In general, the study found that undergraduates were almost as likely as old people to make this mistake and men as likely as women. Older people and this mistake and men as likely as women. Older people and women made the mistake slightly more often, but that may be because grandparents have more grandchildren to mix up than parents have children. Also, mothers may call on their children more often than fathers, given traditional gender norms. There was no evidence that errors occurred more when the misnamer was frustrated, tired or angry."],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":"How might people often feel when they were misnamed?","options":["A) Unwanted.","B) Unhappy.","C) Confused.","D) Indifferent."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查“人们被叫错名字时的心理感受”，由when they were misnamed定位至首段(when your mother called you by a sibling's name)。","analysis":"【精析】A将③句疑问之意“是否爱得更少“偷换为肯定之意爱得更少”，然后再将“爱得更少”程度加深为“不爱”，从而捏造出“不被需要，多余”。C由②③句连续发问臆断出被叫错名字者“困惑:不知道到底是因为不认识还是因为爱得更少而被叫错”,而②句How could. .. not、③句Did it mean.. less实质均暗含被叫错名字者“失落、沮丧”的态度。D与被叫错名字者内心感受upset、心中疑惑How coul... Did it man..所传递的“(对名字被叫错之事)极为在乎”态度相悖。B)文首句指出多数孩子的一种普遍心理:在被妈妈唤错名字时不高兴，然后借助“you (代指读者，泛指任何人)与多数孩子的相似性(like) ”将这一- 心理投射到所有人身上，意即，被唤错名字时，人们通常都会不高兴，故B正确。Unhappy 义同upset。"},{"order":52,"question":"What did David Rubin’s research find about misnaming?","options":["A) It is related to the way our memories work.","B) It is a possible indicator of a faulty memory.","C) It occurs mostly between kids and their friends.","D) It often causes misunderstandings among people."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查戴维●鲁宾的研究发现，定位范围宽泛(由表ZJK特指的the first research, The study, The researchers可知第二至六段所述为同一研究)， 但结合试题命制顺序及后面几道题题干可推断本题实质性针对第二段提纲挈领的研究发现(该段总述研究发现，后续段落详述研究具体内容及结果)。","analysis":"【精析】B中faulty虽意同第二段②句中error,但却将具体指向“认知”偷换为“记忆”:文意实为“由于记忆的分类储存方法(如兄弟姊妹、子女、朋友)，人们容易发生叫错名字这个问题”，其属于认知问题(信息提取时出错)而非记忆问题(对人名的记忆并没出错)。C将第三段①句“被叫错的名字的常见来源:同一关系池(孩子、朋友、兄弟姐妹)”曲解为“叫错名字现象易发人群:孩子与其朋友之间”。D利用首段末两句隐藏文意“被叫错名字者常会感觉不被爱、不被认可”捏造而来，但并非研究发现。A)。第二段②句介绍研究发现:将最熟悉的人的名字叫错是一种常见认知错误，这与我们的记忆如何对熟悉的名字进行分类与储存有关;意即，叫错名字跟我们的记忆运作方式有关，A是对该句的高度概括，其中related to同义改写do with, the way our memories work概括how our memories classify and store familiar names。"},{"order":53,"question":"What is most likely the cause of misnaming?","options":["A) Similar personality traits.","B) Similar spellings of names.","C) Similar physical appearance.","D) Similar pronunciation of names."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查叫错名字的原因(cause of misnaming),可定位至第四段(misnamings occurred where…… a factor……)","analysis":"【精析】A由第三段首句“被叫错者通常属于同一个关系池:朋友、兄弟姐妹、子女”捏造而来,认为“属同一一个 关系池的人大多个性特征相似,但“同属关系池”≠“个性特征相似”。B将第四段首句“发音相似( shared. .. sounds) ”窜改为“拼写相似(similar spellings) ”。C与②句“外貌相似不是(导致名字叫错的)因素”相悖。D)。第四段首句指出:在一个关系池里，如果名字开头或中间发音相同则会出现叫错现象，如Jimmy和Joanie,或者John和Bob。可见，名字发音相似很可能是叫错名字的原因，D正确。"},{"order":54,"question":"What did the surveys of more than 1,700 subjects find about misnaming?","options":["A) It more often than not hurts relationships.","B) It hardly occurs across gender boundaries.","C) It is most frequently found in extended families.","D) It most often occurs within a relationship groups."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题题点为“针对1700多人的调查(结果)”，可由the surveys of more than 1,700 subjects定位至第五段首末句(surveys of more than 1700 people...All the surveys found...)","analysis":"【精析】A由首段现象“叫错名字让被叫错者不高兴”及全文复现词relationship杂糅捏造而来,但文中无据可依。E将末句中these boundaries具体所指boundaries ofrelationship groups 偷换为gender boundaries,而第四段末句明确指出“叫错名字与性别无关(即，会跨越性别界限)”。C由grandchildren 衍生出extended families(与核心家庭相对，指几代同堂的大家庭)，将文中个例“子孙辈名字(、朋友名字、兄弟姊妹名字等其他属于同一关系池内部的名字)容易搞混“窄化曲解为“叫错名字常见于大家庭中”。D)。第五段首句引出研究人员开展的调查:针对1700 多人展开了五项独立调查;末句指出调查结果:人们只将同一关系池内部(孙辈、朋友、兄弟姐妹)的人名搞错，几乎从未跨越过这些关系池的界限。可见，将名字搞混最常发生在一个关系群内部，D正确。"},{"order":55,"question":"Why do mothers misname their children more often than fathers?","options":["A) They suffer more frustrations.","B) They become worn out more often.","C) They communicate more with their children.","D) They generally take on more work at home."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查母亲比父亲更常叫错孩子名字的原因，可定位至第六段②③句( women... more often, mothers. . . more often than fathers)。","analysis":"【精析】 A中frustrations、B中worn out均源自末句，但该句句意实为“叫错名字的几率与叫错名字行为人是否感到沮丧、疲倦、愤怒无关”，选项做了反向干扰。D由③句traditional gender norms“传统性别规范”望文生义出“母亲(比父亲)承担更多家务”,但该词实际指向“母亲更多呼唤孩子”。C)。末段②③句指出:老人和女性叫错名字的频率略高，可能是因为祖父母比父母有更多的孙辈混淆，母亲比父亲更常召唤孩子。由此可见，母亲比父亲更常叫错孩子名字是因为母亲和孩子交流更多，常常召唤孩子。故C正确。"}]}]}
{"_id":"150083c56198ed41030d0d0e43469fdc","id":"2019060203","type":"CET4","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are.2 passages in this section.Each passage is followed by some questions or wnfinishedstatements. For each of them there are four choices marked A),B),C) and D). You should decide on thebest choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["According to the majority of Americans, women are every bit as capable of being good political leaders as men. The same can be said of their ability to dominate the corporate boardroom. And according to a new Pew Research Center survey on women and leadership, most Americans find women indistinguishable from men on key leadership traits such as intelligence and capacity for innovation, with many saying they’re stronger than men in terms of being passionate and organized leaders.","So why, then, are women in short supply at the top of government and business in the United States? According to the public, at least, it’s not that they lack toughness, management talent or proper skill sets.","It’s also not all about work-life balance. Although economic research and previous survey findings have shown that career interruptions related to motherhood may make it harder for women to advance in their careers and compete for top executive jobs, relatively few adults in the recent survey point to this as a key barrier for women seeking leadership roles. Only about one-in-five say women’s family responsibilities are a major reason why there aren’t more females in top leadership positions in business and politics.","Instead, topping the list of reasons, about four-in-ten Americans point to a double standard for women seeking to climb to the highest levels of either politics or business, where they have to do more than their male counterparts to prove themselves. Similar shares say the electorate(选民)and corporate America are just not ready to put more women in top leadership positions.","As a result, the public is divided about whether the imbalance in corporate America will change in the foreseeable future, even though women have made major advances in the workplace. While 53% believe men will continue to hold more top executive positions in business in the future, 44% say it’s only a matter of time before as many women are in top executive positions as men. Americans are less doubtful when it comes to politics: 73% expect to see a female president in their lifetime."],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":".What do most Americans think of women leaders according to a new Pew Research Center survey?","options":["A) They have to do more to distinguish themselves.","B) They have to strive harder to win their positions.","C) They are stronger than men in terms of willpower.","D) They are just as intelligent and innovative as men."],"answer":"D","location":"[定位]本题考查美国大众对女性领导看法的最新调查结果，根据题干关键词定位至第一段③句(a new Pew Research Center survey on women and leadership)。","analysis":"[解析]A、B皆利用第四段①句信息“因面临双重标准，女性必须做得更多才能证明自己(也包括获得现有职位)“干扰,但这是4成美国人的看法(aboutfour-in-tenAmericanspointt...，与题干所问“大多数美国人的看法”不符。C则将第一段③句许多人观点“女性比男性更有激情、更有条理”窜改为“意志力更强”。D句指出，大多数美国人认为，女性与男性不仅在才智、创新等领导力品质方面不相上下，甚至比男性更擅长担任激情而有条理的领导。D与前半句信息契合。"},{"order":47,"question":"What do we learn from previous survey findings about women seeking leadership roles?","options":["A) They have unconquerable difficulties on their way to success.","B) They are lacking in confidence when competing with men.","C) Their failures may have something to do with family duties.","D) Relatively few are hindered in their career advancement."],"answer":"C","location":"[定位]本题考查过往调查关于“寻求领导地位女性”的发现，定位至第三段②句( previous survey findings. . . women seeking leadership roles)。","analysis":"[解析]A将定位句中“生/养育致事业中断，可能更难发展晋升(maymakeitharder)”夸大为“困难克服不了(unconquerable) ”. B利用文中所述的“女性生理方面有劣势(为家庭不得不牺牲事业)”臆断出“女性在职场上因性别而自卑”，文中并未提及女性的心理。D将②句主句中的数据信息“很少受访者认为家庭是职场女性的大碍”偷换为直接结论“很少女性在职场受阻”，且文中为“最新调查”( recent survey),并非题干所问“此前调查”。C句指出，经济学研究和此前的调查发现表明，生养孩子导致工作中断，这可能让女性难以在事业上更进一步，因而无力竞争高级管理层职位。由此可知，女性无法获取高位跟家庭责任有一定的关系，C正确。"},{"order":48,"question":".What is the primary factor keeping women from taking top leadership positions according to the recent survey?","options":["A) Personality traits.","B) Family responsibilities.","C) Gender bias.","D) Lack of vacancies."],"answer":"C","location":"[定位]本题考查阻碍女性晋升顶层职位的主要原因。由题干关键信息primaryfactor定位至第四段①句( topping the list of reasons)。","analysis":"[解析]A项与首段③句“根据最新调查，女性和男性在关键性领导力品质方面不相上下，甚至比男性更有激情、更条理“相悖。B项对第三段③句family responsibilities are a majorreason断章取义，忽 略only about one-in-five (仅2成人这么认为)所暗含的“家庭责任并非主要原因”。D项将第四段②句“选民及企业没有做好准备让女性担任高位”臆断为“职业空缺太少”。第四段①句借“调查(四成美国人认为)”指出女性难登高位的首要原因:女性面临双重标准，她们必须比男性付出更多以证明自己。可见，阻碍女性担任顶层职位的主要原因是性别偏见，C项符合文意。"},{"order":49,"question":".What does the passage say about corporate America in the near future?","options":["A) More and more women will sit in the boardroom.","B) Gender imbalance in leadership is likely to change.","C) The public is undecided about whether women will make good leaders","D) People have opposing opinions as to whether it will have more women leaders."],"answer":"D","location":"[定位]本题考查美国企业界的未来情形。由题干关键信息corporateAmericainthenearfuture定位至末段①句( corporate America.. . in the foreseeable future)。","analysis":"[解析] A、B项利用②③句“女性与男性高管数量齐平只是时间问题”、“希望能有一位女性总统”干扰，但它们仅为(存在分歧的)公众当中一部分人的看法(44%、73%) ,并非题干所问“作者!文中所说”。C项将公众的分歧点由“是否有更多女性领袖出现”窜改为“女性能否成为优秀领袖”，且第一段即已指出公众毫不怀疑女性的领袖品质。末段①句指出，公众在“美国企业界领导层性别失衡是否会在可预见的未来发生改变“这一问题上产生了分歧( is divided about义同选项中have opposing opinions), “性别失衡的现状是否会改变”意即“是否会有更多女性领导者”，故D正确。"},{"order":50,"question":"What do most Americans expect to see soon on America’s political stage?","options":["A) A woman in the highest position of government.","B) More and more women actively engaged in politics.","C) A majority of women voting for a female president.","D) As many women in top government positions as men. "],"answer":"A","location":"[定位]本题考查美国人对美国政坛未来情形的预想。由题干关键信息America's political stage定位至末段③句( when it comes to politics)。","analysis":"[解析] B、C均利用定位句“预计能看到女总统上台”干扰，但“预计会有更多女性参与政治”属过度推断,“预计会有大部分女性投票支持”属主观臆测。D项将末段②句“44%美国人对未来商界的判断(as many women are in top executive positions as men) “偷换为”大部分美国人对未来政坛的判断( As many women in top government positions as men) ”。末段③句指出:美国人对未来政坛的预期分歧更小，73%的人认为在有生之年能看到女总统上台。可见，大部分美国人认为女性很快会出任政府最高职位，故A项正确。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["People have grown taller over the last century, with South Korean women shooting up by more than 20cm on average, and Iranian men gaining. 16.5cm. A global study looked at the average height of 18-year-olds in 200 countries 1914 and 2014.","The results reveal that while Swedes were the tallest people in the world in 1914, Dutch men have risen from 12th place to claim top spot with an average height of 182.5cm. Larvian women. Meanwhile, rose from 28th place in 1914 to become the tallest in the world a century later, with an average height of 169.8cm.","James Bentham, a co-author of the research from Imperial College, London, says the global trend is likely to be due primarily to improvements in nutrition and healthcare. “An individual’s genetics has a big influence on their height, but once you average over whole populations, genetics plays a less key role,” he added.","A little extra height brings a number of advantages, says Elio Riboli of Imperial College. “Being taller is associated with longer life expectancy,” he said. “This is largely due to a lower risk of dying of cardiovascular（心血管的）disease among taller people.”","But while height has increased around the world, the trend in many countries of north and sub-Saharan Africa causes concern, says Riboli. While height increased in Uganda and Niger during the early 20th century, the trend has reversed in recent years, with height decreasing among 18-year-olds.","“One reason for these decreases in height is the economic situation in the 1980s,” said Alexander Moradi of the Universith of Sussex. The nutritional and health crises that followed the policy of structural adjustment, he says, led to many children and teenagers failing to reach their full potential in terms of height.","Bentham believe the global rtend of increasing height has important implications. “How tall we are now is strongly influenced by the environment we grew up in,” he said. “If we give children the best possible start in life now, they will be healthier and more productive for decades to come.”"],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":" What does the global study tell us about people’s height in the last hundred years?","options":["A) There is a remarkable difference across continents.","B) There has been a marked increase in most countries.","C) The increase in people’s height has been quickening.","D) The increase in women’s height is bigger than in men’s."],"answer":"B","location":"[定位]本题就“全球性研究的结果”设题，根据题干关键词the global stud ytell us,in the last hundred years定位至第一- 、二段(over the last century. . . The results [of the study] revealthat. . . )。","analysis":"[解析] A项由首段South Korean、Iranian (属亚洲)增高、第二段Dutch、Latvian ()欧洲)增高、第五段Africa (非洲)先增后降的具体叙述中望文生义出“各大洲存在显着异”,而研究针对的是“国家( countries)”而非“洲( continents)”。C 项将全文关键让increasing height、height has increased1 “ 身高增长”偷换为increase ( in height) has be quickeningl“身高增速一直 在加快“D项由首两段”韩国女性身高增幅大于伊朗男性”及“时脱维亚女性身高排名跃升位次多于荷兰男性捏造而来.但该研究只对男性、女性身高变化别进行纵向研究，并未横向比较男女性身高增幅。第一段开篇指出: -百年来人们身高有所增长，其中韩国女性、伊朗男性身高增长幅分别高达20cm以上、16.5cm;随后引出这项针对“1914-2014年间200个国家平均身高”全球性研究;第二段直接介绍该研究的结果:荷兰男性和拉脱维亚女性身高大幅增长、分从1914年的第12位、第28位- -跃瑞典荣登榜首;最后再结合第三段首句中特定指示名theglobaltrend的语用功能可推知，首两段所述身高大幅增长属于一种全球趋势,故B正确补充:结合第五六段信息“非洲北部及撒哈拉以南地区身高下降趋势”可进一步敲定，这种全球趋势发生在除非洲部分国家以外的其它大多数国家。"},{"order":52,"question":"What does James Bentham say about genetics in the increase of people’s height?","options":["A) It counts less than generally thought.","B) It outweighs nutrition and healthcare.","C) It impacts more on an individual than on population.","D) It plays a more significant role in females than in males."],"answer":"C","location":"[定位]本题考查詹姆斯本瑟姆对“遗传基因之于身高增长的作用”的看法，由题干关键词James Bentham say和genetics 定位至第三段。","analysis":"[解析] A项根据碎片信息“没那么重要(plays a less key role)”断章取义，而忽视其前述条件:当涉及人口整体的平均身高时。B项与首句Bentham观点“营养和医疗保健的改善很可能是人口身高增长的主要原因“相悖。D项将“对个体影响大于对群体影响”偷换为“对女性影响大于对男性影响”.而Bentham并未谈及遗传基因对男女身高的影响。第三段②句指出本瑟姆观点:遗传基因对个体身高影响很大,但计量平均身高时，遗传基因对身高的作用就不那么重要了。故C正确。"},{"order":53,"question":" What does Elio Riboli say about taller people?","options":["A) They tend to live longer.","B) They enjoy an easier life.","C) They generally risk fewer fatal diseases.","D) They have greater expectations in life."],"answer":"A","location":"[定位]本题就埃利奧●里博利对“高个人群”的看法设题，由题干关键词ElioRibolisay和taller people定位至第四段。","analysis":"[解析] B项由“高个子死于心血管疾病的风险较小，寿命较长”过度推断出“高个子鲜受疾病苦痛的纠缠、因而日子过得更轻松”。C项错误同B项，将“患心血管疾病的风险较小”夸大为“患致命疾病的风险较低”。D项利用个别难词longer life expectancy 设置干扰，但life expectancy此处为固定用法，意为“预期寿命”，并非“生活期望”。第四段①句中里博利指出:较高的身高与较长的寿命有关，A中live longer同义改写原文longer life expectancy,,"},{"order":54,"question":"What do we learn about 18-year-olds in Uganda and Niger?","options":["A) They grow up slower than their peers in other countries.","B) They are actually shorter than their earlier generations.","C) They find it hard to bring their potential into full play.","D) They have experienced many changes of government"],"answer":"B","location":"[定位]本题问及“乌干达和尼日尔18岁群体”的相关信息根据题干关键词Uganda and Niger定位至第五段末句。","analysis":"[解析]A项将段中今昔对比“20世纪初增长VS近年来逆转”偷换为横向对比“比其他国家同龄人慢”。C项利用第六段末句碎片信息failing to reach their full potential干扰，却忽略其后限定语in terms of height“身高方面的(潜能)”，选项将其夸大为“个人全部潜能”。D项利用当前非洲政治形势“多国政权更迭频繁”这一常识干扰。B项指出:近年来，乌干达和尼日尔人身高变化趋势出现逆转，由20世纪初的增长转变为下降。由此可知，他们现在实 际上要比前几代人更矮，B正确。"},{"order":55,"question":" What does James Bentham suggest we do?","options":["A) Watch closely the global trend in children’s development.","B) Make sure that our children grow up to their full height.","C) Try every means possible to improve our environment.","D) Ensure our children grow up in an ideal environment."],"answer":"D","location":"[定位]本题就“詹姆斯●本瑟姆的建议”设题，根据题干关键词JamesBentham及本题位置定位至末段。","analysis":"[解析] A项利用末段碎片信息the global trend'children和grew up糅杂干扰，但文中未有提及“儿童发展的全球趋势”。B项由第六段末句“儿童和青少年无法充分发挥其身高潜能”主观推断Bentham建议“确保孩子充分发挥身高潜能”，但Bentham的关注点在于“孩子的成长环境(饮食营养及医疗设施等)对身高的影响，进而对个人健康、发展成就的影响”。C项将文中the environment we grew up in “成长环境”过度泛化为our environment“ 人类环境”。末段引述本瑟姆之言指出，我们的身高很大程度上受到成长环境的影响.如果我们给孩子一个最好的人生开端，即尽可能给他们提供一一个理想的成长环境，那将对孩子今后的几十年人生大有帮助，D正确。"}]}]}
{"_id":"150083c56198ed41030d0d0f491c47fe","id":"2019060303","type":"CET4","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are 2 passages in this section.Each passage is followed by some questions or wnfinishedstatements. For each of them there are four choices marked A),B),C) and D). You should decide on thebest choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["Most kids grow up learning they cannot draw on the walls. But it might be time to unlearn that training—this summer, group of culture addicts, artists and community organizers are inviting New Yorkers to write all over the walls of an old house on Governor’s Island.","The project is called Writing On It All, and it’s a participatory writing project and artistic experiment that has happened on Governor’s Island every summer since 2013.","“Most of the participants are people who are just walking by or are on the island for other reasons, or they just kind of happen to be there,” Alexandra Chasin, artistic director of Writing On It All, tells Smithsonian.com.","The 2016 season runs through June 26 and features sessions facilitated by everyone from dancers to domestic workers. Each session has a theme, and participants are given a variety of materials and prompts and asked to cover surfaces with their thoughts and art. This year, the programs range from one that turns the house into a collaborative essay to one that explores the meaning of exile.","Governor’s Island is a national historic landmark district long used for military purposes. Now known as “New York’s shared space for art and play,” the island, which lies between Manhattan and Brooklyn in Upper New York Bay, is closed to cars but open to summer tourists who flck for festivals, picnics, adventures, as well as these “legal graffiti(涂鸦)” Sessions.","The notes and art scribbled(涂画) on the walls are an experiment in self-expression. So far, participants have ranged in age from 2 to 85. Though Chasin says the focus of the work is on the activity of writing, rather than the text that ends up getting written, some of the work that comes out of the sessions has stuck with her.","“One of the sessions that moved me the most was state violence on black women and black girls,” says Chasin, explaining that in one room, people wrote down the names of those killed because of it. “People do beautiful work and leave beautiful messages.”"],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"What does the project Writing On It All invite people to do?","options":["A) Unlearn their training in drawing.","B) Participate in a state graffiti show.","C) Cover the walls of an old house with graffiti.","D) Exhibit their artistic creations in an old house."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查项目细节信息:邀请人们参加的具体活动内容。由题干关键信息 theproject Writing On It All 及 invite people to do 可定位至首两段（inviting New Yorkers to. ..The project is called Writing On It All。","analysis":"【解析】A源自首段②句unlearn that training，但 that training 指代“教育孩子不能在墙上画画”,与选项中training in drawing(绘画训练)意思完全不同B利用首两段的participatory,write all over the walls、New Yorkers ...Governor(可能联想到纽约州)”等信息主观臆测“该项目邀请人们参加一场纽约州举办的涂鸦展”，但由首段②句可知该项目并非展览（是参与涂鸦)。D将首段②句的邀约活动由“一座老房子的墙上涂鸦( write all over the walls of an oldhouse)”窜改为“在一座老房子里展览艺术作品。首段②句提到“纽约市民受邀到总督岛一座老房子的墙上尽情涂写”，随后第二段①句则指出“该项目名为Writing On It All”。综合即:Writing On It All项目邀请人们在一座老房子的墙上进行涂鸦( write all over the walls义同cover the walls. . . with graffiti）,C正确。"},{"order":47,"question":"What do we learn about the participants in the project?","options":["A) What do we learn about the participants in the project?","B) They are graffiti enthusiasts.","C) They are graffiti enthusiasts.","D) They are mostly passers-by."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查“项目参与者”相关内容。题干关键词participants首现于第三段。","analysis":"【解析】A将首段②句的“项目组织者/邀约发出者( culture addicts...)”偷换为“项目参与者”.B、C分别由首两段提到的项目性质“涂鸦活动”、“涂写项目和艺术实验( writing projectand artistic experiment)”,主观臆测项目参与者为“涂鸦爱好者”、“作家和艺术家（ writers andartists)”,并非文中信息。第三段引语内介绍:大多数参与者都是刚好路过(just walking by)或因其他原因来到岛上( for other reasons)，或者说，他们只是刚好碰巧在这里( happen to bethere）,可见D正确。"},{"order":48,"question":"What did the project participants do during the 2016 season?","options":["A) They were free to scribble on the walls whatever came to their mind.","B) They expressed their thoughts in graffiti on the theme of each session.","C) They learned the techniques of collaborative writing.","D) They were required to cooperate with other creators."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查“2016活动季中项目参与者的行动”。由题干关键词the 2016 season定位至第四段。","analysis":"【解析】A中“完全随意涂画”与第四段②句“每次活动都有一个主题(围绕主题涂画)“不符。C、D均利用第四段③句collaborative干扰，但此句是在例举其中一个主题活动“把房子变成一篇通力合作的漫笔，而非说明活动过程中参与者“学会了合作涂写的技巧”或“被要求与其他创作者合作”。第四段指出,2016活动季主打全民共同推进的活动，每个活动都有一个主题，要求参与者运用自己的想法与技艺来涂抹墙面,B符合文意,expressed their thoughts ingraffiti 与cover surfaces with their thoughts and art同义。"},{"order":49,"question":" What kind of place is Governor’s Island?","options":["A) It is a historic site that attracts tourists and artists.","B) It is an area now accessible only to tourist vehicles.","C) It is a place in Upper New York Bay formerly used for exiles.","D) It is an open area for tourists to enjoy themselves year round."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题询问“总督岛的相关信息”，直接定位至第五段(Governor's Island. . . )。","analysis":"【解析】B与第五段②句“总督岛禁止车辆进入(closed to cars)”相悖。C虽然准确描述了总督岛的地理位置(位于上纽约湾)，但“曾用于流放地(formerly used for exiles)”则是用第四段exile捏造的干扰（文中用于指一个活动主题为“探索流亡的意义”，与总督岛的用途完全无关)。D无视第五段②句“总督岛夏季对游客开放（ open to summer tourists)”,将开放时间扩大为“全年”。本段①句指出，总督岛是一个历史性地标区。②句指出，总督岛现在成了纽约市的“艺术娱乐共享空间”，每年夏天都能吸引大量游客来此参加各类活动，A是对这些信息的概括。"},{"order":50,"question":"What does Chasin say about the project?","options":["A) It just focused on the sufferings of black females.","B) It helped expand the influence of graffiti art.","C) It has started the career of many creative artists.","D) It has created some meaningful artistic works."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题询问查辛对“尽情涂写”项目的看法，根据人名(Chasin）及出题顺序规律定位至第六、七段。","analysis":"【解析】A杂糅第六段个别词汇 focus 与第七段所述活动“关注黑人女性遭遇”，但第七段所述活动仅是项目一部分，并非唯一关注点(just focused on错误)。B中“涂鸦艺术”虽复现第五段②句提到的“合法涂鸦活动”，但“扩大影响”纯属捏造。C所说“该项目开创艺术家的职业生涯”与第三段“该项目参与者大多是过路人，来自各行各业”相悖。第六段③句指出，查辛说虽然项目重点在于涂写活动本身，但还是有些作品令她难以忘怀。第七段进而举例最另其感动的作品“在房间里写下因国家暴力惨遭杀害的黑人女性姓名”。可见查辛认为这个项目创造了一些有意义的艺术作品，D正确。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["Online programs to fight depression are already commercially available. While they sound efficient and cost-saving, a recent study reports that they are not effective, primarily because depressed patients are not likely to engage with them or stick with them.","The study looked at computer-assisted cognitive(认知的) behavioral therapy(CBT) and found that it was no more effective in treating depression than the usual care patients receive from a primary care doctor.","Traditional CBT is considered an effective form of talk therapy for depression, helping people challenge negative thoughts and change the way they think in order to change their mood and behaviors. However, online CBT programs have been gaining popularity, with the attraction of providing low-cost help wherever someone has access to a computer.","A team of researchers from the University of Y ork conducted a randomized(随机的) control trial with 691 depressed patients from 83 physician practices across England. The patients were split into three groups: one group received only usual care from a physician while the other two groups received usual care from a physician plus one of two computerized CBT programs. Participants were balanced across the three groups for age, sex, educational background, severity and duration of depression, and use of antidepressants(抗抑郁药).","After four months, the patients using the computerized CBT programs had no improvement in depression levels over the patients who were only getting usual care from their doctors.","“It’s an important, cautionary note that we shouldn’t get too carried away with the idea that a computer system can replace doctors and therapists,” says Christopher Dowrick, a professor of primary medical care at the University of Liverpool. “We do still need the human touch or the human interaction, particularly when people are depressed.”","Being depressed can mean feeling “lost in your own small, negative, dark world,” Dowrick says. Having a person, instead of a computer, reach out to you is particularly important in combating that sense of isolation. “When you’re emotionally vulnerable, you’re even more in need of a caring human being ,” he says."],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":"What does the recent study say about online CBT programs?","options":["A)  Patients may not be able to carry them through for effective cure.","B)  Patients cannot engage with them without the use of a computer.","C)  They can save patients trouble visiting physicians.","D)  They have been well received by a lot of patients."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查“新近研究发现”，可由the recent study定位至首段②句( a recent studyreports...>","analysis":"【解析】B）将首段not. . . engage with them与第三段wherever someone has access to acomputer杂糅而来，但这是有关在线CBT程序的事实，而非研究发现。C)结合首段efficientand cost-saving 及常识“线下看医生很麻烦”推测而来。D则由第三段gaining popularity 捏造而来，但“越来越受欢迎+受到好评/反响良好”，且指向在线CBT程序现状，并非研究发现。定位句指出，尽管抗抑郁症在线程序(they回指Online programs to fight depression,与 onlineCBT programs同指）听起来既高效又划算，但最近一项研究指出，这些疗法无效，因为抑郁症患者不大可能充分使用或坚持使用这些程序，可见A）正确，carry them through同义改写原文stick with them。"},{"order":52,"question":"What has made online CBT programs increasingly popular?","options":["A) Their effectiveness in combating depression.","B) The low efficiency of traditional talk therapy.","C) Their easy and inexpensive access by patients.","D) The recommendation by primary care doctors."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查“在线CBT程序受欢迎的原因”,可由online CBT programs increasinglypopular定位至第三段②句(online CBT programs. . . gaining popularity...)。","analysis":"【解析】A)利用popularity设障，将“流行性的原因”狭隘理解为“有效性的魅力”，但与首段②句not effective、第二段no more effective、第五段no improvement所述研究发现“在线CBT程序在对抗抑郁症方面无效”相悖。B)由首段“在线CET程序听起来高效”反向推出“传统谈话疗法(传统线下CET)效率低下”，但第三段首句指出谈话疗法是一种有效的疗法(aneffective form of talk therapy)。D)由第二段末词a primary care doctor捏造而来，但文中并未提及初级保健医师“推荐”在线CET程序。定位句指出在线CBT程序越来越受欢迎的原因:它们能够给任何一位能够上网的人(此处指向患者)提供低价治疗。故C正确，其中 easyaccess对应 wherever someone has access to a computer, inexpensive对应 low-cost。"},{"order":53,"question":"What is the major finding by researchers at the University of York?","options":["A) Online CBT programs are no more effective than regular care from physicians.","B) The process of treating depression is often more complicated than anticipated.","C) The combination of traditional CBT and computerized CBT is most effective.","D) Depression is a mental condition which is to be treated with extreme caution."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查“约克大学研究人员的研究发现”，可由finding by researchers at theUniversity of York定位至第四、五段(researchers from the University of York. . . , After fourmonths)。","analysis":"第五段介绍试验结果:接受“计算机化CBT +医师常规治疗”的患者与仅接受常规治疗的患者相比，抑郁程度并未改善，可见计算机化CBT并未起作用。再结合第二段所述研究发现“计算机辅助CBT和初级保健师所提供的常规治疗一样都没有效果”可确定A正确。"},{"order":54,"question":"What is Professor Dowrick’s advice concerning online CBT programs?","options":["A) They should not be neglected in primary care.","B) Their effectiveness should not be overestimated.","C) They should be used by strictly following instructions.","D) Their use should be encouraged by doctors and therapists."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查“多利克教授对在线CBT程序的建议”,可由Professor Dowrick's advice定位至第六段( we shouldn't. . . says Christopher Dowrick)。","analysis":"【解析】A)、D)均由首句can replace doctors and therapists 断章取义而来，却忽略其前cautionary note、shouldn't所传递出的否定之意。C)由首句中 cautionary. . . shouldn't get toocarried away中 carry望文生义出具体操作手法 (be used相当于be carried out)，从而捏造出should. . . strictly following instructions,但 get too carried away为固定表达“不要太过相信/太过痴迷”。第六段多利克教授警示我们:不应过度相信‘计算机系统可以取代医生和治疗师'，这一想法，人们抑郁时仍然需要人际接触或互动。可见，多利克教授建议人们不应高估计算机系统/在线CET程序的有效性。B正确。"},{"order":55,"question":"What is more important to an emotionally vulnerable person?","options":["A) A positive state of mind.","B) Appropriate medication.","C) Timely encouragement.","D) Human interaction."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查“情感脆弱者所需之物”，可由emotionally vulnerable定位至文末句( emotionally vulnerable)。","analysis":"【解析】A)由末段首句“抑郁症患者消极”(以及第三段首句中“消极思想”)及常识“需要积极心态”捏造而来;B)由第四段末句“使用抗抑郁药”及常识“需药物治疗”捏造而来; C)由文末句“体贴之人”及常识“需要给予鼓励”捏造而来;但均与文意不符。定位句指出，当你情感脆弱时，你更需要一个温暖体贴、有血有肉的人( a caring human being);结合上句内容“让一个人而不是一台电脑(a person，instead of a computer〉来帮助抑郁之人克服孤独感尤为重要”可知，作者意在强调“人一人”互动的重要性优于“人一机”互动，故D正确。此外，末段实为第六段末句的解释说明，即，意在说明“我们的确仍然需要人际接触/互动”，可借以印证。"}]}]}
{"_id":"150083c56198ed41030d0d101812dce1","id":"2019060103","type":"CET6","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are 2 passages in this section.Each passage is followed by some questions or wnfinishedstatements. For each of them there are four choices marked A),B),C) and D). You should decide on thebest choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["Professor Stephen Hawking has warned that the creation of powerful artificial intelligence (AI) will be “either the best, or the worst thing, ever to happen to humanity”, and praised the creation of an academic institute dedicated to researching the future of intelligence as “ crucial to the future of our civilisation and our species”.","Hawking was speaking at the opening of the Leverhulme Centre for the Future of Intelligence (LCFI) at Cambridge University, a multi-disciplinary institute that will attempt to tackle some of the open-ended questions raised by the rapid pace of development in AI research. “We spend a great deal of time study in history,” Hawking said, “which, let’s face it, is mostly the history of stupidity. So it’s a welcome change that people are studying instead the future of intelligence.”","While the world-renowned physicist has often been cautious about AI, raising concerns that humanity could be the architect of its own destruction if it creates a super-intelligence with a will of its own, he was also quick to highlight the positives that AI research can bring. “The potential benefits of creating intelligence are huge,” he said. “We cannot predict what we might achieve when our own minds are amplified by AI. Perhaps with the tools of this new technological revolution, we will be able to undo some of the damage done to the natural world by the last one —industrialisation. And surely we will aim to finally eradicate disease and poverty. And every aspect of our lives will be transformed. In short, success in creating AI could be the biggest event in the history of our civilisation.”","Huw Price, the centre’s academic director and the Bertrand Russell professor of philosophy at Cambridge University, where Hawking is also an academic, said that the centre came about partially as a result of the university’s Centre for Existential Risk. That institute examined a wider range of potential problems for humanity, while the LCFI has a narrow focus.","AI pioneer Margaret Boden, professor of cognitive science at the University of Sussex, praised the progress of such discussions. As recently as 2009, she said, the topic wasn’t taken seriously, even among AI researchers. “AI is hugely exciting,” she said, “but it has limitations, which present grave dangers given uncritical use.”","The academic community is not alone in warning about the potential dangers of AI as well as the potential benefits. A number of pioneers from the technology industry, most famously the entrepreneur Elon Musk, have also expressed their concerns about the damage that a super-intelligent AI could do to humanity."],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"What did Stephen Hawking think of artificial intelligence?","options":["A) It would be vital to the progress of human civilisation.","B) It might be a blessing or a disaster in the making.","C) It might present challenges as well as opportunities.","D) It would be a significant expansion of human intelligence."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查霍金对AI的看法。由Hawking , artificial intelligence定位至第一段(Stephen Hawking... Al will be...)。","analysis":"【精析】首段指出霍金警告“AI将会是人类历史最好的事,抑或是最糟的事”,B符合此意, in the making(在发展中,在形成中)对应文中will be(尚未出现) ， a blessing or a disaster对应文中either the best,or the worst thing。"},{"order":47,"question":"47. What did Hawking say about the creation of the LCFI?","options":["A) It would accelerate the progress of AI research.","B) It would mark a step forward in the AI industry.","C) It was extremely important to the destiny of humankind.","D) It was an achievement of multi-disciplinary collaboration."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查霍金对成立LCFI的看法。由Hawking ,LCFI定位至第一、二段(Hawking ...the creation of an academic institute.. .LCFI)。","analysis":"【精析】首段霍金赞扬“创建一个致力于研究未来智能的学术机构(即LCFI)”道:这对人类文明和人类物种的未来至关重要。第二段进一步指出,LCFI致力于研究智能的未来,这是一个可喜的变化,可见C正确体现霍金观点。"},{"order":48,"question":"What did Hawking say was a welcome change in AI research?","options":["A) The shift of research focus from the past to the future.","B) The shift of research from theory to implementation.","C) The greater emphasis on the negative impact of AI.","D) The increasing awareness of mankind’s past stupidity."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查“霍金对AI研究的看法”,由 a welcome change in AI research定位至第二段末。","analysis":"【精析】第二段末两句中霍金指出,我们花了大量时间研究历史,但大部分历史是愚蠢的。所以人们现在转而研究智能的未来是一个可喜的转变﹐可见A是对霍金观点的正确概括。"},{"order":49,"question":"What concerns did Hawking raise about AI?","options":["A) It may exceed human intelligence sooner or later.","B) It may ultimately over-amplify the human mind.","C) Super-intelligence may cause its own destruction.","D) Super-intelligence may eventually ruin mankind."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查霍金对AI的担忧。由题干关键词raise...concerns .Hawking.AI定位至第三段①句。","analysis":"【精析】第三段①句说明霍金的担忧“人类倘若创造出具有自身意志的超级智能，很可能会缔造。自己的毁灭”,D符合此信息, ruin mankind对应humanity... its own destruction。"},{"order":50,"question":"What do we learn about some entrepreneurs from the technology industry?","options":["A) They are much influenced by the academic community.","B) They are most likely to benefit from AI development.","C) They share the same concerns about AI as academics.","D) They believe they can keep AI under human control."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查“科技界企业家的相关信息”。由题干关键词entrepreneurs, technology industry定位至末段。","analysis":"【精析】末段指出:并非只有学术界在告诫人们AI的潜在威胁及益处,科技行业的一些先驱人物(包括知名企业家埃隆·马斯克)也已对超级智能AI的潜在风险表达了担忧。C符合此意。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["The market for products designed specifically for older adults could reach $30 billion by next year, and startups (初创公司) want in on the action. What they sometimes lack is feedback from the people who they hope will use their products. So Brookdale, the country’s largest owner of retirement communities, has been inviting a few select entrepreneurs just to move in for a few days, show off their products and hear what the residents have to say.","That’s what brought Dayle Rodriguez, 28, all the way from England to the dining room of Brookdale South Bay in Torrance, California. Rodriguez is the community and marketing manager for a company called Sentab. The startup’s product, SentabTV, enables older adults who may not be comfortable with computers to access email, video chat and social media using just their televisions and a remote control.","“It’s nothing new, it’s nothing too complicated and it’s natural because lots of people haveTV remotes,” says Rodriguez.","But none of that is the topic of conversation in the Brookdale dining room. Instead, Rodriguez solicits residents’ advice on what he should get on his cheeseburger and how he should spend the afternoon. Playing cards was on the agenda, as well as learning to play mahjong (麻将).","Rodriguez says it’s important that residents here don’t feel like he’s selling them something. “I’ve had more feedback in a passive approach,” he says. “Playing pool, playing cards, having dinner, having lunch,” all work better “than going through a survey of questions. When they get to know me and to trust me, knowing for sure I’m not selling them something—there’ll be more honest feedback from them.”","Rodriguez is just the seventh entrepreneur to move into one of Brookdale’s 1,100 senior living communities. Other new products in the program have included a kind of full-body blow dryer and specially designed clothing that allows people with disabilities to dress and undress themselves.","Mary Lou Busch, 93, agreed to try the Sentab system. She tells Rodriguez that it might be good for someone, but not for her. “I have the computer and FaceTime, which I talk with my family on, ”she explains. She also has an iPad and a smartphone. “So I do pretty much everything I need to do.”","To be fair, if Rodriguez had wanted feedback from some more technophobic (害怕技术的) seniors, he might have ended up in the wrong Brookdale community. This one is located in the heart of Southern California’s aerospace corridor. Many residents have backgrounds in engineering, business and academic circles.","But Rodriguez says he’s still learning something important by moving into this Brookdale community: “People are more tech-proficient than we thought.”","And besides, where else would he learn to play mahjong?"],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":"What does the passage say about the startups?","options":["A) They never lose time in upgrading products for seniors.","B) They want to have a share of the seniors’ goods market.","C) They invite seniors to their companies to try their products.","D) They try to profit from promoting digital products to seniors."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查初创公司的相关事实细节,根据题干关键词startups定位至第一段①②句(startups want...What they sometimes lack is...)。","analysis":"【精析】文首句指出,老年人用品市场价值巨大,初创公司也想参与其中分杯羹(want in on the action),故B正确。"},{"order":52,"question":"Some entrepreneurs have been invited to Brookdale to","options":["A) have an interview with potential customers","B) conduct a survey of retirement communities","C) collect residents’ feedback on their products","D) show senior residents how to use IT products"],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题询问Brookdale邀请创业家去做的事情,根据题干关键词entrepreneurs和Brookdale定位至第一段③句(Brookdale...entrepreneurs)。","analysis":"【精析】定位句指出, Brookdale邀请少数创业家入住老年社区,向住户展示产品并聆听他们的意见,亦即收集产品反馈,C正确。"},{"order":53,"question":"What do we know about SentabTV?","options":["A) It is a TV program catering to the interest of the elderly.","B) It is a digital TV which enjoys popularity among seniors.","C) It is a TV specially designed for seniors to view programs.","D) It is a communication system via TV instead of a computer."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查SentabTV相关事实,定位至第二段③句(SentabTV，enables...)。","analysis":"【精析】定位句指出,SentabTV让不习惯用电脑的老年人用电视和遥控器就能收发电邮,视频聊天、访问社交媒体,意即通过电视而非电脑来与别人交流/通信,故D正确。"},{"order":54,"question":"54. What does Rodriguez say is important in promoting products?","options":["A) Winning trust from prospective customers.","B) Knowing the likes and dislikes of customers.","C) Demonstrating their superiority on the spot.","D) Responding promptly to customer feedback."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查罗德里格斯眼中产品推广的要点,根据人名Rodriguez和关键词important定位至第五段①句(Rodriguez says it's important that...)。","analysis":"【精析】定位句指出,罗德里格斯认为“不让住户觉得自己在推销很重要”。本段接着援引他的说法指出,通过打桌球、玩纸牌等方式接触老年住户,让他们了解并相信自己,知道自己不是在推销,这样就能获得更多中肯的意见。因此要点在于取得顾客信任,A正确。"},{"order":55,"question":"What do we learn about the seniors in the Brookdale community?","options":["A) Most of them are interested in using the Sentab.","B) They are quite at ease with high-tech products.","C) They have much in common with seniors elsewhere.","D) Most of them enjoy a longer life than average people."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查文中涉及的 Brookdale(南湾)社区老年住户的情况,定位至第九段( seniors...in the wrong Brookdale community...This one is...Many residents...)。","analysis":"【精析】第九段①句首先指出,罗德里格斯来到的Brookdale南湾社区的老年住户并不害怕技术(technophobic)。②③句进而解释:南湾社区坐落于南加州航空航天密集区中心地带,住户大多有工程界、商界、学术界背景。意即,他们懂高科技技术,对高科技产品运用自如。B正确。"}]}]}
{"_id":"150083c56198ed41030d0d110b9d77b0","id":"2019060203","type":"CET6","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are 2 passages in this section. Each passage is followed by some questions or unfinished statements. For each of them there are four choices marked A), B), C) and D). You should decide on the best choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["Effective Friday, Screen Actors Guild-American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (SAG-AFTRA) has declared a strike against 11 video game publishers over games that went into production after Feb. 17, 2015. The companies include some of the heavyweights of the industry, like Electronic Arts Productions, Insomniac Games, Activision and Disney.","The strike comes in light of an unsuccessful 19 months of negotiations after the existing labor contract known as the Interactive Media Agreement expired in late 2014. overall, the strike is an effort to provide more secondary compensation along with other concerns, such as transparency upon hiring talent and on-set (制作中) safety precautions.","The video gaming industry has ballooned in recent years. The Los Angeles Times reports that the industry is in the midst of an intense increase in cash flow. In 2015, gaming produced $23.5 billion in domestic revenue.","But SAG-AFTRA says voice actors don’t receive residuals (追加酬金) for their gaming work. Instead, they receive a fixed rate, which is typically about $825 for a standard four-hour vocal session. So the voice actors are pushing for the idea of secondary compensation—a performance bonus every time a game sells 2 million copies or downloads, or reaches 2 million subscribers, with a cap at 8 million.","“It’s a very small number of games that would trigger this secondary compensation issue,”said voice actor Crispin Freeman, who’s a member of the union’s negotiating committee. “This is an important aspect of what it means to be a freelance (从事自由职业的) performer, who isn’t regularly employed every single day working on projects.”","Another major complaint from the actors is the secrecy of the industry. “I can’t imagine if there’s any other acting job in the world where you don’t know what show you’re in, when you’re hired,” says voice actor Keythe Farley, who chairs the SAG-AFTRA negotiating committee.","“And yet that happens every day in the video game world,” Farley told reporters during a press conference Friday. “I was a main character in Fallout 4, a character by the name of Kellogg, and I never knew that I was doing vocal recording for that game throughout the year and a half.”","Scott Witlin, the lawyer representing the video game companies, says voice actors “represent less than one tenth of 1 percent of the work that goes into making a video game.” So “even though they’re the top craftsmen in their field,” Witlin says, “if we pay them under a vastly different system than the people who do the 99.9 percent of the work, that’s going to create far more problems for the video game companies.”"],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"Why did SAG-AFTRA declare a strike against some video game publishers?","options":["A) The labor contract between them had been violated.","B) Its appeal to renegotiate the contract had been rejected.","C) It had been cheated repeatedly in the 19 months of talks.","D) The negotiations between them had broken down."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查SAG-AFTRA罢工的原因,可定位至第二段首句(The strike comes in light of...)。","analysis":"【精析】第二段首句指出,2014年底现行劳工合同到期,而后双方持续了19个月的谈判,最后谈判失败触发了此次罢工。可见SAG-AFTRA宣布罢工的原因是谈判失败,D正确。"},{"order":47,"question":"What do we learn from the passage about the video gaming industry?","options":["A) It has reaped huge profits in recent years.","B) It has become more open and transparent.","C) It has attracted many famous voice actors.","D) It has invested a lot in its domestic market."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查电子游戏产业(the video gaming industry)相关信息,可定位至第三段(The video gaming industry. ..the industry. . .gaming)。","analysis":"【精析】第三段指出,电子游戏业近年来迅速壮大,现金流猛增,2015年创造了巨额国内收入,可知该行业收益巨大,A正确。"},{"order":48,"question":"What are the voice actors demanding?","options":["A) More regular employment.","B) A non-discriminatory contract.","C) Extra pay based on sales revenues.","D) A limit on the maximum work hours."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查配音演员的要求,可定位至第四段②句(the voice actors are pushing for.. . )。","analysis":"【精析】第四段②句指出,配音演员们在努力争取二次付酬,即每款游戏达到一定销售额时(200万份销售量/下载量/用户),配音演员可获得绩效奖金(a performance bonus)。即,配音演员要求根据销售额支付额外工资,C正确。"},{"order":49,"question":"What does Keythe Farley say about voice actors?","options":["A) They are kept in the dark about many details of their job.","B) They are discriminated against in the gaming industry.","C) They are not paid on a regular basis.","D) They are not employed full-time."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查Keythe Farley 谈及的内容，可定位至第六、七段(... says voice actor KeytheFarley. . . ;...Farley told reporters.. .)。","analysis":"【精析】第六段Keythe Farley提出,在电子游戏行业里,配音演员不知道自己在出演什么,也不知道自己什么时候被录用;第七段 Farley讲述亲身经历“工作了一年半都不知道自己在为哪款游戏配音”。可见他提出配音演员对许多工作细节一无所知,A正确。"},{"order":50,"question":"What is the argument of lawyer Scott Witlin?","options":["A) Voice actors should have a pay raise if they prove to be top craftsmen.","B) Changing the pay system would cause the industry more problems.","C) Voice actors are mere craftsmen, not professional performers.","D) Paying voice actors on an hourly basis is in line with the law."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查Scott Witlin律师的观点,定位至末段(Scott Witlin，the lawyer.. . says.. .)。","analysis":"【精析】末段Scott Witlin 提出,对丁电丁游戏刺I令从内子游o司带夹重多问题,可见之一,如果对其采用与那些做了99.9%工作的人不同的薪酬体系,会给电子游戏公司带来更多问题,可见Scott Witlin认为改变薪酬体系会给电子游戏业带来更多问题，B正确。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["Officials at the White House announced a new space policy focused on managing the increasing number of satellites that companies and governments are launching into space. Space Policy Directive-3 lays out general guidelines for the United States to mitigate (缓解) the effects of space debris and track and manage traffic in space.","This policy sets the stage for the Department of Commerce to take over the management of traffic in space. The department will make sure that newly launched satellites don’t use radio frequencies that would interfere with existing satellites, and schedule when such new satellites can be launched. This only applies to American space activities, but the hope is that it will help standardize a set of norms in the dawning commercial spaceflight industry throughout the world.","Space, especially the space directly around our planet, is getting more crowded as more governments and companies launch satellites. One impetus for the policy is that companies are already starting to build massive constellations ( 星 座 ), comprising hundreds or thousands of satellites with many moving parts among them. With so much stuff in space, and a limited area around our planet, the government wants to reduce the chances of a collision. Two or more satellites slamming into each other could create many more out-of-control bits that would pose even more hazards to the growing collection of satellites in space.","And it’s not like this hasn’t happened before. In 2009 an old Russian craft slammed into a communications satellite, creating a cloud of hundreds of pieces of debris and putting other hardware at risk. Journalist Sarah Scoles reports that NASA currently tracks about 24,000 objects in space, and in 2016 the Air Force had to issue 3,995,874 warnings to satellite owners alerting them to a potential nearby threat from another satellite or bit of debris.","That’s why this new policy also includes directions to update the current U.S. Government Orbital Debris Mitigation Standard Practices, which already require any entity that launches a satellite or spacecraft to vigorously analyze the likelihood that any of their actions, from an unexpected failure or normal operations, will create more space debris. It includes accounting for any piece of debris they plan to release over 5mm that might stay in orbit for 25 years or more. It might seem surprising to think about an item staying in space for that long, but the oldest satellite still in orbit-Vanguard 1-turned 60 in 2018.","Agencies and companies throughout the world are working on developing technology that would dispose of or capture space debris before it causes serious damage. But for now, the U.S. government is more focused on preventing new debris from forming than taking the trash out of orbit."],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":"What is the purpose of the new U.S. space policy?","options":["A) To lay out general guidelines for space exploration.","B) To encourage companies to join in space programs.","C) To make the best use of satellites in space.","D) To improve traffic conditions in space."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查美国新太空政策的目标宗旨,依据题目顺序规律,搜寻目的状语可定位至首段( focused on.. . ,to mitigate. . . and track and manage.. . )。","analysis":"【精析】首段指出:新太空政策重在管理日益增多的太空卫星。第3号太空政策指令(新太空政策)为美国缓解太空碎片的影响以及追踪和管理太空交通制定了通用的指导方针,可见新政策旨在改善太空交通状况、减少太空碎片威胁,D正确。"},{"order":52,"question":"What is the Department of Commerce expected to do under the new policy?","options":["A) Reduce debris in space.","B) Monitor satellite operations.","C) Regulate the launching of new satellites.","D) Update satellite communications technology."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查新政策所规定的商务部职权,由关键词the Department of Commerce可定位至第二段①②句(the Department of Commerce... The department.. .)。","analysis":"【精析】第二段指出新政策将令商务部接手太空交通管理,商务部将确保新发射卫星不使用会干扰现有卫星的无线电频率,并安排何时才可发射这种新卫星,C正确。"},{"order":53,"question":"What does the U.S. government hope to do with the new space policy?","options":["A) Set international standards for the space flight industry.","B) Monopolize space industry by developing a set of norms.","C) Facilitate commercial space flights throughout the world.","D) Promote international collaboration in space exploration."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查美国新政策的愿景/深层目标,可定位至第二段③句(the hope is that it[the newpolicy] will help.. .)。","analysis":"【精析】第二段③句指出,美国新政策虽仅适用于本国,但美国希望它有助商业航天业形成一套标准化的全球准则,可见,美国新政策的深层目标是“为商业航天业确立国际标准”,A正确。"},{"order":54,"question":" What is a space vehicle launching entity required to do according to the current U.S. Government Orbital Debris Mitigation Standard Practices?","options":["A) Give an estimate of how long its debris will stay in space.","B) Account for the debris it has released into space at any time.","C) Provide a detailed plan for managing the space debris it creates.","D) Make a thorough analysis of any possible addition to space debris."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查现行“规范”对空间飞行器发射实体的要求,由关键词current U.S. GovernmentOrbital Debris Mitigation Standard Practices可定位至第五段。","analysis":"【精析】第五段指出,现行“规范”要求“任何发射卫星或航天器的实体,均需分析其任一行动产生太空碎片的可能,包括对计划释放的任一片5毫米以上的、可能会在轨道上滞留25年及以上的碎片作出解释(即,详尽分析任一可能释放的碎片,并对特定危险性碎片作出解释)”,D正确。"},{"order":55,"question":"What are space agencies and companies aiming to do at present?","options":["A) Recycle used space vehicles before they turn into debris.","B) Develop technology to address the space debris problem.","C) Limit the amount of debris entering space.","D) Cooperate closely to retrieve space debris."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查航天机构及企业当前努力方向,由关键词space agencies and companies aiming todo可定位至末段①句(Agencies and companies. . . are working on.. .)。","analysis":"【精析】末段①句指出,全世界的政府机构和企业都在努力开发可以处理或捕获太空碎片的技术,以防碎片造成严重损害,B正确。"}]}]}
{"_id":"150083c56198ed41030d0d1243732e76","id":"2019060303","type":"CET6","title":"SectionC","directions":"There are 2 passages in this section. Each passage is followed by some questions or unfinished statements. For each of them there are four choices marked A), B), C) and D). You should decide on the best choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.","exercises":[{"title":"Questions 46 to 50 are based on the following passage.","article":["When I re-entered the full-time workforce a few years ago after a decade of solitary self-employment, there was one thing I was looking forward to the most: the opportunity to have work friends once again. It wasn’t until I entered the corporate world that I realized, for me at least, being friends with colleagues didn’t emerge as a priority at all. This is surprising when you consider the prevailing emphasis by scholars and trainers and managers on the importance of cultivating close interpersonal relationships at work. So much research has explored the way in which collegial ( 同 事 的 ) ties can help overcome a range of workplace issues affecting productivity and the quality of work output such as team-based conflict, jealousy, undermining, anger, and more.","Perhaps my expectations of lunches, water-cooler gossip and caring, deep-and-meaningful conversations were a legacy of the last time I was in that kind of office environment. Whereas now, as I near the end of my fourth decade, I realize work can be fully functional and entirely fulfilling without needing to be best mates with the people sitting next to you.","In an academic analysis just published in the profoundly-respected Journal of Management, researchers have looked at the concept of “indifferent relationships”. It’s a simple term that encapsulates (概括) the fact that relationships at work can reasonably be non-intimate, inconsequential, unimportant and even, dare I say it, disposable or substitutable.","Indifferent relationships are neither positive nor negative. The limited research conducted thus far indicates they’re especially dominant among those who value independence over cooperation, and harmony over confrontation. Indifference is also the preferred option among those who are socially lazy. Maintaining relationships over the long term takes effort. For some of us, too much effort.","As noted above, indifferent relationships may not always be the most helpful approach in resolving some of the issues that pop up at work. But there are nonetheless several empirically proven benefits. One of those is efficiency. Less time chatting and socializing means more time working and churning (产出).","The other is self-esteem. As human beings, we’re primed to compare ourselves to each other in what is an anxiety-inducing phenomenon. Apparently, we look down on acquaintances more so than friends. Since the former is most common among those inclined towards indifferent relationships, their predominance can bolster individuals’ sense of self-worth.","Ego aside, a third advantage is that the emotional neutrality of indifferent relationships has been found to enhance critical evaluation, to strengthen one’s focus on task resolution, and to gain greater access to valuable information. None of that might be as fun as after-work socializing but, hey, I’ll take it anyway."],"questions":[{"order":46,"question":"What did the author realize when he re-entered the corporate world?","options":["A) Making new friends with his workmates was not as easy as he had anticipated.","B) Cultivating positive interpersonal relationships helped him expel solitary feelings.","C) Working in the corporate world requires more interpersonal skills than self-employment.","D) Building close relationships with his colleagues was not as important as he had expected."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查作者重回职场的感悟,由re-entered the corporate world定位至首段①②句(When I re-entered the full-time workforce... It wasn't until I enter the corporate world that... )。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案]D)。文首两句对比作者重回职场前后的心理感受:最期待与同事为友vs与同事为友根本算不上头等大事。可见,作者重回职场前以为与同事为友是头等大事,而重回职场后发现这根本算不上头等大事,故D)正确。"},{"order":47,"question":"What do we learn from many studies about collegial relationships?","options":["A) Inharmonious relationships have an adverse effect on productivity.","B) Harmonious relationships are what many companies aim to cultivate.","C) Close collegial relationships contribute very little to product quality.","D) Conflicting relationships in the workplace exist almost everywhere."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题考查有关同事关系的研究,由studies about collegial relationships 定位至首段末句(research...collegial ties...)。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案]A)。该句指出,许多研究探索了“(亲密)同事关系如何帮助克服职场中一系列影响工作效率和工作质量的问题的方式”,由此可见,密切/和谐的同事关系会对工作效率和质量有积极影响,而疏远/不和谐的同事关系会对工作效率和质量有消极影响。故A)正确,同时排除C)。"},{"order":48,"question":"What can be inferred about relationships at work from an academic analysis?","options":["A) They should be cultivated.","B) They are virtually irrelevant.","C) They are vital to corporate culture.","D) They should be reasonably intimate."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查学术分析中对职场关系的相关信息,由relationships at work、an academic analysis可定位至第三段(In an academic analysis...relationships at work...)。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案]B)。段中首先引出学术分析中探讨的概念:淡漠关系;随后对它进行具体介绍:这一术语简单,却囊括这样一个事实一职场关系可以不亲密、微不足道、不重要、甚至可以用完即扔或可任意取代。由此可推知,职场关系几乎无关紧要,故B)正确。"},{"order":49,"question":"What does the author say about people who are socially lazy?","options":["A) They feel Uncomfortable when engaging in social interactions.","B) They often find themselves in confrontation with their colleagues.","C) They are Unwilling to make efforts to maintain Workplace relationships.","D) They lack basic communication skills in dealing with interpersonal issues."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题考查作者对社交懒人的评价,由socially lazy定位至第四段③句。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案]C)。第四段③句指出,淡漠(关系)是社交懒人首选;随后④⑤句补充说明原因:长期维持关系需要付出(太多)努力。可见,对于社交懒人而言,他们不愿意努力维持职场关系,他们选择淡漠职场关系,认为职场关系并不重要(不影响工作效率及质量),故C)正确。"},{"order":50,"question":"What is one of the benefits of indifferent relationships?","options":["A) They provide fun at Work.","B) They help control emotions.","C) They help resolve differences.","D) They improve Work efficiency."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查淡漠关系的好处,由benefits of indifferent relationships定位至第五、六、七段。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案] D)。第五段末两句指出好处之一:效率花在闲聊、社交上的时间更少意味着有更好的时间来工作及产出,意即,淡漠关系能够提升工作效率,故D)正确。"}]},{"title":"Questions 51 to 55 are based on the following passage.","article":["In a few decades, artificial intelligence (AI) will surpass many of the abilities that we believe make us special. This is a grand challenge for our age and it may require an “irrational” response.","One of the most significant pieces of news from the US in early 2017 was the efforts of Google to make autonomous driving a reality. According to a report, Google’s self-driving cars clocked 1,023,330 km, and required human intervention 124 times. That is one intervention about every 8,047 km of autonomous driving. But even more impressive is the progress in just a single year: human interventions fell from 0.8 times per thousand miles to 0.2, a 400% improvement. With such progress, Google’s cars will easily surpass my own driving ability later this year.","Driving once seemed to be a very human skill. But we said that about chess, too. Then a computer beat the human world champion, repeatedly. The board game Go (围棋) took over from chess as a new test for human thinking in 2016, when a computer beat one of the world’s leading professional Go players. With computers conquering what used to be deeply human tasks, what will it mean in the future to be human? I worry about my six-year-old son. What will his place be in a world where machines beat us in one area after another? He’ll never calculate faster, never drive better, or even fly more safely. Actually, it all comes down to a fairly simple question: What’s so special about us? It can’t be skills like arithmetic, which machines already excel in. So far, machines have a pretty hard time emulating creativity, arbitrary enough not to be predicted by a computer, and yet more than simple randomness.","Perhaps, if we continue to improve information-processing machines, we’ll soon have helpful rational assistants. So we must aim to complement the rationality of the machine, rather than to compete with it. If I'm right, we should foster a creative spirit because a dose of illogical creativity will complement the rationality of the machine. Unfortunately, however, our education system has not caught up to the approaching reality. Indeed, our schools and universities are structured to mould pupils to be mostly obedient servants of rationality, and to develop outdated skills in interacting with outdated machines. We need to help our children learn how to best work with smart computers to improve human decision-making. But most of all we need to keep the long-term perspective in mind: that even if computers will outsmart us, we can still be the most creative. Because if we aren’t, we won’t be providing much value in future ecosystems, and that may put in question the foundation for our existence."],"questions":[{"order":51,"question":"What is the author’s greatest concern about the use of AI?","options":["A) Computers are performing lots of creative tasks.","B) Many abilities will cease to be unique to human beings.","C) Computers may become more rational than humans.","D) Many human skills are fast becoming outdated."],"answer":"B","location":"【定位】本题考查作者对AI应用的担忧,根据题干关键词greatest concern和AI定位至第一段(AI...grand challenge)。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案] B)。第一段①句介绍趋势:人工智能将在许多我们自以为独特的能力方面超越我们。②句评论:这是我们当今时代的一大挑战。由此可知,作者担忧AI的应用将导致很多能力不再为人类所独有,B正确。"},{"order":52,"question":"What impresses the author most in the field of AI?","options":["A) Google’s experimental driverless cars require little human intervention.","B) Google’s cars have surpassed his driving ability in just a single year.","C) Google has made huge progress in autonomous driving in a short time.","D) Google has become a world leader in the field of autonomous driving."],"answer":"C","location":"【定位】本题询问最令作者叹服的AI领域成就,可结合题干关键词impress与选项复现词Google定位至第二段(Google...impressive)。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案]C)。本段介绍了AI领域重大应用之一“谷歌自动驾驶汽车”。①句首先指出谷歌在自动驾驶方面的努力引发关注。②③句具体介绍其成就:自动驾驶汽车仅需要极少的人为干预操作。④句进而引出更令人叹服的内容:仅一年内自动化程度就提高400%。综上可知,最令作者印象深刻的当属谷歌自动驾驶技术“在短时间内取得的巨大进步”,C正确。"},{"order":53,"question":"What do we learn from the passage about creativity?","options":["A) It is rational.","B) It is predictable.","C) It is human specific.","D) It is yet to be emulated by AI."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题考查创造力的事实细节,定位至第三段末句(...creativity...)。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案]D)。该句指出,目前为止,机器(即AI)想模仿创造力还相当困难,因为创造力不是单纯的随机,它具有很强的任意性,不是计算机所能够推知的。故D正确,同时排除B。"},{"order":54,"question":"What should schools help children do in the era of AI?","options":["A) Cultivate original thinking.","B) Learn to work independently.","C) Compete with smart machines.","D) Understand how AI works."],"answer":"A","location":"【定位】本题询问学校在AI时代应履行的教育义务,根据题干关键词help children定位至第四段⑥句(help our children)。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案] A)。该句指出,我们需要帮助孩子,让他们学会如何与智能计算机合作,改善人类决策。而回顾②③句可知,人类需要借助创造力与机器的理性形成互补,我们需要鼓励创新精神。综上可知,学校应该鼓励并帮助学童培养创新思维,A正确。"},{"order":55,"question":"How can we humans justify our future existence?","options":["A) By constantly outsmarting computers.","B) By adopting a long-term perspective.","C) By rationally compromising with AI.","D) By providing value with our creativity."],"answer":"D","location":"【定位】本题询问“人类如何为我们未来的存在正名(=要想不被机器淘汰，应该如何做)”,根据题干关键词our future existence定位至第四段末句。","analysis":"【精析】[锁定答案] D)。本句指出,如果我们做不到这点(we aren't),那么我们就不能在未来创造多少价值,从而动摇自身存在的根基。回溯⑦句可知,“这点”的具体内容即指“具有创造力(be the most creative)”。综上可知,未来人类需要利用创造力创造价值,这样才能捍卫自身存在,D正确。"}]}]}
